[{
  "email": "yassin",
  "interactions": [{
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "7dfeae57-3155-4fc5-b230-75d482897942",
    "question": "Quiz Question 5: What is 'dog' in French?",
    "response": "Answer: d, Feedback: That's not correct. The correct answer is: chien",
    "timestamp": 1747599006071,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "2c374b56-1dad-4660-a91e-1fe890771788",
    "question": "Quiz Question 4: What is 'book' in French?",
    "response": "Answer: dd, Feedback: That's not correct. The correct answer is: livre",
    "timestamp": 1747599005444,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "2b5f8009-3ed3-4d54-8cd7-5d57e6dba448",
    "question": "Quiz Question 3: What is 'food' in French?",
    "response": "Answer: d, Feedback: That's not correct. The correct answer is: nourriture",
    "timestamp": 1747599004575,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "9db7b12f-5f81-406e-b51b-d50f75dcdcfc",
    "question": "Quiz Question 2: What is 'house' in French?",
    "response": "Answer: d, Feedback: That's not correct. The correct answer is: maison",
    "timestamp": 1747599004293,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "6235945b-24fa-4e68-b355-c30a822a389d",
    "question": "Quiz Question 1: What is 'family' in French?",
    "response": "Answer: d, Feedback: That's not correct. The correct answer is: famille",
    "timestamp": 1747599003973,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "48745e42-d1d3-47c0-9e57-c0cd359b134f",
    "question": "What type of quiz would you like to take?",
    "response": "1",
    "timestamp": 1747599000257,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "97b2e316-c65d-429f-b051-61d956f1d398",
    "question": "Quiz Question 5: What is 'family' in French?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: That's not correct. The correct answer is: famille",
    "timestamp": 1747598989070,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "759ac537-0025-4e82-b9c7-f20a8c460f2e",
    "question": "Quiz Question 4: What is 'book' in French?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747598988421,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "ace6d945-d002-45c6-ae1c-ae7beef83079",
    "question": "Quiz Question 3: What is 'house' in French?",
    "response": "Answer: s, Feedback: That's not correct. The correct answer is: maison",
    "timestamp": 1747598987848,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "98aa4a29-9f33-4606-bdc5-038fcf65da00",
    "question": "Quiz Question 2: What is 'dog' in French?",
    "response": "Answer: c, Feedback: That's not correct. The correct answer is: chien",
    "timestamp": 1747598987015,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "22db0def-aebd-4a19-9d9b-ceca5fe27db5",
    "question": "Quiz Question 1: What is 'food' in French?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: That's not correct. The correct answer is: nourriture",
    "timestamp": 1747598985574,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "ceb22715-9955-485f-8192-f88209f1c74d",
    "question": "What type of quiz would you like to take?",
    "response": "1",
    "timestamp": 1747598982824,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "d5c85f0d-fecc-4064-986f-a1b4aa84ab15",
    "question": "Quiz Question 5: What is 'family' in French?",
    "response": "Answer: f, Feedback: That's not correct. The correct answer is: famille",
    "timestamp": 1747598408393,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "577cdd3d-fa30-4681-b004-62275312ec0c",
    "question": "Quiz Question 4: What is 'book' in French?",
    "response": "Answer: f, Feedback: That's not correct. The correct answer is: livre",
    "timestamp": 1747598407763,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "aee2a3d7-13c0-4b15-bbfa-92f2a9954b05",
    "question": "Quiz Question 3: What is 'food' in French?",
    "response": "Answer: d, Feedback: That's not correct. The correct answer is: nourriture",
    "timestamp": 1747598407270,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "2631055c-f38c-478a-9fae-ca2c266364b1",
    "question": "Quiz Question 2: What is 'dog' in French?",
    "response": "Answer: as, Feedback: That's not correct. The correct answer is: chien",
    "timestamp": 1747598406508,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "7ab57c88-6a40-4f99-94cb-3f32457dac08",
    "question": "Quiz Question 1: What is 'house' in French?",
    "response": "Answer: d, Feedback: That's not correct. The correct answer is: maison",
    "timestamp": 1747598405327,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "5c20dad0-b27b-4b95-a5b2-b2e6c21e83aa",
    "question": "What type of quiz would you like to take?",
    "response": "1",
    "timestamp": 1747598401776,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "dcfd9bae-07fc-4f80-bfea-778e36269d48",
    "question": "Quiz Question 5: What is 'family' in French?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: That's not correct. The correct answer is: famille",
    "timestamp": 1747598396135,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "7497c854-314a-4716-adb3-00285d61b69a",
    "question": "Quiz Question 4: What is 'book' in French?",
    "response": "Answer: aa, Feedback: That's not correct. The correct answer is: livre",
    "timestamp": 1747598395703,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "a01dcc3e-eda4-4ba9-b5c7-eb5154b620ac",
    "question": "Quiz Question 3: What is 'food' in French?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: That's not correct. The correct answer is: nourriture",
    "timestamp": 1747598394938,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "daa2c258-2603-41e4-8318-8227607d306f",
    "question": "Quiz Question 2: What is 'dog' in French?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: That's not correct. The correct answer is: chien",
    "timestamp": 1747598394609,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "847a8292-d2c0-4017-a34e-bcd2652e0281",
    "question": "Quiz Question 1: What is 'house' in French?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747598394291,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "9641ca48-0297-464a-a050-e57c794bd011",
    "question": "What type of quiz would you like to take?",
    "response": "1",
    "timestamp": 1747598392875,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "91d7ed55-9fdf-4ae2-8de9-2f5757e3915f",
    "question": "Quiz Question 5: What is 'family' in French?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: That's not correct. The correct answer is: famille",
    "timestamp": 1747598276507,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "25c8d4eb-86bf-4f4c-bcd0-bbaf5285c6ab",
    "question": "Quiz Question 4: What is 'book' in French?",
    "response": "Answer: xs, Feedback: That's not correct. The correct answer is: livre",
    "timestamp": 1747598275954,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "3dd3d642-6a4c-4521-b04b-968cce5ee497",
    "question": "Quiz Question 3: What is 'food' in French?",
    "response": "Answer: x, Feedback: That's not correct. The correct answer is: nourriture",
    "timestamp": 1747598274549,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "6d2e04a1-a2dd-4233-b8ab-ab1fe28ce648",
    "question": "Quiz Question 2: What is 'dog' in French?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: That's not correct. The correct answer is: chien",
    "timestamp": 1747598272845,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "0e38965e-8168-4fea-8c66-36360e4e16be",
    "question": "Quiz Question 1: What is 'house' in French?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747598257230,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "907bb9dc-a105-4a46-b7d4-c839e9c4ed50",
    "question": "What type of quiz would you like to take?",
    "response": "1",
    "timestamp": 1747598247302,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "04c36921-b314-4c68-8383-ab01219b5c2d",
    "question": "Quiz Question 5: What is 'family' in French?",
    "response": "Answer: aa, Feedback: That's not correct. The correct answer is: famille",
    "timestamp": 1747598239163,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "5fccf4d2-9276-4272-ad49-bedd8652fb89",
    "question": "Quiz Question 4: What is 'book' in French?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747598238510,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "e5546234-151e-4f4c-bcca-f66585ad092f",
    "question": "Quiz Question 3: What is 'food' in French?",
    "response": "Answer: aa, Feedback: That's not correct. The correct answer is: nourriture",
    "timestamp": 1747598238119,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "558c9a60-4bd8-4f44-a516-bc9686f35c8a",
    "question": "Quiz Question 2: What is 'dog' in French?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: That's not correct. The correct answer is: chien",
    "timestamp": 1747598237276,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "59d93d9a-e7d4-4789-b0a3-61a4b56859a2",
    "question": "Quiz Question 1: What is 'house' in French?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747598236951,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "f73a1405-3fc8-4dd8-b325-0166082bc5b8",
    "question": "What type of quiz would you like to take?",
    "response": "1",
    "timestamp": 1747598235381,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "system",
    "id": "02a0e5b6-b6b5-4276-a0de-5c69d49e120e",
    "question": "help",
    "response": "\nAvailable commands:\n1. chat - Start a conversation\n2. quiz - Take a quiz\n3. history - View your learning history\n4. preferences - Set your language preferences\n5. help - Show this help message\n6. logout - Log out\n7. exit - Exit the application\n",
    "timestamp": 1747598225200,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "system",
    "id": "6323355e-aeb3-47da-8333-fbe82c3f958f",
    "question": "help",
    "response": "\nAvailable commands:\n1. chat - Start a conversation\n2. quiz - Take a quiz\n3. history - View your learning history\n4. preferences - Set your language preferences\n5. help - Show this help message\n6. logout - Log out\n7. exit - Exit the application\n",
    "timestamp": 1747596997345,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "f0f83897-8cd7-4f7d-9e7f-7093bf989b01",
    "question": "Quiz Question 5: Select the correct sentence:",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: That's not correct. The correct answer is: Ich esse einen Apfel",
    "timestamp": 1747596990024,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "72eaa621-5efb-4666-8cba-16b36552ffc1",
    "question": "Quiz Question 4: Which word is a verb?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: That's not correct. The correct answer is: lesen",
    "timestamp": 1747596989003,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "539ac891-4a3f-4754-bf09-788cf10f98eb",
    "question": "Quiz Question 3: What is the plural form of 'das Buch'?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: That's not correct. The correct answer is: die Bücher",
    "timestamp": 1747596988739,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "15548b08-48c6-48ca-9d1e-d7d48767de7f",
    "question": "Quiz Question 2: Which article matches with 'Haus'?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: That's not correct. The correct answer is: das",
    "timestamp": 1747596988459,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "7ccdf495-c8ec-46d2-a4dc-bdaa841d0191",
    "question": "Quiz Question 1: Which is the correct conjugation of 'sprechen' for 'ich'?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747596988153,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "d101daf1-dffa-4062-9a19-3c27a5dc7acc",
    "question": "What type of quiz would you like to take?",
    "response": "2",
    "timestamp": 1747596984111,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "607efeb7-71cf-4d21-a1d2-344ec8524ebb",
    "question": "Quiz Question 5: Select the correct sentence:",
    "response": "Answer: d, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747596966613,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "65216920-51ed-4ddf-afae-23b72d4cb859",
    "question": "Quiz Question 4: Which word is a verb?",
    "response": "Answer: c, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747596958668,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "051462da-9dcc-45c0-8cc4-eebed5186c1b",
    "question": "Quiz Question 3: What is the plural form of 'das Buch'?",
    "response": "Answer: c, Feedback: That's not correct. The correct answer is: die Bücher",
    "timestamp": 1747596951011,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "c56d4bcc-fff5-4793-b945-5cac41b6b012",
    "question": "Quiz Question 2: Which article matches with 'Haus'?",
    "response": "Answer: c, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747596942343,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "e07b97ba-f443-4aca-bf1b-03a87f9f1f50",
    "question": "Quiz Question 1: Which is the correct conjugation of 'sprechen' for 'ich'?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747596938139,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "51c9128c-4a96-40d9-b98b-f2c29ee55ff5",
    "question": "What type of quiz would you like to take?",
    "response": "2",
    "timestamp": 1747596931699,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "925d1a1e-1f92-44f9-9641-cc9a28658e9f",
    "question": "What type of quiz would you like to take?",
    "response": "",
    "timestamp": 1747596924811,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "settings",
    "id": "a49b9597-7a0a-4ea8-83c1-8d737daf2a76",
    "question": "set target language german",
    "response": "Target language set to German",
    "timestamp": 1747596915506,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "settings",
    "id": "0e69f4aa-f51b-4e01-b901-7f337e725633",
    "question": "set mother language english",
    "response": "Mother language set to English",
    "timestamp": 1747596905816,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "system",
    "id": "34f95d23-24aa-427e-a31a-ec91310e57e8",
    "question": "save settings",
    "response": "Displayed user settings",
    "timestamp": 1747596885377,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "settings",
    "id": "70e87396-e4df-405b-ba8c-54d9461cb8af",
    "question": "settings",
    "response": "You can change your settings for:\n- Mother language\n- Target language\nWhat would you like to update?",
    "timestamp": 1747596885372,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "settings",
    "id": "c0850591-2969-47e8-9520-a27bd6aacfea",
    "question": "set target language german",
    "response": "Target language set to German",
    "timestamp": 1747596873443,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "settings",
    "id": "130c1405-7fba-4d9d-870e-60b39aecbc88",
    "question": "set mother language spanish",
    "response": "Mother language set to Spanish",
    "timestamp": 1747596859166,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "system",
    "id": "7b2a5e40-1f27-4e2f-8941-802dece464b6",
    "question": "preferences",
    "response": "Displayed user settings",
    "timestamp": 1747596848770,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "settings",
    "id": "d5746dd9-f46b-45da-b6ae-bfa72ff39207",
    "question": "settings",
    "response": "You can change your settings for:\n- Mother language\n- Target language\nWhat would you like to update?",
    "timestamp": 1747596848753,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "system",
    "id": "43aef4e3-39be-4f62-bc14-29a6b8e1769b",
    "question": "help",
    "response": "\nAvailable commands:\n1. chat - Start a conversation\n2. quiz - Take a quiz\n3. history - View your learning history\n4. preferences - Set your language preferences\n5. help - Show this help message\n6. logout - Log out\n7. exit - Exit the application\n",
    "timestamp": 1747596842494,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "unknown",
    "id": "7ba73a01-66ea-4f6e-971c-ec801762090f",
    "question": "",
    "response": "I'm not sure I understand. Try asking about quizzes, changing settings.",
    "timestamp": 1747596392303,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "chat",
    "id": "ada07f72-a841-41d2-8b3c-74377af5108c",
    "question": "Is it hot or cold outside?",
    "response": "cold weather",
    "timestamp": 1747596382224,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "chat",
    "id": "7dbbd7df-256d-4343-bb93-82632365e641",
    "question": "Is it hot or cold outside?",
    "response": "light clothing",
    "timestamp": 1747596372223,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "chat",
    "id": "6c561622-ac63-4813-8d54-1d690a996964",
    "question": "Is it hot or cold outside?",
    "response": "light",
    "timestamp": 1747596363198,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "chat",
    "id": "6ffe8334-beb4-4bd1-a32b-075ae19358f1",
    "question": "Is it hot or cold outside?",
    "response": "hot",
    "timestamp": 1747596353265,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "system",
    "id": "a875172a-e45b-4d5a-bbfa-cee9c13c0244",
    "question": "help",
    "response": "\nAvailable commands:\n1. chat - Start a conversation\n2. quiz - Take a quiz\n3. history - View your learning history\n4. preferences - Set your language preferences\n5. help - Show this help message\n6. logout - Log out\n7. exit - Exit the application\n",
    "timestamp": 1747596344732,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "system",
    "id": "0d3fe592-347e-44b5-876f-c03840310bab",
    "question": "help",
    "response": "\nAvailable commands:\n1. chat - Start a conversation\n2. quiz - Take a quiz\n3. history - View your learning history\n4. preferences - Set your language preferences\n5. help - Show this help message\n6. logout - Log out\n7. exit - Exit the application\n",
    "timestamp": 1747596079481,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "chat",
    "id": "0800e260-bd10-4b12-9ec7-3a5e01de892e",
    "question": "What's your favorite season?",
    "response": "shirt",
    "timestamp": 1747595854945,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "chat",
    "id": "5615413c-8590-4223-978e-412bc184efbd",
    "question": "What's your favorite season?",
    "response": "warm",
    "timestamp": 1747595844357,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "chat",
    "id": "f7d7d594-dcaf-46ff-88ed-6b564600a3f1",
    "question": "What's your favorite season?",
    "response": "summer",
    "timestamp": 1747595839165,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "system",
    "id": "102a071d-2744-4830-8afe-0df5aaec6e37",
    "question": "prefrences",
    "response": "Displayed user settings",
    "timestamp": 1747595820627,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "settings",
    "id": "f09943da-5780-4175-b854-c1b952cd4ccb",
    "question": "settings",
    "response": "You can change your settings for:\n- Mother language\n- Target language\nWhat would you like to update?",
    "timestamp": 1747595820619,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "settings",
    "id": "bb89e63e-7961-49a7-bbd6-dbe3e774fca6",
    "question": "settngs",
    "response": "You can change your settings for:\n- Mother language\n- Target language\nWhat would you like to update?",
    "timestamp": 1747595813423,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "settings",
    "id": "ea239ced-21dd-4e25-ac52-02bd1b65823d",
    "question": "set target language french",
    "response": "Target language set to French",
    "timestamp": 1747595810862,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "settings",
    "id": "f8ed9b54-15c0-428b-a789-82dea1c9e6aa",
    "question": "set mother language english",
    "response": "Mother language set to English",
    "timestamp": 1747595800324,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "system",
    "id": "77463d77-5d2f-4b07-9b3b-e897efb699f2",
    "question": "help",
    "response": "\nAvailable commands:\n1. chat - Start a conversation\n2. quiz - Take a quiz\n3. history - View your learning history\n4. preferences - Set your language preferences\n5. help - Show this help message\n6. logout - Log out\n7. exit - Exit the application\n",
    "timestamp": 1747595789258,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "unknown",
    "id": "4324437b-dbf6-4dee-8749-f0cffb256d43",
    "question": "exit chat",
    "response": "I'm not sure I understand. Try asking about quizzes, changing settings.",
    "timestamp": 1747595749126,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "unknown",
    "id": "5ae2a524-7e83-43d4-8287-c0b390ea312e",
    "question": "swimming",
    "response": "I'm not sure I understand. Try asking about quizzes, changing settings.",
    "timestamp": 1747595733490,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "chat",
    "id": "793c0a9e-5523-4799-ae23-3da3af2182dd",
    "question": "How is the weather today?",
    "response": "shirt",
    "timestamp": 1747595724666,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "chat",
    "id": "10510765-5d45-44ea-a697-665e98eacb4c",
    "question": "How is the weather today?",
    "response": "hot",
    "timestamp": 1747595706878,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "chat",
    "id": "5f4ba475-3cfa-436f-bc84-08eb511a9192",
    "question": "How is the weather today?",
    "response": "coat",
    "timestamp": 1747595692657,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "chat",
    "id": "4b357a45-2014-49be-a7d6-c3a92fe3d030",
    "question": "How is the weather today?",
    "response": "cold",
    "timestamp": 1747595684073,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "system",
    "id": "3881d54f-556a-41f2-a321-f1f13d5ba827",
    "question": "help",
    "response": "\nAvailable commands:\n1. chat - Start a conversation\n2. quiz - Take a quiz\n3. history - View your learning history\n4. preferences - Set your language preferences\n5. help - Show this help message\n6. logout - Log out\n7. exit - Exit the application\n",
    "timestamp": 1747595675407,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "chat",
    "id": "32103e74-4276-4573-8e6b-7143ea369f76",
    "question": "Is it hot or cold outside?",
    "response": "cold",
    "timestamp": 1747595402023,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "chat",
    "id": "c75f9c4d-3500-4bb4-965b-74ebad33e378",
    "question": "What's your favorite season?",
    "response": "exit chat",
    "timestamp": 1747595384806,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "chat",
    "id": "634ccc5c-a31f-4a16-b021-fe1fc8131802",
    "question": "What's your favorite season?",
    "response": "",
    "timestamp": 1747595374986,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "system",
    "id": "9f33bf40-257f-494e-9465-7d51465a8923",
    "question": "help",
    "response": "\nAvailable commands:\n1. chat - Start a conversation\n2. quiz - Take a quiz\n3. history - View your learning history\n4. preferences - Set your language preferences\n5. help - Show this help message\n6. logout - Log out\n7. exit - Exit the application\n",
    "timestamp": 1747595372395,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "chat",
    "id": "f14658c7-e0d5-447f-9c61-921c26bf30a4",
    "question": "How is the weather today?",
    "response": "warm",
    "timestamp": 1747595301467,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "chat",
    "id": "e246d7f9-b19e-4710-9e25-aa25d657c430",
    "question": "How is the weather today?",
    "response": "thanks",
    "timestamp": 1747595292926,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "chat",
    "id": "be18ec5d-95ea-46d4-9237-50a704a8d498",
    "question": "How is the weather today?",
    "response": "cool",
    "timestamp": 1747595272607,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "system",
    "id": "0624a885-9740-4175-a2ed-980bc7e3b35a",
    "question": "help",
    "response": "\nAvailable commands:\n1. chat - Start a conversation\n2. quiz - Take a quiz\n3. history - View your learning history\n4. preferences - Set your language preferences\n5. help - Show this help message\n6. logout - Log out\n7. exit - Exit the application\n",
    "timestamp": 1747595162678,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "weather",
    "id": "58a1a433-2e8a-4e70-9345-b87efcbf86ea",
    "question": "weather is hot",
    "response": "It sounds hot! I recommend wearing light, breathable clothes like shorts and a t-shirt. Stay hydrated, use sunscreen, and try to stay in the shade when possible. A hat can also help protect you from the sun.",
    "timestamp": 1747594778440,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "unknown",
    "id": "8d0624fa-e63b-405b-8707-637eaf855880",
    "question": "chat",
    "response": "I'm not sure I understand. Try asking about quizzes, changing settings.",
    "timestamp": 1747594764154,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "system",
    "id": "9b46e8ab-6c79-4f0e-a2dd-371c6cc22781",
    "question": "help",
    "response": "\nAvailable commands:\n1. chat - Start a conversation\n2. quiz - Take a quiz\n3. history - View your learning history\n4. preferences - Set your language preferences\n5. help - Show this help message\n6. logout - Log out\n7. exit - Exit the application\n",
    "timestamp": 1747594762241,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "56c41cac-cc60-4116-b833-f32c910cbaf4",
    "question": "exit quiz",
    "response": "Exited quiz mode",
    "timestamp": 1747594758409,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "02517620-4b2a-4d7d-901e-7e5382b66b15",
    "question": "1",
    "response": "Started a Vocabulary quiz",
    "timestamp": 1747594749255,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "system",
    "id": "31f15422-0685-4efb-a5bc-2cf971f1e590",
    "question": "help",
    "response": "\nAvailable commands:\n1. chat - Start a conversation\n2. quiz - Take a quiz\n3. history - View your learning history\n4. preferences - Set your language preferences\n5. help - Show this help message\n6. logout - Log out\n7. exit - Exit the application\n",
    "timestamp": 1747594747504,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "system",
    "id": "5a0e5ccb-5d88-449c-aa76-7c997e3390f9",
    "question": "settings",
    "response": "Displayed user settings",
    "timestamp": 1747592849908,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "settings",
    "id": "83c9700e-172d-4e20-9c1b-d9bce58a0ae3",
    "question": "settings",
    "response": "You can change your settings for:\n- Mother language\n- Target language\nWhat would you like to update?",
    "timestamp": 1747592849902,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "936abe4a-7aa4-45fc-9724-41aafb965824",
    "question": "quit quiz",
    "response": "Cancelled quiz setup",
    "timestamp": 1747592844661,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "c3297530-c296-44c0-bb5e-ca7923247fe4",
    "question": "What type of quiz would you like to take?",
    "response": "quit quiz",
    "timestamp": 1747592844645,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "system",
    "id": "5c60ff4c-002a-4256-9a66-9ea4d519673e",
    "question": "help",
    "response": "\r\nAvailable commands:\r\n1. chat - Start a conversation\r\n2. quiz - Take a quiz\r\n3. history - View your learning history\r\n4. preferences - Set your language preferences\r\n5. help - Show this help message\r\n6. logout - Log out\r\n7. exit - Exit the application\r\n",
    "timestamp": 1747592825490,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "b4147ebc-f994-4d7e-ae90-48f114cfafd7",
    "question": "exit quiz",
    "response": "Cancelled quiz setup",
    "timestamp": 1747592707305,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "8dbab25a-71a1-43da-9fab-7301b5f442e9",
    "question": "What type of quiz would you like to take?",
    "response": "exit quiz",
    "timestamp": 1747592707298,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "313ee997-8018-4956-b9e7-14192713e67d",
    "question": "What type of quiz would you like to take?",
    "response": "exit",
    "timestamp": 1747592700518,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "system",
    "id": "201c7ebd-0c08-4793-9586-22a679abdec7",
    "question": "settings",
    "response": "Displayed user settings",
    "timestamp": 1747592282690,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "settings",
    "id": "9e15150b-b2e7-4ffc-b095-8888d958c7ba",
    "question": "settings",
    "response": "You can change your settings for:\n- Mother language\n- Target language\nWhat would you like to update?",
    "timestamp": 1747592282685,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "7c7f3dcc-f600-407a-9b78-431e06c9de37",
    "question": "exit quiz",
    "response": "Cancelled quiz setup",
    "timestamp": 1747592279231,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "3d3eac46-4c76-4564-99cc-198e207212ca",
    "question": "What type of quiz would you like to take?",
    "response": "exit quiz",
    "timestamp": 1747592279224,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "78a04c76-0368-4d96-bc9f-23c4a42be7ed",
    "question": "exit quiz",
    "response": "Cancelled quiz setup",
    "timestamp": 1747592263018,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "257c2e74-6121-4a86-a5f3-1950b91dbb14",
    "question": "What type of quiz would you like to take?",
    "response": "exit quiz",
    "timestamp": 1747592263012,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "8f71744b-aeaf-4222-aa88-c5bf1efb520f",
    "question": "What type of quiz would you like to take?",
    "response": "quiz",
    "timestamp": 1747592258906,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "settings",
    "id": "9e8727d1-057f-44d4-b5ca-01bf9d0d11c6",
    "question": "set target language french",
    "response": "Target language set to French",
    "timestamp": 1747592238220,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "settings",
    "id": "701e2350-662b-4755-a2ba-58a5bf523cbf",
    "question": "set mother language spanish",
    "response": "Mother language set to Spanish",
    "timestamp": 1747592230131,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "a3ba19c1-469f-4f5e-a642-bc7eb0760265",
    "question": "exit quiz",
    "response": "Cancelled quiz setup",
    "timestamp": 1747592219083,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "ee466025-1564-4025-b9de-21661e3e84d2",
    "question": "What type of quiz would you like to take?",
    "response": "exit quiz",
    "timestamp": 1747592219070,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "system",
    "id": "682bbc18-06a9-4502-b071-4337f0276f32",
    "question": "settings",
    "response": "Displayed user settings",
    "timestamp": 1747592190357,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "settings",
    "id": "fcde93fc-a4e9-4130-be6b-3313d6365320",
    "question": "settings",
    "response": "You can change your settings for:\n- Mother language\n- Target language\nWhat would you like to update?",
    "timestamp": 1747592190305,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "20e530a9-df3e-4743-8bdd-4e6f1b49a79f",
    "question": "What type of quiz would you like to take?",
    "response": "3",
    "timestamp": 1747591645124,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "system",
    "id": "210469d4-2797-4493-85b3-5034c7eb569d",
    "question": "settings",
    "response": "Displayed user settings",
    "timestamp": 1747591633385,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "settings",
    "id": "bb781fbb-1ac5-41f8-9cba-e4aa372cf867",
    "question": "settings",
    "response": "You can change your settings for:\n- Mother language\n- Target language\nWhat would you like to update?",
    "timestamp": 1747591633381,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "settings",
    "id": "8aa0237c-17e6-4f1b-882a-ad17a0e5dea7",
    "question": "set target language french",
    "response": "Target language set to French",
    "timestamp": 1747591628860,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "settings",
    "id": "50f79260-0a18-4078-9967-a14a5d6defb0",
    "question": "set mother language english",
    "response": "Mother language set to English",
    "timestamp": 1747591613226,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "system",
    "id": "f1abe759-617d-40ff-9690-2187e80bda96",
    "question": "settings",
    "response": "Displayed user settings",
    "timestamp": 1747591582803,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "settings",
    "id": "a76f99dc-ee27-400a-a18f-42310941dbad",
    "question": "settings",
    "response": "You can change your settings for:\n- Mother language\n- Target language\nWhat would you like to update?",
    "timestamp": 1747591582799,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "settings",
    "id": "54326d09-5f8d-413b-80b8-95d479d099a6",
    "question": "set target language german",
    "response": "Target language set to German",
    "timestamp": 1747591575320,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "settings",
    "id": "29e94fe7-831b-4aa3-b96b-4226e25486bd",
    "question": "set mother language spanish",
    "response": "Mother language set to Spanish",
    "timestamp": 1747591567378,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "system",
    "id": "24e0270d-b36e-4900-8051-2e23ef3f28e7",
    "question": "preferences",
    "response": "Displayed user settings",
    "timestamp": 1747591495420,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "settings",
    "id": "dbf8fb60-eb2b-4ee6-8879-ef629f15b118",
    "question": "settings",
    "response": "You can change your settings for:\n- Mother language\n- Target language\nWhat would you like to update?",
    "timestamp": 1747591495393,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "system",
    "id": "453ba0a9-696d-4b15-90ed-21d86702ea2b",
    "question": "help",
    "response": "\r\nAvailable commands:\r\n1. chat - Start a conversation\r\n2. quiz - Take a quiz\r\n3. history - View your learning history\r\n4. preferences - Set your language preferences\r\n5. help - Show this help message\r\n6. logout - Log out\r\n7. exit - Exit the application\r\n",
    "timestamp": 1747591488603,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "system",
    "id": "d6078ade-f477-4861-be2a-bb3fc828e1dd",
    "question": "settings",
    "response": "Displayed user settings",
    "timestamp": 1747591178902,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "settings",
    "id": "ddf16dcd-3eb3-4f8a-a300-0d5e04389386",
    "question": "settings",
    "response": "You can change your settings for:\n- Mother language\n- Target language\nWhat would you like to update?",
    "timestamp": 1747591178894,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "system",
    "id": "aebb414a-8984-4464-a43a-f1418e12fcb4",
    "question": "help",
    "response": "\r\nAvailable commands:\r\n1. chat - Start a conversation\r\n2. quiz - Take a quiz\r\n3. history - View your learning history\r\n4. preferences - Set your language preferences\r\n5. help - Show this help message\r\n6. logout - Log out\r\n7. exit - Exit the application\r\n",
    "timestamp": 1747591171079,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "39ac8cee-5885-43fc-bd0e-48c99a4def4e",
    "question": "Quiz Question 5: Select the correct sentence:",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: That's not correct. The correct answer is: Tú comes manzanas",
    "timestamp": 1747591057834,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "60292e81-aee8-4e33-9381-9f0130f3229a",
    "question": "Quiz Question 4: Which word is a verb?",
    "response": "Answer: c, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747591055828,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "558c2e06-dc3d-42f1-8b2f-946c704559f2",
    "question": "Quiz Question 3: What is the plural form of 'el libro'?",
    "response": "Answer: b, Feedback: That's not correct. The correct answer is: los libros",
    "timestamp": 1747591053858,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "cd8fb5df-348b-47e5-9fa1-20ddad951642",
    "question": "Quiz Question 2: Which article matches with 'casa'?",
    "response": "Answer: b, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747591053192,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "1b1ad3fe-3b8d-4d82-8652-c6cbe95f5a52",
    "question": "Quiz Question 1: Which is the correct conjugation of 'hablar' for 'yo'?",
    "response": "Answer: c, Feedback: That's not correct. The correct answer is: hablo",
    "timestamp": 1747591047954,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "789c4cd5-e2b7-4661-9ab2-1b6e5d7dbed7",
    "question": "What type of quiz would you like to take?",
    "response": "grammar",
    "timestamp": 1747591044613,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "system",
    "id": "fd7e6677-459f-4eaa-8d63-e01fcc1f9907",
    "question": "analytics",
    "response": "Displayed user analytics",
    "timestamp": 1747591026135,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "a35a5e34-3a09-43a4-a13a-ce77a5781162",
    "question": "Quiz Question 5: What is 'family' in Spanish?",
    "response": "Answer: c, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747590983680,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "d1698108-dd9f-424c-b64d-14ee061e72ff",
    "question": "Quiz Question 4: What is 'book' in Spanish?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747590978798,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "74e10a5a-9124-4727-9fc7-f8fd14eecc4f",
    "question": "Quiz Question 3: What is 'food' in Spanish?",
    "response": "Answer: b, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747590973998,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "a11751c8-25d0-4056-92d2-a8b704048f1b",
    "question": "Quiz Question 2: What is 'dog' in Spanish?",
    "response": "Answer: , Feedback: That's not correct. The correct answer is: perro",
    "timestamp": 1747590946105,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "51f41e8e-3e90-42ae-86e3-0d0e1bfeef28",
    "question": "Quiz Question 1: What is 'house' in Spanish?",
    "response": "Answer: , Feedback: That's not correct. The correct answer is: casa",
    "timestamp": 1747590945108,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "d617c192-e72a-44b4-a1e2-bd2d2cbf0b17",
    "question": "What type of quiz would you like to take?",
    "response": "1",
    "timestamp": 1747590942898,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "language_question",
    "id": "10a63c31-4429-4c9f-8b4c-762c95eb3bb2",
    "question": "hi",
    "response": "Hello, yassin! I'm your Language Learning Bot. Would you like to practice vocabulary, grammar, or start a quiz?",
    "timestamp": 1747590937341,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "unknown",
    "id": "bf96b786-89d2-4e3e-9fab-3859eb8cc4f3",
    "question": "hello",
    "response": "Hello, yassin! I'm your Language Learning Bot. Would you like to practice vocabulary, grammar, or start a quiz?",
    "timestamp": 1747590935381,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "system",
    "id": "71623493-584a-43e8-b708-a11b3dc30875",
    "question": "settings",
    "response": "Displayed user settings",
    "timestamp": 1747590925339,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "settings",
    "id": "6c8acb6c-3d83-4a89-be8b-c93018b138f6",
    "question": "settings",
    "response": "You can change your settings for:\n- Mother language\n- Target language\nWhat would you like to update?",
    "timestamp": 1747590925293,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "9fb8f1e6-d384-4170-8edc-fa71daa9b24f",
    "question": "exit quiz",
    "response": "Exited quiz mode",
    "timestamp": 1747590550527,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "70c72eb7-44d7-40ba-a12c-981ac508af2b",
    "question": "What type of quiz would you like to take?",
    "response": "1",
    "timestamp": 1747590484389,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "language_question",
    "id": "71138f9f-419c-466b-ab9b-5fa8dade711d",
    "question": "hi",
    "response": "Hello, yassin! I'm your Language Learning Bot. Would you like to practice vocabulary, grammar, or start a quiz?",
    "timestamp": 1747590473720,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "unknown",
    "id": "b9521ae4-2363-43c9-8630-524c0c0ed9bc",
    "question": "hello",
    "response": "Hello, yassin! I'm your Language Learning Bot. Would you like to practice vocabulary, grammar, or start a quiz?",
    "timestamp": 1747590471125,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "unknown",
    "id": "6d798d5b-0d9c-4c92-9399-ce3508681c9b",
    "question": ".\\run_app.bat",
    "response": "I'm not sure I understand. Try asking about quizzes, changing settings.",
    "timestamp": 1747590394822,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "1fa56ac6-23b7-40ee-8b4a-d3bd8d6b1d4d",
    "question": "What type of quiz would you like to take?",
    "response": "3",
    "timestamp": 1747589748479,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "c9af1c49-d17f-4117-b86b-d72399575cf1",
    "question": "exit quiz",
    "response": "Exited quiz mode",
    "timestamp": 1747589742160,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "2c027f40-d595-4e24-b522-572efe80dada",
    "question": "What type of quiz would you like to take?",
    "response": "1",
    "timestamp": 1747589683294,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "3a769195-c875-4951-90c7-7c2c975b35e4",
    "question": "exit quiz",
    "response": "Exited quiz mode",
    "timestamp": 1747589675462,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "c8c20771-a723-47d1-9369-58233fbb949a",
    "question": "What type of quiz would you like to take?",
    "response": "2",
    "timestamp": 1747589661157,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "b4a57e8a-77db-43a4-953c-7c9f476cefba",
    "question": "Quiz Question 5: Which city is the capital of Spain?",
    "response": "Answer: aa, Feedback: That's not correct. The correct answer is: Madrid",
    "timestamp": 1747589648787,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "920287ac-b699-4462-9397-10027339e05b",
    "question": "Quiz Question 4: Which Spanish dish is made with rice and seafood?",
    "response": "Answer: s, Feedback: That's not correct. The correct answer is: Paella",
    "timestamp": 1747589646777,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "92a0a0d1-3948-47e0-a0c9-68508594d123",
    "question": "Quiz Question 3: On which day do Spaniards traditionally eat twelve grapes at midnight?",
    "response": "Answer: d, Feedback: That's not correct. The correct answer is: New Year's Eve",
    "timestamp": 1747589646004,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "ec8ff60b-735b-43ab-9626-3fe3332109fa",
    "question": "Quiz Question 2: Which Spanish football club has won the most UEFA Champions League titles?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747589644897,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "04984f45-9382-4f12-b3e0-cb3d75924f86",
    "question": "Quiz Question 1: Which Spanish artist painted 'Guernica'?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747589642982,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "e9ceb4d7-c62b-429b-8704-1eaaec63eb81",
    "question": "What type of quiz would you like to take?",
    "response": "4",
    "timestamp": 1747589639076,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "92f14fab-5834-4633-8c3e-4115d3d4f70a",
    "question": "exit quiz",
    "response": "Exited quiz mode",
    "timestamp": 1747589624520,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "8c370c24-1921-485c-a7c9-d322f9d948c9",
    "question": "Quiz Question 1: How do you say 'hello' in Spanish?",
    "response": "Answer: la, Feedback: That's not correct. The correct answer is: hola",
    "timestamp": 1747589615364,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "c76d96c3-0f7a-4ae8-9e06-dcd5cb10df31",
    "question": "What type of quiz would you like to take?",
    "response": "1",
    "timestamp": 1747589605347,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "system",
    "id": "58bad8cb-ee61-45f4-9d5e-14e8a13eda40",
    "question": "settings",
    "response": "Displayed user settings",
    "timestamp": 1747589594704,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "settings",
    "id": "2c66102e-19fb-4c1c-b176-b9df02f51e2e",
    "question": "settings",
    "response": "You can change your settings for:\n- Mother language\n- Target language\nWhat would you like to update?",
    "timestamp": 1747589594700,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "system",
    "id": "5056efaa-9bbd-49a9-b3c1-f480b7813dfb",
    "question": "help",
    "response": "\r\nAvailable commands:\r\n1. chat - Start a conversation\r\n2. quiz - Take a quiz\r\n3. history - View your learning history\r\n4. preferences - Set your language preferences\r\n5. help - Show this help message\r\n6. logout - Log out\r\n7. exit - Exit the application\r\n",
    "timestamp": 1747589579706,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "system",
    "id": "c0ec348c-abb1-4354-b8a4-8ee80efd89e6",
    "question": "settings",
    "response": "Displayed user settings",
    "timestamp": 1747589573826,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "settings",
    "id": "c3f9139e-fb88-4dc5-bd2e-b848f482b761",
    "question": "settings",
    "response": "You can change your settings for:\n- Mother language\n- Target language\nWhat would you like to update?",
    "timestamp": 1747589573822,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "system",
    "id": "55197ce7-c2d9-4c7c-85f6-a639d11de98e",
    "question": "save settings",
    "response": "Attempted to save user settings",
    "timestamp": 1747589569456,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "settings",
    "id": "184a6668-6db2-42c9-9786-9579174611e0",
    "question": "prefrences",
    "response": "You can change your settings for:\n- Mother language\n- Target language\nWhat would you like to update?",
    "timestamp": 1747589553511,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "system",
    "id": "0f87b51b-9c63-4ccb-801f-b8e8c3d9ff58",
    "question": "settings",
    "response": "Displayed user settings",
    "timestamp": 1747589546745,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "settings",
    "id": "37d74976-7ba4-4bdb-aec3-d11eb7f3bf15",
    "question": "settings",
    "response": "You can change your settings for:\n- Mother language\n- Target language\nWhat would you like to update?",
    "timestamp": 1747589546739,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "settings",
    "id": "2577bd82-acaa-4c7a-9d5d-ee72bd077379",
    "question": "set target language spanish",
    "response": "Target language set to Spanish",
    "timestamp": 1747589542794,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "settings",
    "id": "c3b741aa-f09b-4687-afb0-445f2a5d15a0",
    "question": "set mother language english",
    "response": "Mother language set to English",
    "timestamp": 1747589528665,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "system",
    "id": "73c69926-301d-43e1-a040-f75662128e2a",
    "question": "settings",
    "response": "Displayed user settings",
    "timestamp": 1747589509658,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "category": "settings",
    "id": "9f4fe601-12d7-465a-a58f-d73a18a5974b",
    "question": "settings",
    "response": "You can change your settings for:\n- Mother language\n- Target language\nWhat would you like to update?",
    "timestamp": 1747589509611,
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }],
  "quizResults": [{
    "correctAnswers": 0,
    "id": "93f14569-ff1b-4f97-8765-c4f64a037376",
    "questions": [{
      "correctAnswer": "famille",
      "isCorrect": false,
      "question": "What is 'family' in French?",
      "userAnswer": "travail"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "maison",
      "isCorrect": false,
      "question": "What is 'house' in French?",
      "userAnswer": "livre"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "nourriture",
      "isCorrect": false,
      "question": "What is 'food' in French?",
      "userAnswer": "argent"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "livre",
      "isCorrect": false,
      "question": "What is 'book' in French?",
      "userAnswer": "dd"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "chien",
      "isCorrect": false,
      "question": "What is 'dog' in French?",
      "userAnswer": "souris"
    }],
    "quizType": "Vocabulary",
    "score": 0.0,
    "timestamp": 1747599006076,
    "totalQuestions": 5,
    "userAnswers": ["travail", "livre", "argent", "dd", "souris"],
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "correctAnswers": 1,
    "id": "ba274b36-159a-4576-8551-1901dfec9e4a",
    "questions": [{
      "correctAnswer": "nourriture",
      "isCorrect": false,
      "question": "What is 'food' in French?",
      "userAnswer": "eau"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "chien",
      "isCorrect": false,
      "question": "What is 'dog' in French?",
      "userAnswer": "oiseau"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "maison",
      "isCorrect": false,
      "question": "What is 'house' in French?",
      "userAnswer": "s"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "livre",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "What is 'book' in French?",
      "userAnswer": "livre"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "famille",
      "isCorrect": false,
      "question": "What is 'family' in French?",
      "userAnswer": "amis"
    }],
    "quizType": "Vocabulary",
    "score": 1.0,
    "timestamp": 1747598989080,
    "totalQuestions": 5,
    "userAnswers": ["eau", "oiseau", "s", "livre", "amis"],
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "correctAnswers": 0,
    "id": "f7f61874-648d-4a3e-9fd6-0ca8f8501681",
    "questions": [{
      "correctAnswer": "maison",
      "isCorrect": false,
      "question": "What is 'house' in French?",
      "userAnswer": "livre"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "chien",
      "isCorrect": false,
      "question": "What is 'dog' in French?",
      "userAnswer": "as"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "nourriture",
      "isCorrect": false,
      "question": "What is 'food' in French?",
      "userAnswer": "argent"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "livre",
      "isCorrect": false,
      "question": "What is 'book' in French?",
      "userAnswer": "f"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "famille",
      "isCorrect": false,
      "question": "What is 'family' in French?",
      "userAnswer": "f"
    }],
    "quizType": "Vocabulary",
    "score": 0.0,
    "timestamp": 1747598408401,
    "totalQuestions": 5,
    "userAnswers": ["livre", "as", "argent", "f", "f"],
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "correctAnswers": 1,
    "id": "46854201-c90c-407e-9c75-0e0a0bab46da",
    "questions": [{
      "correctAnswer": "maison",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "What is 'house' in French?",
      "userAnswer": "maison"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "chien",
      "isCorrect": false,
      "question": "What is 'dog' in French?",
      "userAnswer": "chat"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "nourriture",
      "isCorrect": false,
      "question": "What is 'food' in French?",
      "userAnswer": "eau"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "livre",
      "isCorrect": false,
      "question": "What is 'book' in French?",
      "userAnswer": "aa"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "famille",
      "isCorrect": false,
      "question": "What is 'family' in French?",
      "userAnswer": "amis"
    }],
    "quizType": "Vocabulary",
    "score": 1.0,
    "timestamp": 1747598396149,
    "totalQuestions": 5,
    "userAnswers": ["maison", "chat", "eau", "aa", "amis"],
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "correctAnswers": 1,
    "id": "ba91106d-b70e-4bb4-9fda-d12be803930d",
    "questions": [{
      "correctAnswer": "maison",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "What is 'house' in French?",
      "userAnswer": "maison"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "chien",
      "isCorrect": false,
      "question": "What is 'dog' in French?",
      "userAnswer": "chat"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "nourriture",
      "isCorrect": false,
      "question": "What is 'food' in French?",
      "userAnswer": "x"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "livre",
      "isCorrect": false,
      "question": "What is 'book' in French?",
      "userAnswer": "xs"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "famille",
      "isCorrect": false,
      "question": "What is 'family' in French?",
      "userAnswer": "amis"
    }],
    "quizType": "Vocabulary",
    "score": 1.0,
    "timestamp": 1747598276514,
    "totalQuestions": 5,
    "userAnswers": ["maison", "chat", "x", "xs", "amis"],
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "correctAnswers": 2,
    "id": "9f447ca7-c498-48fc-87e3-a1b9d04996be",
    "questions": [{
      "correctAnswer": "maison",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "What is 'house' in French?",
      "userAnswer": "maison"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "chien",
      "isCorrect": false,
      "question": "What is 'dog' in French?",
      "userAnswer": "chat"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "nourriture",
      "isCorrect": false,
      "question": "What is 'food' in French?",
      "userAnswer": "aa"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "livre",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "What is 'book' in French?",
      "userAnswer": "livre"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "famille",
      "isCorrect": false,
      "question": "What is 'family' in French?",
      "userAnswer": "aa"
    }],
    "quizType": "Vocabulary",
    "score": 2.0,
    "timestamp": 1747598239171,
    "totalQuestions": 5,
    "userAnswers": ["maison", "chat", "aa", "livre", "aa"],
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "correctAnswers": 1,
    "id": "1fcff635-9081-4f90-a8f2-3d9966fe3d25",
    "questions": [{
      "correctAnswer": "spreche",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Which is the correct conjugation of 'sprechen' for 'ich'?",
      "userAnswer": "spreche"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "das",
      "isCorrect": false,
      "question": "Which article matches with 'Haus'?",
      "userAnswer": "der"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "die Bücher",
      "isCorrect": false,
      "question": "What is the plural form of 'das Buch'?",
      "userAnswer": "das bücher"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "lesen",
      "isCorrect": false,
      "question": "Which word is a verb?",
      "userAnswer": "schön"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Ich esse einen Apfel",
      "isCorrect": false,
      "question": "Select the correct sentence:",
      "userAnswer": "ich esse ein apfel"
    }],
    "quizType": "Grammar",
    "score": 1.0,
    "timestamp": 1747596990031,
    "totalQuestions": 5,
    "userAnswers": ["spreche", "der", "das bücher", "schön", "ich esse ein apfel"],
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "correctAnswers": 4,
    "id": "7477d220-a19c-4d47-b56f-af930f852a01",
    "questions": [{
      "correctAnswer": "spreche",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Which is the correct conjugation of 'sprechen' for 'ich'?",
      "userAnswer": "spreche"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "das",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Which article matches with 'Haus'?",
      "userAnswer": "das"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "die Bücher",
      "isCorrect": false,
      "question": "What is the plural form of 'das Buch'?",
      "userAnswer": "der bücher"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "lesen",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Which word is a verb?",
      "userAnswer": "lesen"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Ich esse einen Apfel",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Select the correct sentence:",
      "userAnswer": "Ich esse einen Apfel"
    }],
    "quizType": "Grammar",
    "score": 4.0,
    "timestamp": 1747596966622,
    "totalQuestions": 5,
    "userAnswers": ["spreche", "das", "der bücher", "lesen", "Ich esse einen Apfel"],
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "correctAnswers": 2,
    "id": "354bd5fe-1684-4d09-a4e3-887a2631dc37",
    "questions": [{
      "correctAnswer": "hablo",
      "isCorrect": false,
      "question": "Which is the correct conjugation of 'hablar' for 'yo'?",
      "userAnswer": "habla"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "la",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Which article matches with 'casa'?",
      "userAnswer": "la"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "los libros",
      "isCorrect": false,
      "question": "What is the plural form of 'el libro'?",
      "userAnswer": "los libro"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "correr",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Which word is a verb?",
      "userAnswer": "correr"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Tú comes manzanas",
      "isCorrect": false,
      "question": "Select the correct sentence:",
      "userAnswer": "yo come manzanas"
    }],
    "quizType": "Grammar",
    "score": 2.0,
    "timestamp": 1747591057840,
    "totalQuestions": 5,
    "userAnswers": ["habla", "la", "los libro", "correr", "yo come manzanas"],
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "correctAnswers": 3,
    "id": "10c799dd-0aef-4842-91a0-16381567154e",
    "questions": [{
      "correctAnswer": "casa",
      "isCorrect": false,
      "question": "What is 'house' in Spanish?",
      "userAnswer": ""
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "perro",
      "isCorrect": false,
      "question": "What is 'dog' in Spanish?",
      "userAnswer": ""
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "comida",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "What is 'food' in Spanish?",
      "userAnswer": "comida"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "libro",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "What is 'book' in Spanish?",
      "userAnswer": "libro"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "familia",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "What is 'family' in Spanish?",
      "userAnswer": "familia"
    }],
    "quizType": "Vocabulary",
    "score": 3.0,
    "timestamp": 1747590983688,
    "totalQuestions": 5,
    "userAnswers": ["", "", "comida", "libro", "familia"],
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }, {
    "correctAnswers": 2,
    "id": "4f16cc88-fde4-44f3-854d-adf11b97ad3e",
    "questions": [{
      "correctAnswer": "Pablo Picasso",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Which Spanish artist painted 'Guernica'?",
      "userAnswer": "Pablo Picasso"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Real Madrid",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Which Spanish football club has won the most UEFA Champions League titles?",
      "userAnswer": "Real Madrid"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "New Year's Eve",
      "isCorrect": false,
      "question": "On which day do Spaniards traditionally eat twelve grapes at midnight?",
      "userAnswer": "d"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Paella",
      "isCorrect": false,
      "question": "Which Spanish dish is made with rice and seafood?",
      "userAnswer": "s"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Madrid",
      "isCorrect": false,
      "question": "Which city is the capital of Spain?",
      "userAnswer": "aa"
    }],
    "quizType": "MCQ",
    "score": 2.0,
    "timestamp": 1747589648796,
    "totalQuestions": 5,
    "userAnswers": ["Pablo Picasso", "Real Madrid", "d", "s", "aa"],
    "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27"
  }],
  "userId": "a7f08bed-21d0-4b64-8c03-e10ba39a1e27",
  "username": "yassin"
}, {
  "email": "yaa",
  "interactions": [{
    "category": "thanks",
    "id": "b414e0a3-9efc-4aca-8ce9-23fdeacf877b",
    "question": "set difficulty level hard",
    "response": "You can change your settings for:\n- Mother language\n- Target language\n- Difficulty level\nWhat would you like to update?",
    "timestamp": 1747582314169,
    "userId": "1804cb5b-d3d2-4c2c-a3f2-6ff3c2b596c6"
  }, {
    "category": "thanks",
    "id": "1bdb9737-63c7-4e66-805a-95716c03722e",
    "question": "set difficulty hard",
    "response": "You can change your settings for:\n- Mother language\n- Target language\n- Difficulty level\nWhat would you like to update?",
    "timestamp": 1747582300943,
    "userId": "1804cb5b-d3d2-4c2c-a3f2-6ff3c2b596c6"
  }, {
    "category": "settings",
    "id": "ee2e9d87-a800-485e-8464-d653f835c683",
    "question": "set target language spanish",
    "response": "Target language set to Spanish",
    "timestamp": 1747582293965,
    "userId": "1804cb5b-d3d2-4c2c-a3f2-6ff3c2b596c6"
  }, {
    "category": "settings",
    "id": "e8b805b8-7add-48ef-ad1a-543eb4c138fc",
    "question": "set mother language english",
    "response": "Mother language set to English",
    "timestamp": 1747582284112,
    "userId": "1804cb5b-d3d2-4c2c-a3f2-6ff3c2b596c6"
  }, {
    "category": "system",
    "id": "9accc090-6e75-4665-9eb3-90de840fcdf4",
    "question": "settings",
    "response": "Displayed user settings",
    "timestamp": 1747582271554,
    "userId": "1804cb5b-d3d2-4c2c-a3f2-6ff3c2b596c6"
  }],
  "quizResults": [],
  "userId": "1804cb5b-d3d2-4c2c-a3f2-6ff3c2b596c6",
  "username": "yaa"
}, {
  "email": "ramez",
  "interactions": [{
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "2d41dcee-31b9-49ef-afc8-c801bc2e4760",
    "question": "Quiz Question 5: Which Spanish football club has won the most UEFA Champions League titles?",
    "response": "Answer: , Feedback: You didn't provide an answer. The correct answer is: Real Madrid",
    "timestamp": 1746900489362,
    "userId": "083fa50b-dc29-4076-bc73-53b325339d62"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "ccd9b9c7-326b-4606-8115-6e1f896d6c89",
    "question": "Quiz Question 4: On which day do Spaniards traditionally eat twelve grapes at midnight?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1746900488990,
    "userId": "083fa50b-dc29-4076-bc73-53b325339d62"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "52e3dd65-af09-46d6-b6e8-9faa1a37f890",
    "question": "Quiz Question 3: Which city is the capital of Spain?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1746900488402,
    "userId": "083fa50b-dc29-4076-bc73-53b325339d62"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "fe6ee49b-4f80-400f-a34f-04f5c2c7aaa4",
    "question": "Quiz Question 2: Which Spanish dish is made with rice and seafood?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1746900488002,
    "userId": "083fa50b-dc29-4076-bc73-53b325339d62"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "3b1720bf-34ab-4945-8158-ca48a8fc0eed",
    "question": "Quiz Question 1: Which Spanish artist painted 'Guernica'?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1746900487630,
    "userId": "083fa50b-dc29-4076-bc73-53b325339d62"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "8a101fa8-1ca7-41b8-a973-df3de656ec84",
    "question": "quiz",
    "response": "Started a new quiz session",
    "timestamp": 1746900486242,
    "userId": "083fa50b-dc29-4076-bc73-53b325339d62"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "ff986b31-7931-49d0-bec3-34314fa1440c",
    "question": "What type of quiz would you like to take?",
    "response": "mcq",
    "timestamp": 1746900486237,
    "userId": "083fa50b-dc29-4076-bc73-53b325339d62"
  }, {
    "category": "unknown",
    "id": "b7c64f3a-f82d-4632-acfb-d2d2cfa22075",
    "question": "mcq",
    "response": "I'm not sure I understand. Try asking about quizzes, changing settings, or asking a specific language question.",
    "timestamp": 1746900482800,
    "userId": "083fa50b-dc29-4076-bc73-53b325339d62"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "1db68540-be8e-4fb3-87a9-166e59b094da",
    "question": "Quiz Question 5: Which Spanish football club has won the most UEFA Champions League titles?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1746900478407,
    "userId": "083fa50b-dc29-4076-bc73-53b325339d62"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "310ca165-c4fe-4b2c-bf05-e71237618c5a",
    "question": "Quiz Question 4: Which Spanish artist painted 'Guernica'?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1746900477841,
    "userId": "083fa50b-dc29-4076-bc73-53b325339d62"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "bf60af64-5b53-48d7-913e-cc8cf11514a9",
    "question": "Quiz Question 3: Which city is the capital of Spain?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1746900477395,
    "userId": "083fa50b-dc29-4076-bc73-53b325339d62"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "c21fde75-c3e4-4a0b-ae99-75bacd5236b7",
    "question": "Quiz Question 2: Which Spanish dish is made with rice and seafood?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1746900476972,
    "userId": "083fa50b-dc29-4076-bc73-53b325339d62"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "aecb3d0d-7028-4391-9db5-b59fec6b9b92",
    "question": "Quiz Question 1: On which day do Spaniards traditionally eat twelve grapes at midnight?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1746900476651,
    "userId": "083fa50b-dc29-4076-bc73-53b325339d62"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "2aac629f-d088-4e83-ab26-adbecf1dc1ae",
    "question": "quiz",
    "response": "Started a new quiz session",
    "timestamp": 1746900476052,
    "userId": "083fa50b-dc29-4076-bc73-53b325339d62"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "7175abf7-6707-4ff8-89be-00647eef2a56",
    "question": "What type of quiz would you like to take?",
    "response": "mcq",
    "timestamp": 1746900476047,
    "userId": "083fa50b-dc29-4076-bc73-53b325339d62"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "cab45f5e-8c50-4f59-ac9e-f316bda7cde2",
    "question": "Quiz Question 5: Which Spanish city is famous for the 'Running of the Bulls'?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1746900466011,
    "userId": "083fa50b-dc29-4076-bc73-53b325339d62"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "ff4aa1f3-9afb-4c15-a0ef-5359d6f4fc3c",
    "question": "Quiz Question 4: Which is the longest river in Spain?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1746900465547,
    "userId": "083fa50b-dc29-4076-bc73-53b325339d62"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "7449964f-1c80-44d9-b723-630f447d6a71",
    "question": "Quiz Question 3: Which animal is featured on the Spanish coat of arms?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1746900465162,
    "userId": "083fa50b-dc29-4076-bc73-53b325339d62"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "586d9634-2890-438e-b7ca-e77eed2073bb",
    "question": "Quiz Question 2: Which of these Spanish islands is located in the Mediterranean Sea?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1746900464829,
    "userId": "083fa50b-dc29-4076-bc73-53b325339d62"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "fb03cad2-f130-4e13-a394-4284ca4ebff0",
    "question": "Quiz Question 1: Which mountain range runs along the border between Spain and France?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1746900464499,
    "userId": "083fa50b-dc29-4076-bc73-53b325339d62"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "4241cfab-4c42-4b3a-b091-8e9d293ba3cc",
    "question": "quiz",
    "response": "Started a new quiz session",
    "timestamp": 1746900463283,
    "userId": "083fa50b-dc29-4076-bc73-53b325339d62"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "60c4cf00-7615-4a94-b973-443659059972",
    "question": "What type of quiz would you like to take?",
    "response": "mcq",
    "timestamp": 1746900463219,
    "userId": "083fa50b-dc29-4076-bc73-53b325339d62"
  }, {
    "category": "unknown",
    "id": "93694544-7ccf-4c0d-b9dc-caa4a757bfe1",
    "question": "sss",
    "response": "I'm not sure I understand. Try asking about quizzes, changing settings, or asking a specific language question.",
    "timestamp": 1746888774448,
    "userId": "083fa50b-dc29-4076-bc73-53b325339d62"
  }, {
    "category": "system",
    "id": "83444530-eecc-4427-9c6b-0ab7e5ca1021",
    "question": "help",
    "response": "\r\nAvailable commands:\r\n1. chat - Start a conversation\r\n2. quiz - Take a quiz\r\n3. history - View your learning history\r\n4. preferences - Set your language preferences\r\n5. help - Show this help message\r\n6. logout - Log out\r\n7. exit - Exit the application\r\n",
    "timestamp": 1746888772357,
    "userId": "083fa50b-dc29-4076-bc73-53b325339d62"
  }, {
    "category": "system",
    "id": "29662a70-a516-481c-aeb1-930ef7b06bc6",
    "question": "help",
    "response": "\r\nAvailable commands:\r\n1. chat - Start a conversation\r\n2. quiz - Take a quiz\r\n3. history - View your learning history\r\n4. preferences - Set your language preferences\r\n5. help - Show this help message\r\n6. logout - Log out\r\n7. exit - Exit the application\r\n",
    "timestamp": 1746888638046,
    "userId": "083fa50b-dc29-4076-bc73-53b325339d62"
  }],
  "quizResults": [{
    "correctAnswers": 4,
    "id": "0d373864-df04-4280-8e3b-ff97e4f7b735",
    "questions": [{
      "correctAnswer": "Pablo Picasso",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Which Spanish artist painted 'Guernica'?",
      "userAnswer": "Pablo Picasso"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Paella",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Which Spanish dish is made with rice and seafood?",
      "userAnswer": "Paella"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Madrid",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Which city is the capital of Spain?",
      "userAnswer": "Madrid"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "New Year's Eve",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "On which day do Spaniards traditionally eat twelve grapes at midnight?",
      "userAnswer": "New Year's Eve"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Real Madrid",
      "isCorrect": false,
      "question": "Which Spanish football club has won the most UEFA Champions League titles?",
      "userAnswer": ""
    }],
    "quizType": "MCQ",
    "score": 4.0,
    "timestamp": 1746900489366,
    "totalQuestions": 5,
    "userAnswers": ["Pablo Picasso", "Paella", "Madrid", "New Year's Eve", ""],
    "userId": "083fa50b-dc29-4076-bc73-53b325339d62"
  }, {
    "correctAnswers": 5,
    "id": "fafe6a1c-f530-4f95-9e6e-b21df7e336ba",
    "questions": [{
      "correctAnswer": "New Year's Eve",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "On which day do Spaniards traditionally eat twelve grapes at midnight?",
      "userAnswer": "New Year's Eve"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Paella",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Which Spanish dish is made with rice and seafood?",
      "userAnswer": "Paella"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Madrid",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Which city is the capital of Spain?",
      "userAnswer": "Madrid"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Pablo Picasso",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Which Spanish artist painted 'Guernica'?",
      "userAnswer": "Pablo Picasso"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Real Madrid",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Which Spanish football club has won the most UEFA Champions League titles?",
      "userAnswer": "Real Madrid"
    }],
    "quizType": "MCQ",
    "score": 5.0,
    "timestamp": 1746900478411,
    "totalQuestions": 5,
    "userAnswers": ["New Year's Eve", "Paella", "Madrid", "Pablo Picasso", "Real Madrid"],
    "userId": "083fa50b-dc29-4076-bc73-53b325339d62"
  }, {
    "correctAnswers": 5,
    "id": "65f7eb6e-84e7-411d-9ce5-2acda698279b",
    "questions": [{
      "correctAnswer": "Pyrenees",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Which mountain range runs along the border between Spain and France?",
      "userAnswer": "Pyrenees"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Mallorca",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Which of these Spanish islands is located in the Mediterranean Sea?",
      "userAnswer": "Mallorca"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Eagle",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Which animal is featured on the Spanish coat of arms?",
      "userAnswer": "Eagle"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Ebro",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Which is the longest river in Spain?",
      "userAnswer": "Ebro"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Pamplona",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Which Spanish city is famous for the 'Running of the Bulls'?",
      "userAnswer": "Pamplona"
    }],
    "quizType": "MCQ",
    "score": 5.0,
    "timestamp": 1746900466019,
    "totalQuestions": 5,
    "userAnswers": ["Pyrenees", "Mallorca", "Eagle", "Ebro", "Pamplona"],
    "userId": "083fa50b-dc29-4076-bc73-53b325339d62"
  }, {
    "correctAnswers": 1,
    "id": "9685ae91-fd6c-4f38-81e4-e1c18d977847",
    "questions": [{
      "correctAnswer": "hablo",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "What is the correct present tense conjugation for 'hablar' (yo)?",
      "userAnswer": "hablo"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "comes",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "What is the correct present tense conjugation for 'comer' (tú)?",
      "userAnswer": "comes"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "van",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "What is the correct present tense for 'ir' (ellos)?",
      "userAnswer": "van"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "somos",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "What is the correct present tense for 'ser' (nosotros)?",
      "userAnswer": "somos"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "vive",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "What is the correct present tense conjugation for 'vivir' (él)?",
      "userAnswer": "vive"
    }],
    "quizType": "Grammar",
    "score": 5.0,
    "timestamp": 1746888856146,
    "totalQuestions": 5,
    "userAnswers": ["hablo", "comes", "van", "somos", "vive"],
    "userId": "083fa50b-dc29-4076-bc73-53b325339d62"
  }, {
    "correctAnswers": 1,
    "id": "655f14b0-bc73-47fe-bd51-a797dd5d5cd7",
    "questions": [{
      "correctAnswer": "Mallorca",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Which of these Spanish islands is located in the Mediterranean Sea?",
      "userAnswer": "Mallorca"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Pyrenees",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Which mountain range runs along the border between Spain and France?",
      "userAnswer": "Pyrenees"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Eagle",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Which animal is featured on the Spanish coat of arms?",
      "userAnswer": "Eagle"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Pamplona",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Which Spanish city is famous for the 'Running of the Bulls'?",
      "userAnswer": "Pamplona"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Ebro",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Which is the longest river in Spain?",
      "userAnswer": "Ebro"
    }],
    "quizType": "MCQ",
    "score": 5.0,
    "timestamp": 1746888827725,
    "totalQuestions": 5,
    "userAnswers": ["Mallorca", "Pyrenees", "Eagle", "Pamplona", "Ebro"],
    "userId": "083fa50b-dc29-4076-bc73-53b325339d62"
  }],
  "userId": "083fa50b-dc29-4076-bc73-53b325339d62",
  "username": "mazen"
}, {
  "email": "Yassin.Hany@yahos",
  "interactions": [{
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "62aaa0ea-d5d4-4695-9332-c1186a79e0d4",
    "question": "Quiz Question 5: What is 'house' in Spanish?",
    "response": "Answer: d, Feedback: That's not correct. The correct answer is: casa",
    "timestamp": 1747425158344,
    "userId": "4260a945-81ab-4c93-bf6e-6571b986666b"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "3335a044-d266-402a-bd11-144f5a8728bd",
    "question": "Quiz Question 4: What is 'bed' in Spanish?",
    "response": "Answer: c, Feedback: That's not correct. The correct answer is: cama",
    "timestamp": 1747425157082,
    "userId": "4260a945-81ab-4c93-bf6e-6571b986666b"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "cd73bfd8-910a-4abd-81f0-65892d49a762",
    "question": "Quiz Question 3: What is 'cshair' in Spanish?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747425155793,
    "userId": "4260a945-81ab-4c93-bf6e-6571b986666b"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "16d5fa04-21cf-413e-8e89-13113e67bbbe",
    "question": "Quiz Question 2: What is 'door' in Spanish?",
    "response": "Answer: b, Feedback: That's not correct. The correct answer is: puerta",
    "timestamp": 1747425153652,
    "userId": "4260a945-81ab-4c93-bf6e-6571b986666b"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "50b17757-398e-4cf4-a843-7a73765112a2",
    "question": "Quiz Question 1: What is 'table' in Spanish?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747425151818,
    "userId": "4260a945-81ab-4c93-bf6e-6571b986666b"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "95b0d13f-0c93-488f-9de7-82c41693e684",
    "question": "What type of quiz would you like to take?",
    "response": "vocabulary",
    "timestamp": 1747425149645,
    "userId": "4260a945-81ab-4c93-bf6e-6571b986666b"
  }, {
    "category": "system",
    "id": "f8af57f4-06a7-4450-9d66-ff3b858615e6",
    "question": "settings",
    "response": "Displayed user settings",
    "timestamp": 1747425132054,
    "userId": "4260a945-81ab-4c93-bf6e-6571b986666b"
  }, {
    "category": "thanks",
    "id": "a03434dd-aeae-4a5c-a289-8c6c4563858c",
    "question": "set difficulty easy",
    "response": "You can change your settings for:\n- Mother language\n- Target language\n- Difficulty level\nWhat would you like to update?",
    "timestamp": 1747425128878,
    "userId": "4260a945-81ab-4c93-bf6e-6571b986666b"
  }, {
    "category": "system",
    "id": "fe67de0e-2163-448c-bf0a-050a3aea0a8d",
    "question": "settings",
    "response": "Displayed user settings",
    "timestamp": 1747425101621,
    "userId": "4260a945-81ab-4c93-bf6e-6571b986666b"
  }, {
    "category": "system",
    "id": "f0462229-4692-486d-be42-946bbc9a4122",
    "question": "help",
    "response": "\r\nAvailable commands:\r\n1. chat - Start a conversation\r\n2. quiz - Take a quiz\r\n3. history - View your learning history\r\n4. preferences - Set your language preferences\r\n5. help - Show this help message\r\n6. logout - Log out\r\n7. exit - Exit the application\r\n",
    "timestamp": 1747425092749,
    "userId": "4260a945-81ab-4c93-bf6e-6571b986666b"
  }],
  "quizResults": [{
    "correctAnswers": 2,
    "id": "b13d3580-b1e6-41ea-aaac-c9863ccc44f3",
    "questions": [{
      "correctAnswer": "mesa",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "What is 'table' in Spanish?",
      "userAnswer": "mesa"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "puerta",
      "isCorrect": false,
      "question": "What is 'door' in Spanish?",
      "userAnswer": "ventana"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "silla",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "What is 'cshair' in Spanish?",
      "userAnswer": "silla"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "cama",
      "isCorrect": false,
      "question": "What is 'bed' in Spanish?",
      "userAnswer": "mesa"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "casa",
      "isCorrect": false,
      "question": "What is 'house' in Spanish?",
      "userAnswer": "oficina"
    }],
    "quizType": "Vocabulary",
    "score": 2.0,
    "timestamp": 1747425158357,
    "totalQuestions": 5,
    "userAnswers": ["mesa", "ventana", "silla", "mesa", "oficina"],
    "userId": "4260a945-81ab-4c93-bf6e-6571b986666b"
  }],
  "userId": "4260a945-81ab-4c93-bf6e-6571b986666b",
  "username": "Yassin"
}, {
  "email": "yasi",
  "interactions": [{
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "a3b1ba33-3b49-4464-b53f-f13016327bc8",
    "question": "What type of quiz would you like to take?",
    "response": "3",
    "timestamp": 1747596627555,
    "userId": "6402698b-f199-425c-bc99-02d24c54ee9e"
  }, {
    "category": "settings",
    "id": "808681ee-52bd-4551-aa6c-61fd2e2dad86",
    "question": "set target language spanish",
    "response": "Target language set to Spanish",
    "timestamp": 1747596624679,
    "userId": "6402698b-f199-425c-bc99-02d24c54ee9e"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "18fc5b1f-e285-4b86-b92b-ff4f818d29d5",
    "question": "Quiz Question 5: Translate: 'She works at a hospital'",
    "response": "Answer: b, Feedback: That's not correct. The correct answer is: Ella trabaja en un hospital",
    "timestamp": 1747596580525,
    "userId": "6402698b-f199-425c-bc99-02d24c54ee9e"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "4b39fb87-8536-471f-af56-442e020964cc",
    "question": "Quiz Question 4: Translate: 'I like to travel'",
    "response": "Answer: b, Feedback: That's not correct. The correct answer is: Me gusta viajar",
    "timestamp": 1747596579829,
    "userId": "6402698b-f199-425c-bc99-02d24c54ee9e"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "1f8625ab-f86a-4591-96e6-9e3a32b7d17d",
    "question": "Quiz Question 3: Translate: 'My name is John'",
    "response": "Answer: b, Feedback: That's not correct. The correct answer is: Me llamo John",
    "timestamp": 1747596579396,
    "userId": "6402698b-f199-425c-bc99-02d24c54ee9e"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "16d808ac-8602-46cf-9bad-74e8e45bcae6",
    "question": "Quiz Question 2: Translate: 'Where is the bathroom?'",
    "response": "Answer: , Feedback: That's not correct. The correct answer is: ¿Dónde está el baño?",
    "timestamp": 1747596578005,
    "userId": "6402698b-f199-425c-bc99-02d24c54ee9e"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "6016f7a7-17fd-4c69-8398-cda8c0329e0f",
    "question": "Quiz Question 1: Translate: 'I eat breakfast every day'",
    "response": "Answer: , Feedback: That's not correct. The correct answer is: Yo como el desayuno todos los días",
    "timestamp": 1747596577526,
    "userId": "6402698b-f199-425c-bc99-02d24c54ee9e"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "10ca4514-2118-440e-aa45-d4a809dab6c3",
    "question": "What type of quiz would you like to take?",
    "response": "3",
    "timestamp": 1747596575039,
    "userId": "6402698b-f199-425c-bc99-02d24c54ee9e"
  }, {
    "category": "system",
    "id": "05876903-fc4d-4f12-be8f-1d1132fe4afd",
    "question": "save settings",
    "response": "Displayed user settings",
    "timestamp": 1747596522461,
    "userId": "6402698b-f199-425c-bc99-02d24c54ee9e"
  }, {
    "category": "settings",
    "id": "15cce479-c81a-4dcf-8ec8-5eabd93657ef",
    "question": "settings",
    "response": "You can change your settings for:\n- Mother language\n- Target language\nWhat would you like to update?",
    "timestamp": 1747596522457,
    "userId": "6402698b-f199-425c-bc99-02d24c54ee9e"
  }, {
    "category": "system",
    "id": "e41abb88-116e-44d2-9dcb-8c858a7bca7e",
    "question": "save settings",
    "response": "Displayed user settings",
    "timestamp": 1747596487030,
    "userId": "6402698b-f199-425c-bc99-02d24c54ee9e"
  }, {
    "category": "settings",
    "id": "c725867a-18a5-4352-88c8-d81b674f6347",
    "question": "settings",
    "response": "You can change your settings for:\n- Mother language\n- Target language\nWhat would you like to update?",
    "timestamp": 1747596487023,
    "userId": "6402698b-f199-425c-bc99-02d24c54ee9e"
  }, {
    "category": "settings",
    "id": "3786b1c7-d72b-456c-8e43-f33597eb7e4c",
    "question": "set target language spanish",
    "response": "Target language set to Spanish",
    "timestamp": 1747596481986,
    "userId": "6402698b-f199-425c-bc99-02d24c54ee9e"
  }, {
    "category": "settings",
    "id": "77d8c8d2-1078-4bbd-8833-3e1e13222778",
    "question": "set mother language english",
    "response": "Mother language set to English",
    "timestamp": 1747596471970,
    "userId": "6402698b-f199-425c-bc99-02d24c54ee9e"
  }, {
    "category": "system",
    "id": "dd1dc3cb-c331-49a4-a218-c1c8dd24a44d",
    "question": "settings",
    "response": "Displayed user settings",
    "timestamp": 1747596457613,
    "userId": "6402698b-f199-425c-bc99-02d24c54ee9e"
  }, {
    "category": "settings",
    "id": "a5bf7e55-9df7-4c03-9920-d185255e6408",
    "question": "settings",
    "response": "You can change your settings for:\n- Mother language\n- Target language\nWhat would you like to update?",
    "timestamp": 1747596457605,
    "userId": "6402698b-f199-425c-bc99-02d24c54ee9e"
  }, {
    "category": "unknown",
    "id": "e9427dc5-02c5-4f5f-886f-a45289677afa",
    "question": "hello",
    "response": "Hello, hh! I'm your Language Learning Bot. Would you like to practice vocabulary, grammar, or start a quiz?",
    "timestamp": 1747596454423,
    "userId": "6402698b-f199-425c-bc99-02d24c54ee9e"
  }, {
    "category": "language_question",
    "id": "81deaa2c-51cf-400b-8894-6e551c977d6b",
    "question": "hi",
    "response": "Hello, hh! I'm your Language Learning Bot. Would you like to practice vocabulary, grammar, or start a quiz?",
    "timestamp": 1747596451875,
    "userId": "6402698b-f199-425c-bc99-02d24c54ee9e"
  }],
  "quizResults": [{
    "correctAnswers": 0,
    "id": "f14d3512-4ae0-42c9-bc71-2961ae8e5664",
    "questions": [{
      "correctAnswer": "Yo como el desayuno todos los días",
      "isCorrect": false,
      "question": "Translate: 'I eat breakfast every day'",
      "userAnswer": ""
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "¿Dónde está el baño?",
      "isCorrect": false,
      "question": "Translate: 'Where is the bathroom?'",
      "userAnswer": ""
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Me llamo John",
      "isCorrect": false,
      "question": "Translate: 'My name is John'",
      "userAnswer": "yo llamo john"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Me gusta viajar",
      "isCorrect": false,
      "question": "Translate: 'I like to travel'",
      "userAnswer": "yo gusto viajar"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Ella trabaja en un hospital",
      "isCorrect": false,
      "question": "Translate: 'She works at a hospital'",
      "userAnswer": "ella trabajar en un hospital"
    }],
    "quizType": "Translation",
    "score": 0.0,
    "timestamp": 1747596580535,
    "totalQuestions": 5,
    "userAnswers": ["", "", "yo llamo john", "yo gusto viajar", "ella trabajar en un hospital"],
    "userId": "6402698b-f199-425c-bc99-02d24c54ee9e"
  }],
  "userId": "6402698b-f199-425c-bc99-02d24c54ee9e",
  "username": "hh"
}, {
  "email": "mazen",
  "interactions": [{
    "category": "settings",
    "id": "4a096b7f-0414-445d-b280-7ab4a546d2e2",
    "question": "dir settings",
    "response": "You can change your settings for:\n- Mother language\n- Target language\n- Difficulty level\nWhat would you like to update?",
    "timestamp": 1747583943740,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "unknown",
    "id": "c7f943d6-7f6b-4006-8a0f-f3d7919cce8a",
    "question": "q",
    "response": "I'm not sure I understand. Try asking about quizzes, changing settings.",
    "timestamp": 1747583934408,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "thanks",
    "id": "c4d3c574-b9e0-4177-af30-43b5e0c4b846",
    "question": "set difficulty hard",
    "response": "You can change your settings for:\n- Mother language\n- Target language\n- Difficulty level\nWhat would you like to update?",
    "timestamp": 1747583914307,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "thanks",
    "id": "11c0426c-def7-4e06-9472-2594e7221d8e",
    "question": "set difficulty hard",
    "response": "You can change your settings for:\n- Mother language\n- Target language\n- Difficulty level\nWhat would you like to update?",
    "timestamp": 1747581841371,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "system",
    "id": "5987797b-8c59-4bc1-9349-373132536180",
    "question": "settings",
    "response": "Displayed user settings",
    "timestamp": 1747581592917,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "thanks",
    "id": "50dff41b-0c11-44f1-90ee-8904fe410daa",
    "question": "set difficulty hard",
    "response": "You can change your settings for:\n- Mother language\n- Target language\n- Difficulty level\nWhat would you like to update?",
    "timestamp": 1747581584046,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "system",
    "id": "1722d404-3a02-44cd-8ec8-32b3163849d8",
    "question": "settings",
    "response": "Displayed user settings",
    "timestamp": 1747581546500,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "thanks",
    "id": "28794068-175e-41e7-91ce-d132d059cc69",
    "question": "set difficulty hard",
    "response": "You can change your settings for:\n- Mother language\n- Target language\n- Difficulty level\nWhat would you like to update?",
    "timestamp": 1747581380090,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "system",
    "id": "d2c532af-57cb-47c4-b71a-f7f754ece356",
    "question": "settings",
    "response": "Displayed user settings",
    "timestamp": 1747581349855,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "system",
    "id": "94d166cb-b9ff-40cd-ad15-7490559dcfd6",
    "question": "settings",
    "response": "Displayed user settings",
    "timestamp": 1747581325812,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "unknown",
    "id": "74d7c1f1-4ce7-4206-9fc8-6621a157f84f",
    "question": "setting",
    "response": "I'm not sure I understand. Try asking about quizzes, changing settings.",
    "timestamp": 1747581321504,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "thanks",
    "id": "7a872ece-c8ae-4fa0-a39a-895afa23f544",
    "question": "change difficulty level hard",
    "response": "You can change your settings for:\n- Mother language\n- Target language\n- Difficulty level\nWhat would you like to update?",
    "timestamp": 1747415742959,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "settings",
    "id": "c91d7b33-79da-4465-9176-537bb307fe2f",
    "question": "set difficult easy",
    "response": "You can change your settings for:\n- Mother language\n- Target language\n- Difficulty level\nWhat would you like to update?",
    "timestamp": 1747415728702,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "unknown",
    "id": "6dc29a3c-ffe2-48a0-b55b-6f5233c7f0bd",
    "question": "hello",
    "response": "Hello, mazen! I'm your Language Learning Bot. Would you like to practice vocabulary, grammar, or start a quiz?",
    "timestamp": 1747415701823,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "language_question",
    "id": "20443fb0-6f93-4942-be00-99e323146c53",
    "question": "hi",
    "response": "Hello, mazen! I'm your Language Learning Bot. Would you like to practice vocabulary, grammar, or start a quiz?",
    "timestamp": 1747415699518,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "thanks",
    "id": "b191b1f9-d9bb-4128-822e-1d7590db23b1",
    "question": "set difficulty medium",
    "response": "You can change your settings for:\n- Mother language\n- Target language\n- Difficulty level\nWhat would you like to update?",
    "timestamp": 1747415575891,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "thanks",
    "id": "419b81ff-83a4-4907-8b5c-73077f5ecc09",
    "question": "change difficulty easy",
    "response": "You can change your settings for:\n- Mother language\n- Target language\n- Difficulty level\nWhat would you like to update?",
    "timestamp": 1747415564678,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "thanks",
    "id": "58f00e50-f908-4b2c-9dca-c48f7109b43f",
    "question": "set difficulty hard",
    "response": "You can change your settings for:\n- Mother language\n- Target language\n- Difficulty level\nWhat would you like to update?",
    "timestamp": 1747415552903,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "thanks",
    "id": "3e62a0aa-9931-4f8e-aecc-96d397eea725",
    "question": "set difficulty hard",
    "response": "You can change your settings for:\n- Mother language\n- Target language\n- Difficulty level\nWhat would you like to update?",
    "timestamp": 1747415422491,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "thanks",
    "id": "f9ce6ed4-5050-4edd-a31c-c169cebb48f0",
    "question": "set difficulty hrd",
    "response": "You can change your settings for:\n- Mother language\n- Target language\n- Difficulty level\nWhat would you like to update?",
    "timestamp": 1747415411873,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "system",
    "id": "9209af3e-03b6-4506-9b14-e7aeab170e1a",
    "question": "settings",
    "response": "Displayed user settings",
    "timestamp": 1747415400282,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "thanks",
    "id": "42d9c954-582e-4109-9263-4d35d8929f12",
    "question": "set difficulty level hard",
    "response": "You can change your settings for:\n- Mother language\n- Target language\n- Difficulty level\nWhat would you like to update?",
    "timestamp": 1747415384661,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "thanks",
    "id": "03d0eb4a-bbf7-48df-9396-56edbf085d38",
    "question": "set difficulty level medium",
    "response": "You can change your settings for:\n- Mother language\n- Target language\n- Difficulty level\nWhat would you like to update?",
    "timestamp": 1747415214577,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "thanks",
    "id": "96be43dc-b7d7-41da-8747-c8001114ef17",
    "question": "change difficulty level hard",
    "response": "You can change your settings for:\n- Mother language\n- Target language\n- Difficulty level\nWhat would you like to update?",
    "timestamp": 1747415202141,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "thanks",
    "id": "af145493-c013-48bc-b93e-969c2fb98e10",
    "question": "set difficulty level easy",
    "response": "You can change your settings for:\n- Mother language\n- Target language\n- Difficulty level\nWhat would you like to update?",
    "timestamp": 1747415178015,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz_request",
    "id": "71400649-e18c-4913-b156-7d4d26ad1d6c",
    "question": "i want a quiz",
    "response": "Quel type de quiz souhaitez-vous passer ? Nous proposons :\r\n1. Vocabulaire - Testez votre connaissance des mots\r\n2. Grammaire - Pratiquez les règles de langue\r\n3. Traduction - Traduisez entre les langues\r\n4. Choix multiple (MCQ) - Questions générales sur la langue\r\n\r\nVeuillez taper le numéro (1-4) ou le nom du quiz que vous souhaitez passer.",
    "timestamp": 1747412814534,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "thanks",
    "id": "642b9a1e-4b88-4c7e-9a4c-32321b9ee6d6",
    "question": "set difficulty level easy",
    "response": "You can change your settings for:\n- Mother language\n- Target language\n- Difficulty level\nWhat would you like to update?",
    "timestamp": 1747412631131,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "thanks",
    "id": "5fe324a6-a407-4aa3-85d6-33e742954aa2",
    "question": "set difficulty level easy",
    "response": "You can change your settings for:\n- Mother language\n- Target language\n- Difficulty level\nWhat would you like to update?",
    "timestamp": 1747412451544,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "thanks",
    "id": "9fa162a1-9aaf-4cb3-8ee0-d7e2e4593ab5",
    "question": "set difficulty level  hard",
    "response": "You can change your settings for:\n- Mother language\n- Target language\n- Difficulty level\nWhat would you like to update?",
    "timestamp": 1747412444209,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "system",
    "id": "19e82a99-7b8f-46dd-89ea-7579e437c49c",
    "question": "settings",
    "response": "Displayed user settings",
    "timestamp": 1747412422016,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "thanks",
    "id": "3576fb61-1f1e-4441-a0d0-431b169382c7",
    "question": "difficulty level hard",
    "response": "I'm not sure I understand. Try asking about quizzes, changing settings.",
    "timestamp": 1747412405755,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "thanks",
    "id": "bd04c517-6e9a-46a9-b915-a5c615d36b45",
    "question": "set difficulty hard",
    "response": "You can change your settings for:\n- Mother language\n- Target language\n- Difficulty level\nWhat would you like to update?",
    "timestamp": 1747412380324,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "system",
    "id": "cfe0ac2d-5857-4b5a-b2ae-02eb46761694",
    "question": "settings",
    "response": "Displayed user settings",
    "timestamp": 1747412331296,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "system",
    "id": "34713e76-8809-4e87-9ef3-6418bcffefd7",
    "question": "help",
    "response": "\r\nAvailable commands:\r\n1. chat - Start a conversation\r\n2. quiz - Take a quiz\r\n3. history - View your learning history\r\n4. preferences - Set your language preferences\r\n5. help - Show this help message\r\n6. logout - Log out\r\n7. exit - Exit the application\r\n",
    "timestamp": 1747412319834,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "thanks",
    "id": "30eb8a21-6a3f-4bce-be28-15b130be1244",
    "question": "set difficulty level hard",
    "response": "You can change your settings for:\n- Mother language\n- Target language\n- Difficulty level\nWhat would you like to update?",
    "timestamp": 1747412105853,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "thanks",
    "id": "90d391c3-c2a2-40bd-8d01-5f102cd16545",
    "question": "set difficulty level medium",
    "response": "You can change your settings for:\n- Mother language\n- Target language\n- Difficulty level\nWhat would you like to update?",
    "timestamp": 1747412075968,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "thanks",
    "id": "ecbb8f44-50c9-4250-a05b-d627a903e475",
    "question": "set difficulty level medium",
    "response": "You can change your settings for:\n- Mother language\n- Target language\n- Difficulty level\nWhat would you like to update?",
    "timestamp": 1747411914366,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "thanks",
    "id": "8a278e53-38eb-4c53-843b-ab1f57372859",
    "question": "difficulty level",
    "response": "I'm not sure I understand. Try asking about quizzes, changing settings.",
    "timestamp": 1747411899931,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "thanks",
    "id": "53297384-b476-4f9b-86e3-c269ec909fdb",
    "question": "set difficulty level medium",
    "response": "You can change your settings for:\n- Mother language\n- Target language\n- Difficulty level\nWhat would you like to update?",
    "timestamp": 1747411867480,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "thanks",
    "id": "14b662b5-6e20-45c2-8446-aba9a716173e",
    "question": "set difficulty level hard",
    "response": "You can change your settings for:\n- Mother language\n- Target language\n- Difficulty level\nWhat would you like to update?",
    "timestamp": 1747411853234,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "b3f105db-a1ff-4d8b-b317-235191639c1e",
    "question": "exit quiz",
    "response": "Exited quiz mode",
    "timestamp": 1747410938968,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "994ce756-2f9f-4af3-8923-9d43f060b62a",
    "question": "Quiz Question 2: Example question 2?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: That's not correct. The correct answer is: Option B",
    "timestamp": 1747410192725,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "5db9e045-17b1-4302-b04b-0348d9ff52fb",
    "question": "Quiz Question 1: Example question 3?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: That's not correct. The correct answer is: Option C",
    "timestamp": 1747410192255,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "c3ed43f6-b5e4-47fa-a0f8-da0885c41775",
    "question": "vocabulary",
    "response": "Started a Vocabulary quiz",
    "timestamp": 1747410189731,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "language_selection",
    "id": "46547fd0-7a8b-4d76-8e3e-0dbb0c021eb0",
    "question": "i want to learn english",
    "response": "Great! I'll help you learn english. Would you like to take a quiz to practice?",
    "timestamp": 1747410183092,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "60901920-675f-4805-b9f9-13bbfa793b88",
    "question": "Quiz Question 5: Was ist 'old' auf Deutsch?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747410113809,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "f23b570f-c1b3-4dae-80bb-631f6c6dac8d",
    "question": "Quiz Question 4: Was ist 'young' auf Deutsch?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747410113194,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "58b92a80-9fdd-4b3d-bda5-e9dcf0393f3b",
    "question": "Quiz Question 3: Was ist 'beautiful' auf Deutsch?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747410102903,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "dd2c27b2-d327-4c48-aed9-b4c7b4ceae9d",
    "question": "Quiz Question 2: Was ist 'big' auf Deutsch?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747410102000,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "2c1033ff-1afb-4ce9-a820-e50dee1d804c",
    "question": "Quiz Question 1: Was ist 'small' auf Deutsch?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747410101586,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "55c50445-861e-43eb-81a6-e1c86947e3be",
    "question": "vocabulry",
    "response": "Started a Vocabulary quiz",
    "timestamp": 1747410091493,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "language_selection",
    "id": "e75d2482-3a72-44de-93dd-d61a5b31276b",
    "question": "i want learn german",
    "response": "Great! I'll help you learn german. Would you like to take a quiz to practice?",
    "timestamp": 1747410082716,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "bd9d1946-dd55-4e80-b23d-e842e2e1ab9b",
    "question": "exit quiz",
    "response": "Exited quiz mode",
    "timestamp": 1747409657554,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "40971baf-292f-4d89-81a1-17e958ad3c5d",
    "question": "What type of quiz would you like to take?",
    "response": "grammar",
    "timestamp": 1747409650478,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "e9b85154-bc34-429a-b7a8-d3b94892b97a",
    "question": "exit quiz",
    "response": "Exited quiz mode",
    "timestamp": 1747409632319,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "d6f9da24-544a-4bf3-b7b6-7291151d7f20",
    "question": "What type of quiz would you like to take?",
    "response": "vocabulary",
    "timestamp": 1747409624369,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "33fe9bef-c314-4aff-9795-3353eec13e37",
    "question": "exit quiz",
    "response": "Exited quiz mode",
    "timestamp": 1747409583421,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "5c6fba97-6cfc-48ad-b6de-440fd13f6b68",
    "question": "vocabulary",
    "response": "Started a Vocabulary quiz",
    "timestamp": 1747409568998,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "language_selection",
    "id": "24acba74-442f-47ca-8cb7-2a6cb1cd6ca9",
    "question": "i want to learn english",
    "response": "Great! I'll help you learn english. Would you like to take a quiz to practice?",
    "timestamp": 1747409557459,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "d33109ab-f0a5-48ce-80ce-ff00b0f15697",
    "question": "Quiz Question 5: Example question 5?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747409515443,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "6c686b32-8b43-430d-b6fd-3ca8d7c41eba",
    "question": "Quiz Question 4: Example question 1?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747409515049,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "1b17d33f-db8a-414b-bb36-35a5adfa7b3e",
    "question": "Quiz Question 3: Example question 3?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: That's not correct. The correct answer is: Option C",
    "timestamp": 1747409514646,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "140948c9-ac44-485a-8669-e3390bfa78ca",
    "question": "Quiz Question 2: Example question 4?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: That's not correct. The correct answer is: Option D",
    "timestamp": 1747409514190,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "beaab8ea-6e91-4a06-b9c9-99d9692f7ac0",
    "question": "Quiz Question 1: Example question 2?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: That's not correct. The correct answer is: Option B",
    "timestamp": 1747409513521,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "16b89c54-5185-4ca6-99f8-3ed6b2807707",
    "question": "vocabulary",
    "response": "Started a Vocabulary quiz",
    "timestamp": 1747409497940,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "language_selection",
    "id": "ea53150f-1dcb-4e1a-920c-6db6be02d3fc",
    "question": "learn german",
    "response": "Great! I'll help you learn german. Would you like to take a quiz to practice?",
    "timestamp": 1747409488737,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "91cb77fb-1fcd-4678-b742-71366ac4e24f",
    "question": "Quiz Question 5: What time do Spaniards typically eat dinner?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747409469963,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "3cfe5dca-9410-4e0a-9d17-b9a21dabd36f",
    "question": "Quiz Question 4: Which of these is a traditional Spanish dance?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747409469475,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "8cfb20be-d360-4e6f-ba59-ad0516026bd0",
    "question": "Quiz Question 3: What color is the Spanish flag?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747409469030,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "7c867e4c-9d28-4561-8be8-1458faad31a7",
    "question": "Quiz Question 2: What is the traditional Spanish midday rest called?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747409468596,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "ede2676c-96f3-4b1f-822b-56684eb93b36",
    "question": "Quiz Question 1: What is the currency used in Spain?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747409468099,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "b438c732-447a-463b-8c52-ac5004dbb5b7",
    "question": "mcq",
    "response": "Started a MCQ quiz",
    "timestamp": 1747409463458,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "language_selection",
    "id": "1a79e962-b9a2-45d2-bdc2-c6d33fd8a813",
    "question": "learn spanish",
    "response": "Great! I'll help you learn spanish. Would you like to take a quiz to practice?",
    "timestamp": 1747409442476,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "e86867d4-eb7b-46a1-b930-d5cc6780d9b2",
    "question": "exit quiz",
    "response": "Exited quiz mode",
    "timestamp": 1747409434312,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "1409ae50-42f1-49c6-96e9-d74f3651adf5",
    "question": "What type of quiz would you like to take?",
    "response": "2",
    "timestamp": 1747409429098,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "c0f23259-1c30-4c58-b21d-5e13421fc863",
    "question": "Quiz Question 1: What is the currency used in France?",
    "response": "Answer: i want to learn spanish, Feedback: That's not correct. The correct answer is: Euro",
    "timestamp": 1747409368135,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "bfdbc032-8f51-48b3-8e0e-a51032927515",
    "question": "learn me spanish",
    "response": "Started a MCQ quiz",
    "timestamp": 1747409351929,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "thanks",
    "id": "6e6dd23c-2086-404a-a76a-c01d11461418",
    "question": "set Difficulty level hard",
    "response": "You can change your settings for:\n- Mother language\n- Target language\n- Difficulty level\nWhat would you like to update?",
    "timestamp": 1747409115762,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "thanks",
    "id": "20e5036f-d8a3-47fc-be6d-a0fb1a8e7300",
    "question": "Difficulty level easy",
    "response": "I'm not sure I understand. Try asking about quizzes, changing settings.",
    "timestamp": 1747409102042,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "thanks",
    "id": "51d61a23-2640-4ad8-8a88-db4c6f015642",
    "question": "set difficulty easy",
    "response": "You can change your settings for:\n- Mother language\n- Target language\n- Difficulty level\nWhat would you like to update?",
    "timestamp": 1747409077762,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "unknown",
    "id": "67fd12e5-4ed8-444c-81d5-35f64b2cd048",
    "question": "chat",
    "response": "I'm not sure I understand. Try asking about quizzes, changing settings.",
    "timestamp": 1747409002997,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "system",
    "id": "80ab3a24-ea68-4534-93fb-4cb657019d68",
    "question": "help",
    "response": "\r\nAvailable commands:\r\n1. chat - Start a conversation\r\n2. quiz - Take a quiz\r\n3. history - View your learning history\r\n4. preferences - Set your language preferences\r\n5. help - Show this help message\r\n6. logout - Log out\r\n7. exit - Exit the application\r\n",
    "timestamp": 1747408996934,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "system",
    "id": "0f6e5dc8-0910-4ae7-8789-4ea09c344e2d",
    "question": "analytics",
    "response": "Displayed user analytics",
    "timestamp": 1747403880226,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "thanks",
    "id": "fc4e7571-ad93-4c9a-b027-7e7cea3292e0",
    "question": "thank you lautaro",
    "response": "You're welcome! Would you like to try a quiz or Changing Settings?",
    "timestamp": 1747403869225,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "0da110a4-7d8c-49c1-bb4d-b46b615a1a39",
    "question": "Quiz Question 5: Translate 'I would like to order' to German",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747403850043,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "d59827f3-835d-4863-b458-c81651da5d29",
    "question": "Quiz Question 4: How do you say 'This food is delicious' in German?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747403848246,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "61093de6-2731-4adc-9da0-ac19144e46b0",
    "question": "Quiz Question 3: Translate 'I am allergic to nuts' to German",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747403846030,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "fe9a852d-97e7-4d57-99aa-dd4cea5c0d34",
    "question": "Quiz Question 2: Translate 'Is there a vegetarian option?' to German",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747403842923,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "c5a4959e-37ec-466c-a89d-0ac919990908",
    "question": "Quiz Question 1: How do you say 'The bill, please' in German?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747403841360,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "dd0fd475-4481-4cba-b1e6-9ef879b819d4",
    "question": "translation",
    "response": "Started a Translation quiz",
    "timestamp": 1747403839326,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "language_selection",
    "id": "4257cd15-5820-45f8-98be-d184ade25ace",
    "question": "i want to learn german",
    "response": "Great! I'll help you learn german. Would you like to take a quiz to practice?",
    "timestamp": 1747403829496,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "unknown",
    "id": "a794e137-91d8-4439-b206-4c919c20c48d",
    "question": "i want to lear german",
    "response": "I'm not sure I understand. Try asking about quizzes, changing settings.",
    "timestamp": 1747403820821,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "thanks",
    "id": "f946ee12-d4dc-41f9-9f5d-12e9f90bf371",
    "question": "thank you baby",
    "response": "You're welcome! Would you like to try a quiz or Changing Settings?",
    "timestamp": 1747403798760,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "ea5b0fd6-b9a3-4fc3-bc1d-3fb060022a3f",
    "question": "Quiz Question 5: Which is NOT a neighboring country of France?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747403791630,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "4f7000ff-b00a-4eeb-a9f7-526868c20eff",
    "question": "Quiz Question 4: Which mountain range is found in France?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747403790651,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "9c39c182-5c0c-4f63-a872-15035a7e08b6",
    "question": "Quiz Question 3: Which is the longest river in France?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747403789681,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "0e3950ae-b88d-4f25-be00-2a945f7b3db6",
    "question": "Quiz Question 2: Which sea borders the south of France?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747403788730,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "340b9c53-c396-476f-9b53-deacc585d988",
    "question": "Quiz Question 1: Which French region is known for its wine production?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747403787658,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "73798f3d-7c9b-4aa4-89db-99b98e7d2d9d",
    "question": "mcq",
    "response": "Started a MCQ quiz",
    "timestamp": 1747403786159,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "language_selection",
    "id": "cd20c6fe-e8ff-4a83-9724-2d4875710bc0",
    "question": "i want to learn french",
    "response": "Great! I'll help you learn french. Would you like to take a quiz to practice?",
    "timestamp": 1747403770481,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "c1e3eaf1-3f80-4be7-a5c8-be5fdb04e64f",
    "question": "Quiz Question 5: Which of these is a famous French fashion brand?",
    "response": "Answer: i, Feedback: That's not correct. The correct answer is: Chanel",
    "timestamp": 1747403760832,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "59261bf9-f7fb-4e36-8160-e2d5f69cca2c",
    "question": "Quiz Question 4: What is a 'baguette'?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747403758647,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "4e0e7a09-80f0-4678-8938-383a9c69c17d",
    "question": "Quiz Question 3: What is the typical French greeting?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747403757395,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "44f89508-1c23-42dc-a0b0-59afe90d0bce",
    "question": "Quiz Question 2: What is the most widely spoken language in France?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747403756151,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "d3d9d6e0-d7b1-4f1e-a43f-2e5046018c58",
    "question": "Quiz Question 1: What is the currency used in France?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747403755181,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "46765e16-5db9-4f64-80a6-24e7f43cc09a",
    "question": "What type of quiz would you like to take?",
    "response": "4",
    "timestamp": 1747403753584,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "language_question",
    "id": "463f28b8-f71c-44fa-b0af-2b0bccef88e6",
    "question": "hi",
    "response": "Hello, mazen! I'm your Language Learning Bot. Would you like to practice vocabulary, grammar, or start a quiz?",
    "timestamp": 1747403745805,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "unknown",
    "id": "5b1e9d67-545d-4f3c-82a1-508b92ef997b",
    "question": "eif",
    "response": "I'm not sure I understand. Try asking about quizzes, changing settings.",
    "timestamp": 1747403496572,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "unknown",
    "id": "05ac8c60-06b0-475d-9fd3-179b6d307e0e",
    "question": "exff",
    "response": "I'm not sure I understand. Try asking about quizzes, changing settings.",
    "timestamp": 1747403491946,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "system",
    "id": "fa697748-4c49-4f20-abaa-24fe4ba66479",
    "question": "analytics",
    "response": "Displayed user analytics",
    "timestamp": 1747403452475,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "5e2ca6ea-7818-408e-a14b-c7f8bf20f8b7",
    "question": "Quiz Question 5: Which of these is a famous French fashion brand?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747403448499,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "1c624cdb-1d43-4b78-972c-09d2e371aa2b",
    "question": "Quiz Question 4: What is the typical French greeting?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747403448074,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "de3aae3f-464f-47f9-8926-bf84ba3107fe",
    "question": "Quiz Question 3: What is the currency used in France?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747403447731,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "661d60c0-0386-4bfc-88db-760efdfc910f",
    "question": "Quiz Question 2: What is the most widely spoken language in France?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747403447391,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "4917620a-f45c-45eb-9583-344fa77cd7af",
    "question": "Quiz Question 1: What is a 'baguette'?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747403447065,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "22a8cc6f-0821-4357-a6f9-0cb700a5028a",
    "question": "What type of quiz would you like to take?",
    "response": "4",
    "timestamp": 1747403445908,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "system",
    "id": "249ba95f-b7b9-42db-9651-6c990a23f91a",
    "question": "analytics",
    "response": "Displayed user analytics",
    "timestamp": 1747403405098,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "unknown",
    "id": "619b30a1-94e9-4ab4-b653-74b4446f349e",
    "question": "analtics",
    "response": "I'm not sure I understand. Try asking about quizzes, changing settings.",
    "timestamp": 1747403400791,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "9f716b12-a43a-48a0-a232-646f49978279",
    "question": "Quiz Question 5: Which is NOT a neighboring country of France?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747403330200,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "dd9e0609-abfa-4ce9-8abb-d4bb5b8470ac",
    "question": "Quiz Question 4: Which is the longest river in France?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747403329530,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "cf7f7c3a-9751-4a8a-bed3-0ad2ea8b5f86",
    "question": "Quiz Question 3: Which French region is known for its wine production?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747403329086,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "e5aa0d2d-e8a2-4030-906b-479fcd72df87",
    "question": "Quiz Question 2: Which sea borders the south of France?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747403328646,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "9c5f727c-27c5-4460-a52f-1fd6b9538138",
    "question": "Quiz Question 1: Which mountain range is found in France?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747403328309,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "c4a0c80a-1708-41ab-8bb7-9a038cf4b550",
    "question": "What type of quiz would you like to take?",
    "response": "4",
    "timestamp": 1747403327529,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "language_question",
    "id": "8120507b-1ffa-4744-8ff1-4925ee06107b",
    "question": "a",
    "response": "What would you like to know about language learning? I can help with vocabulary, grammar, and more.",
    "timestamp": 1747403305434,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "41c92f98-c5b4-4185-bccc-693e03e1db72",
    "question": "Quiz Question 5: What colors are on the French flag?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747403304856,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "03602d9f-253c-43af-9d81-481f78c80d22",
    "question": "Quiz Question 4: Which city is the capital of France?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747403304258,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "58eda568-ca4d-4fcc-a146-3ee6e0c613a0",
    "question": "Quiz Question 3: Which French dish consists of snails cooked with garlic and butter?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747403303819,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "feed17dd-ce7a-449c-9ab9-4fe530927ad9",
    "question": "Quiz Question 2: Which of these is a traditional French cheese?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747403303431,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "e1aa44a2-a6a8-4c16-aac6-352dc66e3b0e",
    "question": "Quiz Question 1: Which famous museum is located in Paris?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747403303127,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "3802d7a5-06d3-4edf-a6a3-8e1ded5a19e4",
    "question": "What type of quiz would you like to take?",
    "response": "4",
    "timestamp": 1747403302035,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "system",
    "id": "2e08ab64-1fe3-4de7-8a04-032a9edf8298",
    "question": "analytics",
    "response": "Displayed user analytics",
    "timestamp": 1747403290472,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "thanks",
    "id": "13bff42e-ab5c-4c09-937f-e5cd98241af4",
    "question": "exit pleae thnk you",
    "response": "You're welcome! Would you like to try a quiz or Changing Settings?",
    "timestamp": 1747402922732,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "thanks",
    "id": "bc32e262-62a0-4f1a-a1fc-17ca19d22152",
    "question": "thank you exit please",
    "response": "You're welcome! Would you like to try a quiz or Changing Settings?",
    "timestamp": 1747402914616,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "unknown",
    "id": "20b60b0e-3962-418a-812c-ce43c27f2d06",
    "question": "kareem",
    "response": "I'm not sure I understand. Try asking about quizzes, changing settings.",
    "timestamp": 1747402843390,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "unknown",
    "id": "bcffddb7-fc96-48b5-b959-95a662adc55e",
    "question": "mazen",
    "response": "I'm not sure I understand. Try asking about quizzes, changing settings.",
    "timestamp": 1747402841210,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "unknown",
    "id": "938dab3d-2883-44ef-9a07-d60b93f5150b",
    "question": "wggwgw",
    "response": "I'm not sure I understand. Try asking about quizzes, changing settings.",
    "timestamp": 1747402835658,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "language_question",
    "id": "c3b413be-8716-4be8-b5ca-5118e905798f",
    "question": "you are a goat",
    "response": "What would you like to know about language learning? I can help with vocabulary, grammar, and more.",
    "timestamp": 1747402831684,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "thanks",
    "id": "667cb1d3-1b55-4046-8ec7-ab2c9d42c09e",
    "question": "thank you very much hearty",
    "response": "You're welcome! Would you like to try a quiz or Changing Settings?",
    "timestamp": 1747402816811,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "4c5c2744-152b-4fe9-a7a0-8c2bda4faef9",
    "question": "Quiz Question 5: Which is NOT a neighboring country of France?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747402805592,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "e26d4e78-ca2a-4526-800b-e4c0593b7b43",
    "question": "Quiz Question 4: Which French region is known for its wine production?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747402805086,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "1c2a575d-0540-495d-b5b7-680ca27b2a10",
    "question": "Quiz Question 3: Which is the longest river in France?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747402804604,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "eb5898d5-6226-4a7c-a9c6-374daa8d7709",
    "question": "Quiz Question 2: Which sea borders the south of France?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747402804283,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "fbf4b3f8-19de-42d4-8c5c-121fe0f717fe",
    "question": "Quiz Question 1: Which mountain range is found in France?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747402803826,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "a38f2303-75a8-4f7c-bef2-50094d877a68",
    "question": "help me to start a quiz",
    "response": "Started a MCQ quiz",
    "timestamp": 1747402798568,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "greeting",
    "id": "4935cfbf-b6fc-424a-a233-adf79d53f312",
    "question": "hallo",
    "response": "Hello, mazen! I'm your Language Learning Bot. Would you like to practice vocabulary, grammar, or start a quiz?",
    "timestamp": 1747402787489,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "unknown",
    "id": "cbfeb237-8bec-4a97-b40b-39233dff3a20",
    "question": "hall\\",
    "response": "I'm not sure I understand. Try asking about quizzes, changing settings.",
    "timestamp": 1747402785281,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz_request",
    "id": "db106c08-4c9c-44f0-a822-f4539e9fe538",
    "question": "i want to start quiz",
    "response": "Quel type de quiz souhaitez-vous passer ? Nous proposons :\n1. Vocabulaire - Testez votre connaissance des mots\n2. Grammaire - Pratiquez les règles de langue\n3. Traduction - Traduisez entre les langues\n4. Choix multiple (MCQ) - Questions générales sur la langue\n\nVeuillez taper le numéro (1-4) ou le nom du quiz que vous souhaitez passer.",
    "timestamp": 1747402765439,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "63ba8b6a-992d-43ff-b9b0-9900697629fd",
    "question": "exit quiz",
    "response": "Exited quiz mode",
    "timestamp": 1747402751948,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "a8b78794-40fb-45a7-872e-d50ea45c329b",
    "question": "Quiz Question 1: Which city is the capital of France?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747402737596,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "18d8db30-02f4-4295-ab0e-87e5f473ad29",
    "question": "give me a quiz",
    "response": "Started a MCQ quiz",
    "timestamp": 1747402736167,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz_request",
    "id": "30fd05c9-e65e-49d5-ade8-81253684d9c9",
    "question": "quuz",
    "response": "Quel type de quiz souhaitez-vous passer ? Nous proposons :\n1. Vocabulaire - Testez votre connaissance des mots\n2. Grammaire - Pratiquez les règles de langue\n3. Traduction - Traduisez entre les langues\n4. Choix multiple (MCQ) - Questions générales sur la langue\n\nVeuillez taper le numéro (1-4) ou le nom du quiz que vous souhaitez passer.",
    "timestamp": 1747402725537,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "9278d415-594e-4107-b6c0-d0468d5cf8d7",
    "question": "Quiz Question 5: Which is the longest river in France?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747402722288,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "ddcdfd13-bc35-4ef4-a329-5e55be75a8cc",
    "question": "Quiz Question 4: Which French region is known for its wine production?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747402721428,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "de32f057-0322-4733-8f97-8dde6cfa6ce8",
    "question": "Quiz Question 3: Which mountain range is found in France?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747402719911,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "8916b235-b916-4c51-9085-b8994bd1c54e",
    "question": "Quiz Question 2: Which sea borders the south of France?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747402719406,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "7fcaee9e-0d70-4d90-b7d5-03c013e6a440",
    "question": "Quiz Question 1: Which is NOT a neighboring country of France?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747402719123,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "04b54630-4b70-4ee3-bc0a-763d479a1c1d",
    "question": "What type of quiz would you like to take?",
    "response": "4",
    "timestamp": 1747402717953,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "language_question",
    "id": "48a38b01-c817-4ec8-9c80-6a58c4657ebe",
    "question": "hi",
    "response": "Hello, mazen! I'm your Language Learning Bot. Would you like to practice vocabulary, grammar, or start a quiz?",
    "timestamp": 1747402709584,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "c5bfebee-e187-4fd5-a2ae-5719b34e345f",
    "question": "exit quiz",
    "response": "Exited quiz mode",
    "timestamp": 1747402544148,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "05b5f1ee-33dd-4b7f-ad32-2c158c8da365",
    "question": "give me a grammer quiz",
    "response": "Started a Grammar quiz",
    "timestamp": 1747402541105,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "language_question",
    "id": "7c71beb1-b4c5-4bfb-b3b1-6913a0c12ed5",
    "question": "hi",
    "response": "Hello, mazen! I'm your Language Learning Bot. Would you like to practice vocabulary, grammar, or start a quiz?",
    "timestamp": 1747402521496,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "599f87a7-283f-4432-9852-13505f8a6dd3",
    "question": "Quiz Question 5: Which Spanish city is famous for the 'Running of the Bulls'?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747402517740,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "fff687be-436f-48d0-b7e0-c113176e041b",
    "question": "Quiz Question 4: Which mountain range runs along the border between Spain and France?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747402517120,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "e438b35f-a2b4-42f1-b703-d58c9b4a70f5",
    "question": "Quiz Question 3: Which animal is featured on the Spanish coat of arms?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747402516594,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "60a94506-e041-4083-aa3e-1316cd7a7e20",
    "question": "Quiz Question 2: Which is the longest river in Spain?",
    "response": "Answer: exit uz, Feedback: That's not correct. The correct answer is: Ebro",
    "timestamp": 1747402508490,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "60d64b29-565e-469e-8f12-7fdf61ff781c",
    "question": "Quiz Question 1: Which of these Spanish islands is located in the Mediterranean Sea?",
    "response": "Answer: , Feedback: You didn't provide an answer. The correct answer is: Mallorca",
    "timestamp": 1747402500356,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "44995f66-30b4-4d32-8fb4-fd437d3472d6",
    "question": "give me spanish quiz",
    "response": "Started a MCQ quiz",
    "timestamp": 1747402500346,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "9e41ba15-1f5e-4542-8220-339bcd343c2b",
    "question": "exit quiz",
    "response": "Exited quiz mode",
    "timestamp": 1747402489515,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "83c56173-eb97-4866-9f0d-f8538aecac55",
    "question": "learn me spanish",
    "response": "Started a MCQ quiz",
    "timestamp": 1747402335853,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "language_selection",
    "id": "f6ba748d-8107-4a8c-aeef-6ff038a014f1",
    "question": "i want to learn spanish",
    "response": "Great! I'll help you learn spanish. Would you like to take a quiz to practice?",
    "timestamp": 1747402324381,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "language_question",
    "id": "1b5d9618-3d4e-4726-8b10-9fee50e76a74",
    "question": "hi",
    "response": "Hello, mazen! I'm your Language Learning Bot. Would you like to practice vocabulary, grammar, or start a quiz?",
    "timestamp": 1747402308575,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "language_selection",
    "id": "28293d2e-3c78-474e-8a49-5e5d0b941e8a",
    "question": "i want to learn spanish",
    "response": "Great! I'll help you learn spanish. Would you like to take a quiz to practice?",
    "timestamp": 1747402032782,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "d02ad405-318f-4a27-bd79-565b6dbf3ac5",
    "question": "exit quiz",
    "response": "Exited quiz mode",
    "timestamp": 1747402022701,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "0a87003f-33bd-402a-8433-9c3bc4fa75c4",
    "question": "learn me spanish",
    "response": "Started a MCQ quiz",
    "timestamp": 1747402004150,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "unknown",
    "id": "870afc53-7481-42eb-89ab-260f55b6dc95",
    "question": "hello",
    "response": "Hello, mazen! I'm your Language Learning Bot. Would you like to practice vocabulary, grammar, or start a quiz?",
    "timestamp": 1747401993724,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "language_question",
    "id": "7f15b5bc-b8f6-4d05-8176-2bf17072b053",
    "question": "hi",
    "response": "Hello, mazen! I'm your Language Learning Bot. Would you like to practice vocabulary, grammar, or start a quiz?",
    "timestamp": 1747401990528,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "5a02d583-e4eb-4b1f-aa00-08a24a0ee0b9",
    "question": "learn me quiz",
    "response": "Started a MCQ quiz",
    "timestamp": 1747401787328,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "language_selection",
    "id": "ac233dec-670c-4f7c-89df-7ad0874cf3e3",
    "question": "i want to learn french",
    "response": "Great! I'll help you learn french. Would you like to take a quiz to practice?",
    "timestamp": 1747401766180,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "40ab85ee-2fef-4eed-9b30-0c1b25c59084",
    "question": "exit quiz",
    "response": "Exited quiz mode",
    "timestamp": 1747401668276,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "2ee59fe5-f492-4a19-9837-174aa2e93fd3",
    "question": "give me a grammar quiz",
    "response": "Started a Grammar quiz",
    "timestamp": 1747401660777,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "59b72dd2-9851-4c8c-8dcf-dc47fa63f3f5",
    "question": "exit quiz",
    "response": "Exited quiz mode",
    "timestamp": 1747401652528,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "30c921d1-aef8-4d58-b49b-80cfb8cfa9d3",
    "question": "give me a mcq quiz",
    "response": "Started a MCQ quiz",
    "timestamp": 1747401649535,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "unknown",
    "id": "3ffa8d97-afff-41d3-98a3-962dde227a60",
    "question": "wbwbw",
    "response": "I'm not sure I understand. Try asking about quizzes, changing settings.",
    "timestamp": 1747401641190,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "system",
    "id": "3ccd0765-3d96-4a66-a42c-a8cd36575a81",
    "question": "help",
    "response": "\nAvailable commands:\n1. chat - Start a conversation\n2. quiz - Take a quiz\n3. history - View your learning history\n4. preferences - Set your language preferences\n5. help - Show this help message\n6. logout - Log out\n7. exit - Exit the application\n",
    "timestamp": 1747401639898,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "thanks",
    "id": "f6ea0840-ca14-444b-bb1e-346132c5284a",
    "question": "hanks",
    "response": "You're welcome! Would you like to try a quiz or Changing Settings?",
    "timestamp": 1747401636871,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "unknown",
    "id": "5433c4d6-6187-4cec-aebf-95504107449c",
    "question": "wfww",
    "response": "I'm not sure I understand. Try asking about quizzes, changing settings.",
    "timestamp": 1747401627933,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "unknown",
    "id": "33287354-4642-4e39-892a-8731d5ab3bb2",
    "question": "mffkvkvkbkktkrk",
    "response": "I'm not sure I understand. Try asking about quizzes, changing settings.",
    "timestamp": 1747401623464,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "unknown",
    "id": "f926e810-6488-4a4c-9cd6-5faaed6fb7ce",
    "question": "rwnnqqqnnnq",
    "response": "I'm not sure I understand. Try asking about quizzes, changing settings.",
    "timestamp": 1747401619518,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "unknown",
    "id": "e7758185-8f91-4860-95b0-5ee3b2b2d990",
    "question": "gwgw",
    "response": "I'm not sure I understand. Try asking about quizzes, changing settings.",
    "timestamp": 1747401615938,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "82434349-1a72-4e96-b0d4-2813d4e2f02e",
    "question": "exit quiz",
    "response": "Cancelled quiz setup",
    "timestamp": 1747401607352,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "91e99df6-e912-4a90-b95c-13798856963a",
    "question": "What type of quiz would you like to take?",
    "response": "exit quiz",
    "timestamp": 1747401607344,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "2042b94d-433a-4d4d-ba24-28e3eeeab6e9",
    "question": "exit quiz",
    "response": "Exited quiz mode",
    "timestamp": 1747401600831,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "e955345a-c4d1-4113-8221-051704891c84",
    "question": "learn me a quiz",
    "response": "Started a MCQ quiz",
    "timestamp": 1747401593615,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "e5a25412-cb8e-4414-b7ee-0a8e0b23d27f",
    "question": "exit quiz",
    "response": "Exited quiz mode",
    "timestamp": 1747401581319,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "3942bc4d-1553-4ca1-93a0-65791556ed4e",
    "question": "give me a quiz",
    "response": "Started a MCQ quiz",
    "timestamp": 1747401577819,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz_request",
    "id": "146fbe01-ff7d-483f-96b9-8315f562ffa3",
    "question": "start a quiz",
    "response": "Quel type de quiz souhaitez-vous passer ? Nous proposons :\n1. Vocabulaire - Testez votre connaissance des mots\n2. Grammaire - Pratiquez les règles de langue\n3. Traduction - Traduisez entre les langues\n4. Choix multiple (MCQ) - Questions générales sur la langue\n\nVeuillez taper le numéro (1-4) ou le nom du quiz que vous souhaitez passer.",
    "timestamp": 1747401567975,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "unknown",
    "id": "8aaa6212-33af-4352-8a85-942f4f2ba05a",
    "question": "hello",
    "response": "Hello, mazen! I'm your Language Learning Bot. Would you like to practice vocabulary, grammar, or start a quiz?",
    "timestamp": 1747401564414,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "language_question",
    "id": "46211422-28ea-4a43-be6c-a1c08357fe45",
    "question": "hi",
    "response": "Hello, mazen! I'm your Language Learning Bot. Would you like to practice vocabulary, grammar, or start a quiz?",
    "timestamp": 1747401561356,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "unknown",
    "id": "7d3eb801-b1c0-4fe6-b4ad-36acd266eb70",
    "question": "hi",
    "response": "I'm not sure I understand. Try asking about quizzes, changing settings.",
    "timestamp": 1747401250742,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "unknown",
    "id": "c838036d-667d-4fb6-9bb2-871583dbdca7",
    "question": "hi",
    "response": "I'm not sure I understand. Try asking about quizzes, changing settings.",
    "timestamp": 1747401249035,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "unknown",
    "id": "8506e694-4778-4a18-80e4-bc482cf0698a",
    "question": "i",
    "response": "I'm not sure I understand. Try asking about quizzes, changing settings.",
    "timestamp": 1747401247664,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "unknown",
    "id": "b27bfa99-ba4c-4641-be3c-674a4671d272",
    "question": "hi",
    "response": "I'm not sure I understand. Try asking about quizzes, changing settings.",
    "timestamp": 1747401246781,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "unknown",
    "id": "eadeec04-a863-4835-9fcb-2b50c846a063",
    "question": "hu",
    "response": "I'm not sure I understand. Try asking about quizzes, changing settings.",
    "timestamp": 1747401245385,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "unknown",
    "id": "bb21c57e-11c2-482d-9cb9-593352d0cb5a",
    "question": "give mw grammar",
    "response": "I'm not sure I understand. Try asking about quizzes, changing settings.",
    "timestamp": 1747401242954,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "unknown",
    "id": "d3b21d6f-1eb9-49e4-9a15-0081eda9cb6f",
    "question": "give me grammar quiz",
    "response": "I'm not sure I understand. Try asking about quizzes, changing settings.",
    "timestamp": 1747401233836,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "c548cb0b-1e78-47bd-b440-d1cb02aa6f2f",
    "question": "3v3f3wf3fg3g3g34g34",
    "response": "Started a Translation quiz",
    "timestamp": 1747400998710,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "0a6facdc-73a6-473f-98ad-d93d4eb0aff0",
    "question": "exit quiz",
    "response": "Exited quiz mode",
    "timestamp": 1747400996866,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "7ff610d8-ad89-499d-b84f-90b75d38e3da",
    "question": "Quiz Question 1: Translate 'Is it far from here?' to French",
    "response": "Answer: 3v32v3ve4v3v3v3, Feedback: That's not correct. The correct answer is: All of these are correct",
    "timestamp": 1747400991810,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "b1591a45-3999-4767-8bef-9a824926e2bc",
    "question": "er3v3fe3f",
    "response": "Started a Translation quiz",
    "timestamp": 1747400985554,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "unknown",
    "id": "918c64ec-c41c-4c99-9b1b-57fa869ba295",
    "question": "hello",
    "response": "Hello, mazen! I'm your Language Learning Bot. Would you like to practice vocabulary, grammar, or start a quiz?",
    "timestamp": 1747400983372,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "language_question",
    "id": "02fb6de1-c93c-45c1-9260-ee9713201041",
    "question": "hi",
    "response": "Hello, mazen! I'm your Language Learning Bot. Would you like to practice vocabulary, grammar, or start a quiz?",
    "timestamp": 1747400981539,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "language_question",
    "id": "dd9d665e-3efb-430a-8273-5fef76028c0c",
    "question": "y kkjkjk",
    "response": "What would you like to know about language learning? I can help with vocabulary, grammar, pronunciation, and more.",
    "timestamp": 1747400766020,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "language_question",
    "id": "fc64ea0a-00f9-4593-931b-85765a237013",
    "question": "y hagagag",
    "response": "What would you like to know about language learning? I can help with vocabulary, grammar, pronunciation, and more.",
    "timestamp": 1747400755559,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "language_question",
    "id": "c5a68846-cad1-4d10-9d1e-09475e1e2776",
    "question": "a",
    "response": "What would you like to know about language learning? I can help with vocabulary, grammar, pronunciation, and more.",
    "timestamp": 1747400750995,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "language_question",
    "id": "089ea50b-8fc5-4747-97a3-ed1a6b064423",
    "question": "ay hagagagag",
    "response": "What would you like to know about language learning? I can help with vocabulary, grammar, pronunciation, and more.",
    "timestamp": 1747400747109,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "unknown",
    "id": "79be1eae-0737-4937-a024-bfbc0853362e",
    "question": "hello",
    "response": "Hello, mazen! I'm your Language Learning Bot. Would you like to practice vocabulary, grammar, or start a quiz?",
    "timestamp": 1747400738534,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "language_question",
    "id": "f83b3e0f-1dc3-4094-9cea-1b224ad8aaec",
    "question": "hi",
    "response": "Hello, mazen! I'm your Language Learning Bot. Would you like to practice vocabulary, grammar, or start a quiz?",
    "timestamp": 1747400735481,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "system",
    "id": "b4102631-349f-48ce-aaa7-824078d69e5f",
    "question": "analytics",
    "response": "Displayed user analytics",
    "timestamp": 1747400723688,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "16f3d0a9-41b0-4c87-88cb-37341eaaf4c3",
    "question": "exit quiz",
    "response": "Exited quiz mode",
    "timestamp": 1747400713993,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "fa744e46-bb39-4850-9256-af3517fa6ed0",
    "question": "learn me quiz",
    "response": "Started a MCQ quiz",
    "timestamp": 1747400709614,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "831a1b54-5b8a-40b2-9ca9-e970c2b9d0c9",
    "question": "exit quiz",
    "response": "Cancelled quiz setup",
    "timestamp": 1747400704196,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "3df9a633-7bc2-4db8-b8f9-b968c95f6883",
    "question": "What type of quiz would you like to take?",
    "response": "exit quiz",
    "timestamp": 1747400704191,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "unknown",
    "id": "495766df-db72-4992-acd9-067746d69eea",
    "question": "quizess",
    "response": "I'm not sure I understand. Try asking about quizzes, changing settings.",
    "timestamp": 1747400686375,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "unknown",
    "id": "a6041d2d-2acc-4a5b-9481-aaaf97c7b69e",
    "question": "quzzies",
    "response": "I'm not sure I understand. Try asking about quizzes, changing settings.",
    "timestamp": 1747400679387,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "unknown",
    "id": "1628c4c7-7726-4f3a-afe0-aa91bf356374",
    "question": "ard",
    "response": "I'm not sure I understand. Try asking about quizzes, changing settings.",
    "timestamp": 1747400673138,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "unknown",
    "id": "70f25550-f622-4831-a6ab-d737335bd56f",
    "question": "cqfqf",
    "response": "I'm not sure I understand. Try asking about quizzes, changing settings.",
    "timestamp": 1747400668752,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "language_question",
    "id": "dfe368c5-9dbe-42fc-8b1b-bd008a330719",
    "question": "a",
    "response": "What would you like to know about language learning? I can help with vocabulary, grammar, pronunciation, and more.",
    "timestamp": 1747400634794,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "thanks",
    "id": "b2f13007-291d-4743-994f-fef9bf299208",
    "question": "thanks",
    "response": "You're welcome! Would you like to try a quiz or Changing Settings?",
    "timestamp": 1747400630993,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "3f855645-eaf3-4e33-8293-0fe7f82f2b60",
    "question": "Quiz Question 5: What is the typical French greeting?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747400628343,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "d07f4832-3cbe-4c96-997f-1a5a7b16943b",
    "question": "Quiz Question 4: What is the currency used in France?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747400628001,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "01a4ba1e-6de0-4fc4-a433-bcd57b3d1738",
    "question": "Quiz Question 3: What is the most widely spoken language in France?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747400627591,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "aafe125c-e1a6-4ff4-9f37-b74db38b4d51",
    "question": "Quiz Question 2: Which of these is a famous French fashion brand?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747400627334,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "f8d4e21f-3b26-46d4-b8ab-4cd4211cc3ed",
    "question": "Quiz Question 1: What is a 'baguette'?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747400627015,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "413e6ce9-605d-44ec-93fe-c2d2d6af54be",
    "question": "learn me a quiz",
    "response": "Started a MCQ quiz",
    "timestamp": 1747400624629,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz_request",
    "id": "52628814-d6b8-49a0-9500-1b0795983661",
    "question": "start a quiz",
    "response": "Quel type de quiz souhaitez-vous passer ? Nous proposons :\n1. Vocabulaire - Testez votre connaissance des mots\n2. Grammaire - Pratiquez les règles de langue\n3. Traduction - Traduisez entre les langues\n4. Choix multiple (MCQ) - Questions générales sur la langue\n\nVeuillez taper le numéro (1-4) ou le nom du quiz que vous souhaitez passer.",
    "timestamp": 1747400565146,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "ceab330d-3819-46cb-989a-910304a02c1b",
    "question": "exit quiz",
    "response": "Cancelled quiz setup",
    "timestamp": 1747400559455,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "a5227ac4-848c-4f9d-bb31-49556ad09f1a",
    "question": "What type of quiz would you like to take?",
    "response": "exit quiz",
    "timestamp": 1747400559450,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "e78bbf4d-6f5c-4860-9857-5a0dd12b161f",
    "question": "What type of quiz would you like to take?",
    "response": "start a quiz",
    "timestamp": 1747400552102,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "085a58b2-4f53-460e-8fb8-13dbca8e37e1",
    "question": "What type of quiz would you like to take?",
    "response": "start a quiz",
    "timestamp": 1747400545447,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz_request",
    "id": "bfaa617b-2c60-4de3-ac82-6ee589a2104f",
    "question": "start a quiz",
    "response": "Quel type de quiz souhaitez-vous passer ? Nous proposons :\n1. Vocabulaire - Testez votre connaissance des mots\n2. Grammaire - Pratiquez les règles de langue\n3. Traduction - Traduisez entre les langues\n4. Choix multiple (MCQ) - Questions générales sur la langue\n\nVeuillez taper le numéro (1-4) ou le nom du quiz que vous souhaitez passer.",
    "timestamp": 1747400483001,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "ce95bbfa-f843-40e6-b2b0-a371f4205681",
    "question": "exit quiz",
    "response": "Exited quiz mode",
    "timestamp": 1747400478669,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "6fddd935-1b55-4ac6-83f7-00dd7b0ceafb",
    "question": "learn me",
    "response": "Started a MCQ quiz",
    "timestamp": 1747400474453,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "thanks",
    "id": "9dc3d51b-64e4-416c-b59f-02d4fec73e6d",
    "question": "thanks",
    "response": "You're welcome! Would you like to try a quiz or Changing Settings?",
    "timestamp": 1747400470802,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "unknown",
    "id": "46d4389a-8cfd-42da-8604-f1ab5ca1993d",
    "question": "hello",
    "response": "Hello, mazen! I'm your Language Learning Bot. Would you like to practice vocabulary, grammar, or start a quiz?",
    "timestamp": 1747400469044,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "language_question",
    "id": "9f2ab4c1-f32b-4354-aad0-00ce1406fe0d",
    "question": "hi",
    "response": "Hello, mazen! I'm your Language Learning Bot. Would you like to practice vocabulary, grammar, or start a quiz?",
    "timestamp": 1747400466794,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "language_question",
    "id": "fc42af51-7033-4ae6-ab05-e441d3bf77c3",
    "question": "a",
    "response": "What would you like to know about language learning? I can help with vocabulary, grammar, pronunciation, and more.",
    "timestamp": 1747400464803,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "02b6ef82-bb99-4896-ac01-458b8d9998c1",
    "question": "Quiz Question 5: Which famous museum is located in Paris?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747400463813,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "19db41a9-ab4a-461b-b65b-ec9932b78abc",
    "question": "Quiz Question 4: What colors are on the French flag?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747400463265,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "a48dbcdf-0549-4440-b9c7-f1b143bb6938",
    "question": "Quiz Question 3: Which French dish consists of snails cooked with garlic and butter?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747400463038,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "8002d1f1-593f-4b45-af85-e90dcbe47a8b",
    "question": "Quiz Question 2: Which of these is a traditional French cheese?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747400462786,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "8597ff42-be5b-49c8-8cb6-093099fd70ab",
    "question": "Quiz Question 1: Which city is the capital of France?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747400462489,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "e77871ef-8ba3-41b3-a378-400d3085eaf5",
    "question": "learn me french",
    "response": "Started a MCQ quiz",
    "timestamp": 1747400460179,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "language_question",
    "id": "5fef1052-7d72-4684-a1e1-a4b29dbecb7a",
    "question": "hi",
    "response": "Hello, mazen! I'm your Language Learning Bot. Would you like to practice vocabulary, grammar, or start a quiz?",
    "timestamp": 1747400454186,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "language_question",
    "id": "6c2abb72-a4fd-46d5-b31a-d004bfe9391a",
    "question": "a",
    "response": "What would you like to know about language learning? I can help with vocabulary, grammar, pronunciation, and more.",
    "timestamp": 1747400452735,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "language_question",
    "id": "d65d35ab-06bd-456f-ab51-0b35df752b46",
    "question": "a",
    "response": "What would you like to know about language learning? I can help with vocabulary, grammar, pronunciation, and more.",
    "timestamp": 1747400451856,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "language_question",
    "id": "107714c0-80ef-4d5f-8e91-24dcea81ba3c",
    "question": "a",
    "response": "What would you like to know about language learning? I can help with vocabulary, grammar, pronunciation, and more.",
    "timestamp": 1747400450377,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "0c824e3d-12a9-4f86-b25b-02f3cd4fac7a",
    "question": "Quiz Question 5: Which article is correct: ___ ami",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747400449566,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "7efc802f-2275-4b04-af5a-5df189d91052",
    "question": "Quiz Question 4: Which article is correct: ___ voiture",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747400448450,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "7df130d5-81eb-4a14-92fc-746c91fa556c",
    "question": "Quiz Question 3: Which is the correct feminine form of 'un ami'?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747400447969,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "f1cfb100-f6e5-4b5b-8887-20e3e0848f90",
    "question": "Quiz Question 2: Which article is correct: ___ livre",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747400447554,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "b6f93634-869a-4ae8-ad68-98c37875ba5b",
    "question": "Quiz Question 1: Which is the correct plural form of 'un animal'?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747400447090,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "bef9f55f-8b88-4632-8c93-2b18c4c0ed63",
    "question": "give me grammar quiz",
    "response": "Started a Grammar quiz",
    "timestamp": 1747400444665,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "3d8fddb5-551b-4206-aa83-b2b3c8c1b15a",
    "question": "exit quiz",
    "response": "Exited quiz mode",
    "timestamp": 1747400437206,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "7e75f51e-d9a1-4699-8301-ca10673db7cc",
    "question": "learn me english",
    "response": "Started a MCQ quiz",
    "timestamp": 1747400225416,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "eee81acf-6ad4-4824-b427-17691e74d683",
    "question": "exit quiz",
    "response": "Exited quiz mode",
    "timestamp": 1747400220432,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "b43e68b3-8c64-4830-8f68-ea723945891b",
    "question": "learn me english",
    "response": "Started a MCQ quiz",
    "timestamp": 1747400119693,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "150a3e83-ee6d-4684-9e0f-68cc750dea94",
    "question": "Quiz Question 5: Which sea borders the south of France?",
    "response": "Answer: 4, Feedback: That's not correct. The correct answer is: Mediterranean Sea",
    "timestamp": 1747400111093,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "90fd5c1a-21a9-4253-a344-14a496ec180d",
    "question": "Quiz Question 4: Which is NOT a neighboring country of France?",
    "response": "Answer: 4, Feedback: That's not correct. The correct answer is: Portugal",
    "timestamp": 1747400110211,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "11165a12-f4a1-471c-bea0-01759b927621",
    "question": "Quiz Question 3: Which is the longest river in France?",
    "response": "Answer: 4, Feedback: That's not correct. The correct answer is: Loire",
    "timestamp": 1747400109382,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "03d06604-7a98-4af8-93ca-88a39708a7b9",
    "question": "Quiz Question 2: Which French region is known for its wine production?",
    "response": "Answer: 4, Feedback: That's not correct. The correct answer is: Bordeaux",
    "timestamp": 1747400109025,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "403573f7-39ac-4049-b1cd-404c3596654c",
    "question": "Quiz Question 1: Which mountain range is found in France?",
    "response": "Answer: 4, Feedback: That's not correct. The correct answer is: The Alps",
    "timestamp": 1747400108525,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "d104b8dc-41f2-45d7-acee-28b614b071ef",
    "question": "What type of quiz would you like to take?",
    "response": "4",
    "timestamp": 1747400107587,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "thanks",
    "id": "c0d5fd1c-73c4-451d-96de-ffb6824f40db",
    "question": "thank you",
    "response": "You're welcome! Would you like to try a quiz or Changing Settings?",
    "timestamp": 1747400102808,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "d2e07e8d-f7b8-49f3-ae29-2bf29637f540",
    "question": "Quiz Question 5: Which sea borders the south of France?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747400097895,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "b6b728bd-7be4-47a9-9c9f-a03d9ebcea54",
    "question": "Quiz Question 4: Which mountain range is found in France?",
    "response": "Answer: aa, Feedback: That's not correct. The correct answer is: The Alps",
    "timestamp": 1747400096936,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "d4a66419-d853-4e30-a275-11223bd03ae3",
    "question": "Quiz Question 3: Which French region is known for its wine production?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747400094373,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "8f21b370-4857-4ca4-a957-51e032e85efd",
    "question": "Quiz Question 2: Which is the longest river in France?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747400092143,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "a634fb61-c162-4e86-bafd-7e651db1bfe5",
    "question": "Quiz Question 1: Which is NOT a neighboring country of France?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747400090650,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "d82e94c3-b646-46b6-b1da-6f24249baff0",
    "question": "What type of quiz would you like to take?",
    "response": "4",
    "timestamp": 1747400087676,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "thanks",
    "id": "1aba6251-fc0e-41ca-a576-8b2ea000ff6d",
    "question": "thank you so much",
    "response": "You're welcome! Would you like to try a quiz or Changing Settings?",
    "timestamp": 1747400055011,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "thanks",
    "id": "dc8c7b80-28fb-4e0f-b17e-bfb25b6c24b8",
    "question": "thank you",
    "response": "You're welcome! Would you like to try a quiz or Changing Settings?",
    "timestamp": 1747400048794,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "2f646763-3f10-4b09-a12d-9a69cd5092ef",
    "question": "thank you so much",
    "response": "Started a MCQ quiz",
    "timestamp": 1747399797622,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "65ba8ca7-74d3-444d-8f5c-2d04357c31fa",
    "question": "exit quiz",
    "response": "Exited quiz mode",
    "timestamp": 1747399792194,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "74538fb2-4522-4336-8e63-ce42b008d040",
    "question": "thank you so much",
    "response": "Started a MCQ quiz",
    "timestamp": 1747399762405,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "4d596dea-0295-4783-90a5-cb1393728cf4",
    "question": "Quiz Question 5: Which preposition completes: 'Je vais ___ Paris'?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747399756847,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "d36027f2-5054-45b1-8b67-0d93f2d06da0",
    "question": "Quiz Question 4: Which preposition completes: 'Je viens ___ Canada'?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747399756008,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "7ad7cfb7-eba1-40d1-8959-1b5a75381a08",
    "question": "Quiz Question 3: Which preposition completes: 'Le livre est ___ la table'?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747399755548,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "f9425d56-d7ec-4ba3-9f63-caedc07121ed",
    "question": "Quiz Question 2: Which preposition completes: 'Je voyage ___ avion'?",
    "response": "Answer: , Feedback: You didn't provide an answer. The correct answer is: en",
    "timestamp": 1747399754961,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "a6f9e257-d785-47f4-bf59-1cf5fd39d463",
    "question": "Quiz Question 1: Which preposition completes: 'Je vais ___ France'?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747399754755,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "b63860f9-fc7c-4e5c-9138-eb6ad5d7e8a9",
    "question": "grmmar",
    "response": "Started a Grammar quiz",
    "timestamp": 1747399752034,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "language_question",
    "id": "25efd927-ed21-4215-a6d0-b4620a37b85b",
    "question": "hi",
    "response": "Hello, mazen! I'm your Language Learning Bot. Would you like to practice vocabulary, grammar, or start a quiz?",
    "timestamp": 1747399746571,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "d9ca6b56-4d53-4312-952c-2f291515bc45",
    "question": "What type of quiz would you like to take?",
    "response": "4",
    "timestamp": 1747340164851,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "142f689c-3dde-4901-8dfc-d4c97a25092e",
    "question": "exit quiz",
    "response": "Exited quiz mode",
    "timestamp": 1747340155754,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "515045c6-b7d5-4f8d-bb3b-59ae08b6cfd1",
    "question": "yes give me quiz",
    "response": "Started a MCQ quiz",
    "timestamp": 1747340112266,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "thanks",
    "id": "1ee4c68c-55c4-4cdc-9ef7-81595eb41854",
    "question": "thanks",
    "response": "You're welcome! Would you like to try a quiz or Changing Settings?",
    "timestamp": 1747340099300,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "e41cc5a2-0653-46c7-aa3f-f8948757fb60",
    "question": "Quiz Question 5: Which preposition completes: 'Je vais ___ France'?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747340094246,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "8c2b75b2-c420-4385-bc86-c8c1b78838ed",
    "question": "Quiz Question 4: Which preposition completes: 'Je viens ___ Canada'?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747340093788,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "9e0d5149-c62e-4ce1-9047-8566df5f4ae1",
    "question": "Quiz Question 3: Which preposition completes: 'Je voyage ___ avion'?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747340093438,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "943387cb-4e43-4d9a-bce4-607be880bab8",
    "question": "Quiz Question 2: Which preposition completes: 'Le livre est ___ la table'?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747340093043,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "bade4b61-4254-42a7-a082-6502038a0c4a",
    "question": "Quiz Question 1: Which preposition completes: 'Je vais ___ Paris'?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747340092575,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "6266d5dc-83cc-430f-8b8a-5e346609432e",
    "question": "start grammar quiz",
    "response": "Started a Grammar quiz",
    "timestamp": 1747340091462,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "2c5c3270-f435-423a-895d-96bd64889318",
    "question": "exit quiz",
    "response": "Exited quiz mode",
    "timestamp": 1747340084699,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "7112c09f-83ae-4329-9f82-b87d2cac8a3b",
    "question": "start grammar quiz",
    "response": "Started a Grammar quiz",
    "timestamp": 1747340074017,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "1e614c67-3de7-4cef-88e1-1c9dfd6f7349",
    "question": "exit quiz",
    "response": "Exited quiz mode",
    "timestamp": 1747340049517,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "deda2987-b9f0-4879-9ebc-56f002f9c629",
    "question": "Quiz Question 1: Which of these is a famous French fashion brand?",
    "response": "Answer: , Feedback: You didn't provide an answer. The correct answer is: Chanel",
    "timestamp": 1747340037750,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "2b82df88-09de-4697-9186-022215faa15c",
    "question": "give me \tquiz",
    "response": "Started a MCQ quiz",
    "timestamp": 1747340035299,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "language_question",
    "id": "ae2058fa-65db-400e-b808-fa708a89116b",
    "question": "hi",
    "response": "Hello, mazen! I'm your Language Learning Bot. Would you like to practice vocabulary, grammar, or start a quiz?",
    "timestamp": 1747340028482,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "c94d91d2-86d3-481e-b0b9-ed0d394b54fb",
    "question": "giv me grammar quiz",
    "response": "Started a Grammar quiz",
    "timestamp": 1747339961514,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "1fc8668f-73f4-476a-aba4-9ed9c2b72d06",
    "question": "exit quiz",
    "response": "Exited quiz mode",
    "timestamp": 1747339955229,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "1f3e95c1-df52-45fd-9ff8-6664eb7af77c",
    "question": "give me quiz",
    "response": "Started a MCQ quiz",
    "timestamp": 1747339911737,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "language_question",
    "id": "f15f3b31-6c7e-4439-ae8d-62198119dac7",
    "question": "hi",
    "response": "Hello, mazen! I'm your Language Learning Bot. Would you like to practice vocabulary, grammar, or start a quiz?",
    "timestamp": 1747339905499,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "ccbb1d30-27f5-49ef-a3b3-4c91d946bdf9",
    "question": "exit quiz",
    "response": "Exited quiz mode",
    "timestamp": 1747339904012,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "8421ac26-d709-40c3-8de5-476982a7ee4a",
    "question": "learn me a quiz",
    "response": "Started a MCQ quiz",
    "timestamp": 1747339893624,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "ca0ff968-d30e-471f-b6ab-fd004743359d",
    "question": "exit quiz",
    "response": "Exited quiz mode",
    "timestamp": 1747339835989,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "890cf5c0-5a76-46b4-af1e-5769ba930492",
    "question": "give me quiz",
    "response": "Started a MCQ quiz",
    "timestamp": 1747339824901,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "cff4edbb-520b-439b-9023-4df468dd48d8",
    "question": "exit quiz",
    "response": "Exited quiz mode",
    "timestamp": 1747339820034,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "0c720b6f-bda9-4d03-8cb7-b4a8315f6d2e",
    "question": "Quiz Question 1: What is the currency used in France?",
    "response": "Answer: give me mcq quiz, Feedback: That's not correct. The correct answer is: Euro",
    "timestamp": 1747339815269,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "52228e52-a43f-4bff-83bf-af00432a87d5",
    "question": "give me quiz",
    "response": "Started a MCQ quiz",
    "timestamp": 1747339803702,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "language_question",
    "id": "1cb0db0e-ce02-4ebf-8ee2-92a96783bd07",
    "question": "hi",
    "response": "Hello, mazen! I'm your Language Learning Bot. Would you like to practice vocabulary, grammar, or start a quiz?",
    "timestamp": 1747339738342,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "language_question",
    "id": "a1f396f3-5ebc-4294-a4a8-87599354009c",
    "question": "hi",
    "response": "Hello, mazen! I'm your Language Learning Bot. Would you like to practice vocabulary, grammar, or start a quiz?",
    "timestamp": 1747339733597,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "unknown",
    "id": "786cb7f6-fb47-4534-aae2-9b9875ad7c0e",
    "question": "hello",
    "response": "Hello, mazen! I'm your Language Learning Bot. Would you like to practice vocabulary, grammar, or start a quiz?",
    "timestamp": 1747339729835,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "language_question",
    "id": "47f8c4d8-5516-4f20-92c2-e78cadbae085",
    "question": "hi",
    "response": "What would you like to know about language learning? I can help with vocabulary, grammar, pronunciation, and more.",
    "timestamp": 1747339597190,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "unknown",
    "id": "998c3eca-0310-4a8a-a8ab-918df388b5b4",
    "question": "hello",
    "response": "I'm not sure I understand. Try asking about quizzes, changing settings.",
    "timestamp": 1747339463329,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "unknown",
    "id": "d7bef17e-d42b-4d5c-a1dc-98a86fc8ac20",
    "question": "hello",
    "response": "I'm not sure I understand. Try asking about quizzes, changing settings.",
    "timestamp": 1747339297529,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "language_question",
    "id": "0a4bb897-6fb7-4b84-9f17-d5d46321f5a8",
    "question": "hi",
    "response": "What would you like to know about language learning? I can help with vocabulary, grammar, pronunciation, and more.",
    "timestamp": 1747339289859,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "unknown",
    "id": "f68f835a-1df0-4886-82fd-a95979566511",
    "question": "hello",
    "response": "I'm not sure I understand. Try asking about quizzes, changing settings.",
    "timestamp": 1747339225886,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "287f96e3-4a13-426a-b8da-f8f77675bdcb",
    "question": "exit quiz",
    "response": "Exited quiz mode",
    "timestamp": 1747339215952,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "48c16be5-3fc0-4fab-ad02-595514af20f8",
    "question": "learn me mcq",
    "response": "Started a MCQ quiz",
    "timestamp": 1747339212428,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "03572f23-099b-4fbe-aa62-6536e6f3b1f7",
    "question": "exit quiz",
    "response": "Exited quiz mode",
    "timestamp": 1747339207877,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "d87416c7-5839-4179-bbe9-f05dc876c927",
    "question": "give mcq quiz",
    "response": "Started a MCQ quiz",
    "timestamp": 1747339202891,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "language_question",
    "id": "684f3c74-adb2-4bd7-b6e4-58baa699c45c",
    "question": "hi",
    "response": "What would you like to know about language learning? I can help with vocabulary, grammar, pronunciation, and more.",
    "timestamp": 1747339196966,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "help",
    "id": "4c011a29-ed37-470b-8977-141a31690390",
    "question": "give me",
    "response": "Quel type de quiz souhaitez-vous passer ? Nous proposons :\n1. Vocabulaire - Testez votre connaissance des mots\n2. Grammaire - Pratiquez les règles de langue\n3. Traduction - Traduisez entre les langues\n4. Choix multiple (MCQ) - Questions générales sur la langue\n\nVeuillez taper le numéro (1-4) ou le nom du quiz que vous souhaitez passer.",
    "timestamp": 1747339050465,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz_request",
    "id": "44bd885d-156c-4967-8377-edacc1bbec2d",
    "question": "give me grammar quiz",
    "response": "Quel type de quiz souhaitez-vous passer ? Nous proposons :\n1. Vocabulaire - Testez votre connaissance des mots\n2. Grammaire - Pratiquez les règles de langue\n3. Traduction - Traduisez entre les langues\n4. Choix multiple (MCQ) - Questions générales sur la langue\n\nVeuillez taper le numéro (1-4) ou le nom du quiz que vous souhaitez passer.",
    "timestamp": 1747338887310,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "language_question",
    "id": "bdd02512-6a86-4075-9dc4-3586fcf44d06",
    "question": "hi",
    "response": "What would you like to know about language learning? I can help with vocabulary, grammar, pronunciation, and more.",
    "timestamp": 1747338875124,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz_request",
    "id": "fd8e5f8a-e52a-4499-8928-e52ec320103f",
    "question": "give me mcq quiz",
    "response": "Quel type de quiz souhaitez-vous passer ? Nous proposons :\n1. Vocabulaire - Testez votre connaissance des mots\n2. Grammaire - Pratiquez les règles de langue\n3. Traduction - Traduisez entre les langues\n4. Choix multiple (MCQ) - Questions générales sur la langue\n\nVeuillez taper le numéro (1-4) ou le nom du quiz que vous souhaitez passer.",
    "timestamp": 1747338587476,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz_request",
    "id": "593431f3-79c7-4dfd-bda3-060d2f7e5260",
    "question": "give me quiz",
    "response": "Quel type de quiz souhaitez-vous passer ? Nous proposons :\n1. Vocabulaire - Testez votre connaissance des mots\n2. Grammaire - Pratiquez les règles de langue\n3. Traduction - Traduisez entre les langues\n4. Choix multiple (MCQ) - Questions générales sur la langue\n\nVeuillez taper le numéro (1-4) ou le nom du quiz que vous souhaitez passer.",
    "timestamp": 1747338563088,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "71dbc0bd-04eb-4978-a3a2-002abf5d29bb",
    "question": "exit quiz",
    "response": "Exited quiz mode",
    "timestamp": 1747338555329,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "488ab523-0187-4d33-92ed-329c2c178985",
    "question": "grammar",
    "response": "Started a Grammar quiz",
    "timestamp": 1747338548471,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "language_question",
    "id": "d7d7dc26-b941-42ec-a123-dfd29cbfdd4f",
    "question": "hi",
    "response": "What would you like to know about language learning? I can help with vocabulary, grammar, pronunciation, and more.",
    "timestamp": 1747338544558,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "07d01967-6294-4781-a606-09c9a64ebe00",
    "question": "exit quiz",
    "response": "Exited quiz mode",
    "timestamp": 1747338543194,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "4439e687-84c8-43f5-9094-781a2fc242f8",
    "question": "3",
    "response": "Started a Translation quiz",
    "timestamp": 1747338526429,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz_request",
    "id": "4dfef12f-5aa2-48c3-ab94-b38b0c8ef415",
    "question": "give me a mcq quiz",
    "response": "Quel type de quiz souhaitez-vous passer ? Nous proposons :\n1. Vocabulaire - Testez votre connaissance des mots\n2. Grammaire - Pratiquez les règles de langue\n3. Traduction - Traduisez entre les langues\n4. Choix multiple (MCQ) - Questions générales sur la langue\n\nVeuillez taper le numéro (1-4) ou le nom du quiz que vous souhaitez passer.",
    "timestamp": 1747338521310,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "bc33552b-a85c-42b3-850a-4cccdbdb13f4",
    "question": "exit quiz",
    "response": "Exited quiz mode",
    "timestamp": 1747338510853,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "9c4b1595-b43a-4e01-bda6-f17acb056a4c",
    "question": "2",
    "response": "Started a Grammar quiz",
    "timestamp": 1747338504992,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz_request",
    "id": "780121a3-0817-44c6-adad-166b8fb64b14",
    "question": "give me a quiz",
    "response": "Quel type de quiz souhaitez-vous passer ? Nous proposons :\n1. Vocabulaire - Testez votre connaissance des mots\n2. Grammaire - Pratiquez les règles de langue\n3. Traduction - Traduisez entre les langues\n4. Choix multiple (MCQ) - Questions générales sur la langue\n\nVeuillez taper le numéro (1-4) ou le nom du quiz que vous souhaitez passer.",
    "timestamp": 1747338503992,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "52039fba-30c8-44c4-ad2c-28fb51d8ba4a",
    "question": "exit quiz",
    "response": "Exited quiz mode",
    "timestamp": 1747338493137,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "558872be-f5b6-4a83-95bf-d9d7a6ecf807",
    "question": "2",
    "response": "Started a Grammar quiz",
    "timestamp": 1747338489652,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz_request",
    "id": "a671f8d3-50aa-4506-aa00-46ab67c8aebc",
    "question": "learn me a quiz",
    "response": "Quel type de quiz souhaitez-vous passer ? Nous proposons :\n1. Vocabulaire - Testez votre connaissance des mots\n2. Grammaire - Pratiquez les règles de langue\n3. Traduction - Traduisez entre les langues\n4. Choix multiple (MCQ) - Questions générales sur la langue\n\nVeuillez taper le numéro (1-4) ou le nom du quiz que vous souhaitez passer.",
    "timestamp": 1747338488085,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "f8ab048a-3b0a-4ed5-bc76-a6692b749953",
    "question": "exit quiz",
    "response": "Exited quiz mode",
    "timestamp": 1747338455845,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "3397ebc8-2725-4b66-b1cf-3c41d5f7c7d3",
    "question": "Quiz Question 1: What is the correct conjugation of 'être' for 'je'?",
    "response": "Answer: exit quiz please, Feedback: That's not correct. The correct answer is: suis",
    "timestamp": 1747338451205,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "841e56be-f989-4f71-8cea-31648387d127",
    "question": "2",
    "response": "Started a Grammar quiz",
    "timestamp": 1747338442406,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz_request",
    "id": "db055379-8444-4d72-a338-8e4f914af03c",
    "question": "start a grammar quiz",
    "response": "Quel type de quiz souhaitez-vous passer ? Nous proposons :\n1. Vocabulaire - Testez votre connaissance des mots\n2. Grammaire - Pratiquez les règles de langue\n3. Traduction - Traduisez entre les langues\n4. Choix multiple (MCQ) - Questions générales sur la langue\n\nVeuillez taper le numéro (1-4) ou le nom du quiz que vous souhaitez passer.",
    "timestamp": 1747338432672,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "language_question",
    "id": "f656dda7-0490-4abf-bbe8-1dbdf3b1b586",
    "question": "hi",
    "response": "What would you like to know about language learning? I can help with vocabulary, grammar, pronunciation, and more.",
    "timestamp": 1747338423460,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "language_selection",
    "id": "3b486751-450c-4397-83a9-428c3787d508",
    "question": "\\i want to learn french",
    "response": "Great! I'll help you learn french. Would you like to take a quiz to practice?",
    "timestamp": 1747338177378,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "33ab6584-57ba-419f-99fb-9cec8d04c4a9",
    "question": "exit quiz",
    "response": "Exited quiz mode",
    "timestamp": 1747338120279,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "adc90c06-154d-4c3c-9e9a-9bd1115155ff",
    "question": "Quiz Question 1: Which of these is a famous French fashion brand?",
    "response": "Answer: exit qioz, Feedback: That's not correct. The correct answer is: Chanel",
    "timestamp": 1747338117225,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "5f555689-b26d-4c84-94a7-0fd23398ed15",
    "question": "quiz",
    "response": "Started a new quiz session",
    "timestamp": 1747338113521,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "d9e8ee42-2fce-41dd-bd97-471194e8e014",
    "question": "What type of quiz would you like to take?",
    "response": "mcq",
    "timestamp": 1747338113230,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz_request",
    "id": "9a2f952f-bf97-4780-9312-2ccd6e0abac4",
    "question": "give me quiz grammar",
    "response": "Starting a grammar quiz...\n\nHere's your first question:\n[Quiz content for grammar will be generated here]",
    "timestamp": 1747338089845,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "language_question",
    "id": "7e6ad5b9-4243-465f-942e-829950e2932e",
    "question": "hi",
    "response": "What would you like to know about language learning? I can help with vocabulary, grammar, pronunciation, and more.",
    "timestamp": 1747338076575,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz_request",
    "id": "4f52d883-011e-46af-b95a-4cd2074a03d9",
    "question": "learn me a quiz",
    "response": "I'd be happy to start a quiz! What type would you prefer? We offer:\n1. Vocabulary - Test your word knowledge\n2. Grammar - Practice language rules\n3. Translation - Translate between languages\n4. Multiple Choice (MCQ) - General language questions\n\nPlease type the number (1-4) or name of the quiz you'd like to take.",
    "timestamp": 1747338071714,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "unknown",
    "id": "0e24f570-e17c-42c3-acba-5049fa726883",
    "question": "4",
    "response": "I'm not sure I understand. Try asking about quizzes, changing settings.",
    "timestamp": 1747338065948,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz_request",
    "id": "8ac1fd08-c60d-43a2-9e5e-fc2c7475d781",
    "question": "iwant  quz",
    "response": "I'd be happy to start a quiz! What type would you prefer? We offer:\n1. Vocabulary - Test your word knowledge\n2. Grammar - Practice language rules\n3. Translation - Translate between languages\n4. Multiple Choice (MCQ) - General language questions\n\nPlease type the number (1-4) or name of the quiz you'd like to take.",
    "timestamp": 1747338063822,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "language_question",
    "id": "e6a82d2e-4175-4f00-9e9f-e035020afe4b",
    "question": "hi",
    "response": "What would you like to know about language learning? I can help with vocabulary, grammar, pronunciation, and more.",
    "timestamp": 1747337873748,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "unknown",
    "id": "c1bfa60c-b2a0-4031-8416-0016c4c1f6a8",
    "question": "4",
    "response": "I'm not sure I understand. Try asking about quizzes, changing settings.",
    "timestamp": 1747337682432,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz_request",
    "id": "13031d24-b2ac-4e3a-87c2-f11fd5c99278",
    "question": "give me quiz please",
    "response": "I'd be happy to start a quiz! What type would you prefer? We offer:\n1. Vocabulary - Test your word knowledge\n2. Grammar - Practice language rules\n3. Translation - Translate between languages\n4. Multiple Choice (MCQ) - General language questions\n\nPlease type the number (1-4) or name of the quiz you'd like to take.",
    "timestamp": 1747337678634,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "unknown",
    "id": "302c8bb3-d763-4b29-96d2-dc0cd9f828bf",
    "question": "hello",
    "response": "I'm not sure I understand. Try asking about quizzes, changing settings.",
    "timestamp": 1747337632396,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "language_question",
    "id": "69bbced5-488c-48a8-80f9-9d139a1b330b",
    "question": "hi",
    "response": "What would you like to know about language learning? I can help with vocabulary, grammar, pronunciation, and more.",
    "timestamp": 1747337629892,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "unknown",
    "id": "4bfd482f-b9c1-4417-9af8-1444cf3cd510",
    "question": "2",
    "response": "I'm not sure I understand. Try asking about quizzes, changing settings.",
    "timestamp": 1747335490514,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "unknown",
    "id": "098851c3-d1d4-4aed-9271-128546d18118",
    "question": "2",
    "response": "I'm not sure I understand. Try asking about quizzes, changing settings.",
    "timestamp": 1747335490315,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "unknown",
    "id": "174a4863-c76a-4739-9c61-78007545ffec",
    "question": "2",
    "response": "I'm not sure I understand. Try asking about quizzes, changing settings.",
    "timestamp": 1747335490120,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "unknown",
    "id": "d3e7b136-801f-46c5-9064-86ec41d080f6",
    "question": "2",
    "response": "I'm not sure I understand. Try asking about quizzes, changing settings.",
    "timestamp": 1747335489949,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "unknown",
    "id": "54b34ba8-8279-45c9-acb2-61eacbd0aa4d",
    "question": "2",
    "response": "I'm not sure I understand. Try asking about quizzes, changing settings.",
    "timestamp": 1747335489749,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "unknown",
    "id": "257a9cfb-b8c9-469e-b727-f6cfe4b34522",
    "question": "2",
    "response": "I'm not sure I understand. Try asking about quizzes, changing settings.",
    "timestamp": 1747335489567,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "unknown",
    "id": "668069fc-66df-4905-8f1a-09970831a03e",
    "question": "2",
    "response": "I'm not sure I understand. Try asking about quizzes, changing settings.",
    "timestamp": 1747335489383,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "unknown",
    "id": "8a21e01e-e5d0-4b4d-bc9c-a8368f480404",
    "question": "2",
    "response": "I'm not sure I understand. Try asking about quizzes, changing settings.",
    "timestamp": 1747335489201,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "unknown",
    "id": "cad402b1-f5cc-445f-8fab-dd80413babd5",
    "question": "2",
    "response": "I'm not sure I understand. Try asking about quizzes, changing settings.",
    "timestamp": 1747335488859,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "unknown",
    "id": "a907a443-3c21-4b83-9b45-8db0eb17935f",
    "question": "2",
    "response": "I'm not sure I understand. Try asking about quizzes, changing settings.",
    "timestamp": 1747335488656,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "unknown",
    "id": "264d7bee-d779-4b27-be26-f596f19afac6",
    "question": "2",
    "response": "I'm not sure I understand. Try asking about quizzes, changing settings.",
    "timestamp": 1747335488467,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "unknown",
    "id": "083720cb-10a6-4bd1-965c-65a5e447af96",
    "question": "2",
    "response": "I'm not sure I understand. Try asking about quizzes, changing settings.",
    "timestamp": 1747335488297,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "unknown",
    "id": "dcbf3eb2-fab9-4378-8f59-ffabc8abc322",
    "question": "2",
    "response": "I'm not sure I understand. Try asking about quizzes, changing settings.",
    "timestamp": 1747335487870,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "unknown",
    "id": "4dfc725d-75f7-458f-96da-88cbb2ba6306",
    "question": "2",
    "response": "I'm not sure I understand. Try asking about quizzes, changing settings.",
    "timestamp": 1747335487204,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "unknown",
    "id": "475ed3ef-6fac-4195-a263-67eba12dcc05",
    "question": "2",
    "response": "I'm not sure I understand. Try asking about quizzes, changing settings.",
    "timestamp": 1747335487010,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "unknown",
    "id": "8b7653ca-23af-46d3-bf5c-22e5e6dc4d22",
    "question": "2",
    "response": "I'm not sure I understand. Try asking about quizzes, changing settings.",
    "timestamp": 1747335486831,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "unknown",
    "id": "1379cb00-1356-4bf1-b437-40c52037d56a",
    "question": "2",
    "response": "I'm not sure I understand. Try asking about quizzes, changing settings.",
    "timestamp": 1747335486648,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "unknown",
    "id": "2e0a8247-2379-4743-9c73-c8cf7f774eb4",
    "question": "2",
    "response": "I'm not sure I understand. Try asking about quizzes, changing settings.",
    "timestamp": 1747335486456,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "unknown",
    "id": "82e2c66d-43cf-48f5-8ec1-e6bc59789dc9",
    "question": "",
    "response": "I'm not sure I understand. Try asking about quizzes, changing settings.",
    "timestamp": 1747335486275,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "unknown",
    "id": "a11654cc-eb14-4a1b-94f3-bbec6b66a91b",
    "question": "2",
    "response": "I'm not sure I understand. Try asking about quizzes, changing settings.",
    "timestamp": 1747335486175,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "unknown",
    "id": "d53bd5e3-f522-4aea-8491-c7bf76f7c1ea",
    "question": "2",
    "response": "I'm not sure I understand. Try asking about quizzes, changing settings.",
    "timestamp": 1747335486015,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "unknown",
    "id": "6f60283c-c398-4c8f-8fbd-c9cc85e440d3",
    "question": "2",
    "response": "I'm not sure I understand. Try asking about quizzes, changing settings.",
    "timestamp": 1747335485855,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "unknown",
    "id": "9731a444-7b51-4fae-a3c6-00d1566acc9a",
    "question": "2",
    "response": "I'm not sure I understand. Try asking about quizzes, changing settings.",
    "timestamp": 1747335485693,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "unknown",
    "id": "bfee3213-cd90-4331-a6ee-4f9f0c07e1cf",
    "question": "2",
    "response": "I'm not sure I understand. Try asking about quizzes, changing settings.",
    "timestamp": 1747335485188,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "unknown",
    "id": "5449cf92-897a-4061-a0fa-254fd70fe338",
    "question": "aneeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeekkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkk",
    "response": "I'm not sure I understand. Try asking about quizzes, changing settings.",
    "timestamp": 1747335416277,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "unknown",
    "id": "f1cec018-a437-4131-a9dd-30b2be06da57",
    "question": "zebiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiii",
    "response": "I'm not sure I understand. Try asking about quizzes, changing settings.",
    "timestamp": 1747335410428,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "unknown",
    "id": "ed39f7d5-e24a-4788-8f90-f0c1f0083c5d",
    "question": "zebiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiii",
    "response": "I'm not sure I understand. Try asking about quizzes, changing settings.",
    "timestamp": 1747335404205,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "unknown",
    "id": "85044b0a-4128-4307-9e6c-e95019c4dadd",
    "question": "",
    "response": "I'm not sure I understand. Try asking about quizzes, changing settings.",
    "timestamp": 1747335375305,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "unknown",
    "id": "7541c08d-4e92-41d5-bc4e-c360b19e2a67",
    "question": "hello",
    "response": "I'm not sure I understand. Try asking about quizzes, changing settings.",
    "timestamp": 1747335154305,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "language_question",
    "id": "33ad832a-2ef1-45ca-b341-bf42bf7f7e36",
    "question": "hi",
    "response": "What would you like to know about language learning? I can help with vocabulary, grammar, pronunciation, and more.",
    "timestamp": 1747335151653,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "unknown",
    "id": "cea22109-2cbd-455f-9c9a-cd8c124b0b34",
    "question": "hello",
    "response": "I'm not sure I understand. Try asking about quizzes, changing settings.",
    "timestamp": 1747334649843,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "language_question",
    "id": "d156370f-4218-4b34-afd5-9bf63a3ceaa2",
    "question": "hi",
    "response": "What would you like to know about language learning? I can help with vocabulary, grammar, pronunciation, and more.",
    "timestamp": 1747334645861,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "unknown",
    "id": "c60b5f0f-97cb-48b6-8d38-5f4672f63558",
    "question": "5",
    "response": "I'm not sure I understand. Try asking about quizzes, changing settings.",
    "timestamp": 1747334572142,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz_request",
    "id": "c00558ad-ab2c-4179-9d6e-9e0a37cfe520",
    "question": "give me quiz",
    "response": "I'd be happy to start a quiz! What type would you prefer? We offer:\n1. Vocabulary - Test your word knowledge\n2. Grammar - Practice language rules\n3. Translation - Translate between languages\n4. Multiple Choice (MCQ) - General language questions\n5. Correction - Fix language mistakes\n\nPlease type the number (1-5) or name of the quiz you'd like to take.",
    "timestamp": 1747334568981,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "unknown",
    "id": "fdf1a74e-3634-489c-a353-a7a868342a86",
    "question": "system",
    "response": "I'm not sure I understand. Try asking about quizzes, changing settings.",
    "timestamp": 1747334563718,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "unknown",
    "id": "ebaeb2c0-14c9-4ea4-a450-597090ec8501",
    "question": "hello",
    "response": "I'm not sure I understand. Try asking about quizzes, changing settings.",
    "timestamp": 1747334319958,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "language_question",
    "id": "b576e611-5d37-46c0-9ba8-7f482d07728e",
    "question": "hi",
    "response": "What would you like to know about language learning? I can help with vocabulary, grammar, pronunciation, and more.",
    "timestamp": 1747334317151,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "language_question",
    "id": "78eaa2f7-e5bf-4a98-9a97-3617b4f90543",
    "question": "hi",
    "response": "What would you like to know about language learning? I can help with vocabulary, grammar, pronunciation, and more.",
    "timestamp": 1747334157755,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "unknown",
    "id": "5d47b268-c58e-4568-a02d-117b0d678639",
    "question": "hello",
    "response": "I'm not sure I understand. Try asking about quizzes, changing settings.",
    "timestamp": 1747334153268,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "unknown",
    "id": "fb32657a-2f83-4aaf-92dc-89d837b8f343",
    "question": "2",
    "response": "I'm not sure I understand. Try asking about quizzes, changing settings.",
    "timestamp": 1747334143199,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "system",
    "id": "0b0ebdfd-b29f-4edc-8f50-f26f8762c7a8",
    "question": "help",
    "response": "\nAvailable commands:\n1. chat - Start a conversation\n2. quiz - Take a quiz\n3. history - View your learning history\n4. preferences - Set your language preferences\n5. help - Show this help message\n6. logout - Log out\n7. exit - Exit the application\n",
    "timestamp": 1747334141167,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "language_question",
    "id": "22b32fbd-ff19-4254-8578-56b321a64405",
    "question": "hi",
    "response": "What would you like to know about language learning? I can help with vocabulary, grammar, pronunciation, and more.",
    "timestamp": 1747333811282,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "help",
    "id": "55adc16f-c2dc-4943-a626-8d29a53bbb25",
    "question": "give me",
    "response": "I'm here to help you learn languages! You can:\n- Start a quiz by typing 'quiz'\n- Change settings with 'settings'\n- View your progress with 'analytics'\n- Ask language questions directly\n- Type 'logout' to sign out",
    "timestamp": 1747333658035,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "unknown",
    "id": "d905ac5e-451a-4ab6-8d1a-fb64f7d6f1b7",
    "question": "",
    "response": "I'm not sure I understand. Try asking about quizzes, changing settings.",
    "timestamp": 1747333632707,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "unknown",
    "id": "dd158918-ceb3-458c-85d9-2bd3c9f3ae2f",
    "question": "not working",
    "response": "I'm not sure I understand. Try asking about quizzes, changing settings.",
    "timestamp": 1747333632460,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "language_question",
    "id": "be04e3f4-ae1c-4ea8-988d-6dde155bf292",
    "question": "i want to learn mcq",
    "response": "What would you like to know about language learning? I can help with vocabulary, grammar, pronunciation, and more.",
    "timestamp": 1747333611188,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "help",
    "id": "fc0342a2-0bd1-4d0c-bc6c-3bc2102291f2",
    "question": "give me grammar quiz",
    "response": "I'm here to help you learn languages! You can:\n- Start a quiz by typing 'quiz'\n- Change settings with 'settings'\n- View your progress with 'analytics'\n- Ask language questions directly\n- Type 'logout' to sign out",
    "timestamp": 1747333589786,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "language_question",
    "id": "6d3dbc4d-2c89-4064-9ae8-8b7495ae4bd9",
    "question": "a",
    "response": "What would you like to know about language learning? I can help with vocabulary, grammar, pronunciation, and more.",
    "timestamp": 1747215555472,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "language_question",
    "id": "dadf1973-752e-4813-9dc8-6d2af3e4a37a",
    "question": "a",
    "response": "What would you like to know about language learning? I can help with vocabulary, grammar, pronunciation, and more.",
    "timestamp": 1747215555278,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "language_question",
    "id": "0b45f170-cfdd-4e31-9a04-bb8d048844f9",
    "question": "a",
    "response": "What would you like to know about language learning? I can help with vocabulary, grammar, pronunciation, and more.",
    "timestamp": 1747215555127,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "language_question",
    "id": "04cc7f7c-bce8-4862-aa49-d41b4609e702",
    "question": "a",
    "response": "What would you like to know about language learning? I can help with vocabulary, grammar, pronunciation, and more.",
    "timestamp": 1747215554957,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "language_question",
    "id": "46c64663-d64c-4f16-8e43-4ea5c863947f",
    "question": "a",
    "response": "What would you like to know about language learning? I can help with vocabulary, grammar, pronunciation, and more.",
    "timestamp": 1747215554795,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "language_question",
    "id": "ea54b265-4d9d-4ad0-bf47-74dabdebd5ce",
    "question": "a",
    "response": "What would you like to know about language learning? I can help with vocabulary, grammar, pronunciation, and more.",
    "timestamp": 1747215554415,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "language_question",
    "id": "b08c16b6-5b7f-42bb-adb2-d51cff4e7b6d",
    "question": "a",
    "response": "What would you like to know about language learning? I can help with vocabulary, grammar, pronunciation, and more.",
    "timestamp": 1747215553804,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "76528cba-b171-4c7b-b71f-f8712a81f470",
    "question": "Quiz Question 5: Which city is the capital of France?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747215553634,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "ed21c041-ec3d-4626-b9b0-7c88aa0d141a",
    "question": "Quiz Question 4: Which of these is a traditional French cheese?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747215553456,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "fd0bd1f2-a52b-4fea-af0e-9c406d9a99cb",
    "question": "Quiz Question 3: What colors are on the French flag?",
    "response": "Answer: , Feedback: You didn't provide an answer. The correct answer is: Blue, white, and red",
    "timestamp": 1747215553235,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "f0e76dee-d2f8-46cb-945f-ca4e1ee33cfc",
    "question": "Quiz Question 2: Which French dish consists of snails cooked with garlic and butter?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747215553012,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "da87e878-4f0d-4311-bc79-c4566a284b5e",
    "question": "Quiz Question 1: Which famous museum is located in Paris?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747215552814,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "839f94ad-35e0-4c38-89ab-af936d42792c",
    "question": "quiz",
    "response": "Started a new quiz session",
    "timestamp": 1747215552468,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "0332ffea-8e78-42bf-b87f-579ca8fbc1f1",
    "question": "What type of quiz would you like to take?",
    "response": "mcq",
    "timestamp": 1747215552463,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "language_question",
    "id": "89ece8f7-c371-4c61-b2be-c4a2cd0b4fcc",
    "question": "a",
    "response": "What would you like to know about language learning? I can help with vocabulary, grammar, pronunciation, and more.",
    "timestamp": 1747215546984,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "b92efcfd-347d-47f1-b9a7-86a1fd0cb86b",
    "question": "Quiz Question 5: Which article is correct: ___ ami",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747215546521,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "390356f2-3ce4-4c8c-a8a6-e11b351ba7c8",
    "question": "Quiz Question 4: Which is the correct feminine form of 'un ami'?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747215545959,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "e10ccfed-877b-444a-883a-a4c287189bd2",
    "question": "Quiz Question 3: Which is the correct plural form of 'un animal'?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747215545469,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "ab706106-c720-4790-8f95-04687973a5cc",
    "question": "Quiz Question 2: Which article is correct: ___ livre",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747215545237,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "be976b92-8b54-4fe3-9e5b-303fd88c4068",
    "question": "Quiz Question 1: Which article is correct: ___ voiture",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747215545013,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "468365f2-ec29-447e-84f4-40aea3951d7d",
    "question": "quiz",
    "response": "Started a new quiz session",
    "timestamp": 1747215543461,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "language_question",
    "id": "d8606d90-8e30-4deb-9925-8b5831528264",
    "question": "hi",
    "response": "What would you like to know about language learning? I can help with vocabulary, grammar, pronunciation, and more.",
    "timestamp": 1747215539122,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "language_question",
    "id": "e9cbfa5f-4370-4e32-8fa4-977c6dfd5352",
    "question": "a",
    "response": "What would you like to know about language learning? I can help with vocabulary, grammar, pronunciation, and more.",
    "timestamp": 1747215530929,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "language_question",
    "id": "6ecd618c-3aaa-4b5d-ae6f-c152dc7234f1",
    "question": "a",
    "response": "What would you like to know about language learning? I can help with vocabulary, grammar, pronunciation, and more.",
    "timestamp": 1747215528295,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "language_question",
    "id": "889b22c3-1d82-46a6-9b41-de57c5018db1",
    "question": "a",
    "response": "What would you like to know about language learning? I can help with vocabulary, grammar, pronunciation, and more.",
    "timestamp": 1747215527624,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "language_question",
    "id": "d86f7ed6-6dbf-4e0d-bf4d-0049dd04d056",
    "question": "a",
    "response": "What would you like to know about language learning? I can help with vocabulary, grammar, pronunciation, and more.",
    "timestamp": 1747215526143,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "127809b1-6799-452f-9187-a86593a5a2e2",
    "question": "Quiz Question 5: What is the typical French greeting?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747215525458,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "62f41fc6-76b7-4945-b266-f72202cb4547",
    "question": "Quiz Question 4: Which of these is a famous French fashion brand?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747215525099,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "5cb0ee7d-6946-49f6-825a-c5782a3608ad",
    "question": "Quiz Question 3: What is the currency used in France?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747215524633,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "52bde621-d416-4392-8e6a-adfd04376722",
    "question": "Quiz Question 2: What is a 'baguette'?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747215524414,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "aedbfcab-a8a1-42d3-9da7-3ddf7ee119bd",
    "question": "Quiz Question 1: What is the most widely spoken language in France?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747215524193,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "775e98d9-9ef8-4437-a6c2-446bf5789b2a",
    "question": "quiz",
    "response": "Started a new quiz session",
    "timestamp": 1747215523051,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz_request",
    "id": "9b1c8cbd-2e32-4792-a30b-42794ba4a4b0",
    "question": "quiz'",
    "response": "Would you like to start a quiz? If yes, please type 'start quiz' to begin. Types de quiz disponibles : vocabulaire, grammaire, traduction, choix multiple",
    "timestamp": 1747215513559,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "unknown",
    "id": "590b8589-b0c3-4c7e-a8e2-2b5a155ee3ad",
    "question": "i",
    "response": "I'm not sure I understand. Try asking about quizzes, changing settings.",
    "timestamp": 1747215503066,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "unknown",
    "id": "76312f54-fe08-4194-b747-510885c25bab",
    "question": "start",
    "response": "I'm not sure I understand. Try asking about quizzes, changing settings.",
    "timestamp": 1747213491844,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "language_question",
    "id": "508aa5e3-b344-4dfc-8d8b-eaea57126eb3",
    "question": "hi",
    "response": "What would you like to know about language learning? I can help with vocabulary, grammar, pronunciation, and more.",
    "timestamp": 1747213470683,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "unknown",
    "id": "1561e983-7fe7-4c76-88f8-7761eab5cf6c",
    "question": "hello",
    "response": "I'm not sure I understand. Try asking about quizzes, changing settings.",
    "timestamp": 1747213467964,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "help",
    "id": "e0fa091a-6c37-4e79-8153-71d3fd628f7b",
    "question": "give me help",
    "response": "I'm here to help you learn languages! You can:\n- Start a quiz by typing 'quiz'\n- Change settings with 'settings'\n- View your progress with 'analytics'\n- Ask language questions directly\n- Type 'logout' to sign out",
    "timestamp": 1747213450017,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "help",
    "id": "2ddb7613-9a3c-4950-a687-5bbb3fa37a69",
    "question": "give me quiz",
    "response": "I'm here to help you learn languages! You can:\n- Start a quiz by typing 'quiz'\n- Change settings with 'settings'\n- View your progress with 'analytics'\n- Ask language questions directly\n- Type 'logout' to sign out",
    "timestamp": 1747213423072,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "thanks",
    "id": "7b5d5bbb-020b-44a5-8cca-4182354ca05b",
    "question": "thanks",
    "response": "You're welcome! Would you like to try a quiz or Changing Settings?",
    "timestamp": 1747213304646,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "e7dad14f-b82b-4782-a717-b51d309846a1",
    "question": "Quiz Question 5: Which is the longest river in France?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747213300282,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "70c74364-73a9-4bc5-9b4c-4f7d47ec6247",
    "question": "Quiz Question 4: Which mountain range is found in France?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747213299767,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "12111593-a61f-40f2-a932-b9ca1d9d3a9b",
    "question": "Quiz Question 3: Which is NOT a neighboring country of France?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747213299034,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "0e42cf2c-4464-4046-9ffb-0397b6a17c8a",
    "question": "Quiz Question 2: Which French region is known for its wine production?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747213298803,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "d6ff456d-9635-420b-82f5-2a03b29a4182",
    "question": "Quiz Question 1: Which sea borders the south of France?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747213298560,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "e2fc21d8-c353-46fe-be0b-671ec6659ef3",
    "question": "quiz",
    "response": "Started a new quiz session",
    "timestamp": 1747213297472,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "language_question",
    "id": "061cc021-0feb-4aa3-9de6-1e4b8ae2c313",
    "question": "i want to learn quiz",
    "response": "What would you like to know about language learning? I can help with vocabulary, grammar, pronunciation, and more.",
    "timestamp": 1747213278305,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "unknown",
    "id": "7ce842ec-d78d-4b80-9ce6-d9dc0355f8ee",
    "question": "2",
    "response": "I'm not sure I understand. Try asking about quizzes, changing settings.",
    "timestamp": 1747213246659,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "unknown",
    "id": "be7fff4f-df73-4a02-b957-0dfe39af0381",
    "question": "hello",
    "response": "I'm not sure I understand. Try asking about quizzes, changing settings.",
    "timestamp": 1747213219046,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "help",
    "id": "95c61701-ed50-4b2e-be56-07d83426fbc0",
    "question": "give me quiz",
    "response": "I'm here to help you learn languages! You can:\n- Start a quiz by typing 'quiz'\n- Change settings with 'settings'\n- View your progress with 'analytics'\n- Ask language questions directly\n- Type 'logout' to sign out",
    "timestamp": 1747213214170,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "unknown",
    "id": "1ced38ca-5588-4e9b-984a-5572505b9b41",
    "question": "i want to take quiz",
    "response": "I'm not sure I understand. Try asking about quizzes, changing settings.",
    "timestamp": 1747213204296,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "help",
    "id": "eba7b12c-b98b-4c6c-8d3e-52619e5768e5",
    "question": "give me analytics",
    "response": "I'm here to help you learn languages! You can:\n- Start a quiz by typing 'quiz'\n- Change settings with 'settings'\n- View your progress with 'analytics'\n- Ask language questions directly\n- Type 'logout' to sign out",
    "timestamp": 1747211219527,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "system",
    "id": "a367924b-5c5f-46dd-b066-136ddb0a5744",
    "question": "analytics",
    "response": "Displayed user analytics",
    "timestamp": 1747211210013,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "language_question",
    "id": "f5c3a11e-2688-4897-8003-269dfdbb357b",
    "question": "a",
    "response": "What would you like to know about language learning? I can help with vocabulary, grammar, pronunciation, and more.",
    "timestamp": 1747211201506,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "66c8b88d-6e3b-4ce9-b07c-f75ac544ffc3",
    "question": "Quiz Question 5: What is the most widely spoken language in France?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747211200648,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "adb1b919-39f6-48df-b65c-b93e5500f818",
    "question": "Quiz Question 4: Which of these is a famous French fashion brand?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747211200075,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "cc8acf0b-6116-46fc-b7d5-1dc8f42c0b50",
    "question": "Quiz Question 3: What is a 'baguette'?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747211199680,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "81509b53-479d-4651-af13-5d36f048780b",
    "question": "Quiz Question 2: What is the currency used in France?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747211199134,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "00207142-7110-46df-8e65-ae31f5f0a609",
    "question": "Quiz Question 1: What is the typical French greeting?",
    "response": "Answer: , Feedback: You didn't provide an answer. The correct answer is: Bonjour",
    "timestamp": 1747211198339,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "add5fe27-e06b-4277-b017-b550d1381c50",
    "question": "quiz",
    "response": "Started a new quiz session",
    "timestamp": 1747211194934,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "unknown",
    "id": "dda7727d-de07-422b-9e6f-85f46550a17f",
    "question": "okay",
    "response": "I'm not sure I understand. Try asking about quizzes, changing settings.",
    "timestamp": 1747211180197,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "help",
    "id": "0b5e2ccc-d103-4254-8115-536891899c19",
    "question": "yes give me quiz",
    "response": "I'm here to help you learn languages! You can:\n- Start a quiz by typing 'quiz'\n- Change settings with 'settings'\n- View your progress with 'analytics'\n- Ask language questions directly\n- Type 'logout' to sign out",
    "timestamp": 1747211169315,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "language_question",
    "id": "074382f8-ffb3-4ec0-b4af-b3d4655277ec",
    "question": "grammer quiz",
    "response": "What would you like to know about language learning? I can help with vocabulary, grammar, pronunciation, and more.",
    "timestamp": 1747211144707,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "language_question",
    "id": "0229ca61-2684-4827-b989-f4cdfd070df4",
    "question": "i want to take the quiz again",
    "response": "What would you like to know about language learning? I can help with vocabulary, grammar, pronunciation, and more.",
    "timestamp": 1747211126534,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "system",
    "id": "351e172b-2132-4d7b-8e1b-32c99f32fe83",
    "question": "analytics",
    "response": "Displayed user analytics",
    "timestamp": 1747211118984,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "unknown",
    "id": "b7deb878-f1bc-49e2-b06e-1f74dcf03062",
    "question": "amazing",
    "response": "I'm not sure I understand. Try asking about quizzes, changing settings.",
    "timestamp": 1747211113363,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "9e184dc6-c648-4634-96e3-509c798b1651",
    "question": "Quiz Question 5: Which city is the capital of France?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747211107889,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "cc085d75-43f1-4435-93f4-53dd6d0dfeb3",
    "question": "Quiz Question 4: Which famous museum is located in Paris?",
    "response": "Answer: sdsd, Feedback: That's not correct. The correct answer is: The Louvre",
    "timestamp": 1747211104074,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "853621c9-4af7-4486-a6c9-da464a05e920",
    "question": "Quiz Question 3: Which French dish consists of snails cooked with garlic and butter?",
    "response": "Answer: Escargots, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747211102081,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "102e6f80-4487-4865-a3af-99202778b0a6",
    "question": "Quiz Question 2: Which of these is a traditional French cheese?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747211086735,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "3e9d653f-2589-423d-bd8d-32aa346dc200",
    "question": "Quiz Question 1: What colors are on the French flag?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747211084778,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "c3d7ea45-e58c-492f-91f0-0eb2f714f20a",
    "question": "quiz",
    "response": "Started a new quiz session",
    "timestamp": 1747211066584,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "unknown",
    "id": "0bb47465-a03d-4ca4-98d9-c043e8ac800a",
    "question": "start qui",
    "response": "I'm not sure I understand. Try asking about quizzes, changing settings.",
    "timestamp": 1747210989606,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "unknown",
    "id": "5c106630-5b3c-4479-96fb-9593c717e1b6",
    "question": "yes start quiz",
    "response": "I'm not sure I understand. Try asking about quizzes, changing settings.",
    "timestamp": 1747210977217,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "language_question",
    "id": "f836f5d7-3467-44c4-94d7-a5e30adf38c4",
    "question": "i want to learn grammmer",
    "response": "What would you like to know about language learning? I can help with vocabulary, grammar, pronunciation, and more.",
    "timestamp": 1747210936322,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "language_question",
    "id": "cfff28e0-1fea-41b5-a972-e967cec1cfde",
    "question": "hi",
    "response": "What would you like to know about language learning? I can help with vocabulary, grammar, pronunciation, and more.",
    "timestamp": 1747210918963,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "unknown",
    "id": "183d510b-b581-4a3c-8aa9-63d6bd83eae5",
    "question": "hello",
    "response": "I'm not sure I understand. Try asking about quizzes, changing settings.",
    "timestamp": 1747210902118,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "language_question",
    "id": "ef2ceb3b-0fdc-47f1-b499-8f72f4568503",
    "question": "hi",
    "response": "What would you like to know about language learning? I can help with vocabulary, grammar, pronunciation, and more.",
    "timestamp": 1747209755234,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "unknown",
    "id": "4fdb56d4-ff1f-4204-b5cf-b312ae849e10",
    "question": "thanks",
    "response": "I'm not sure I understand. Try asking about quizzes, changing settings.",
    "timestamp": 1747205335768,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "system",
    "id": "b310065e-6fb4-45ac-ac97-279e265f89d8",
    "question": "analytics",
    "response": "Displayed user analytics",
    "timestamp": 1747205332831,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "34db18e1-2011-4542-9827-128cda7a4ef8",
    "question": "Quiz Question 5: Which city is the capital of France?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747205326363,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "17ab087a-4be9-4347-af7a-162a515986a7",
    "question": "Quiz Question 4: Which French dish consists of snails cooked with garlic and butter?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747205325581,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "d0f05238-cf36-4f99-b866-bc43a269bc91",
    "question": "Quiz Question 3: Which famous museum is located in Paris?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747205325093,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "68245b08-7aa3-46b3-bdc7-4227d7936ee5",
    "question": "Quiz Question 2: What colors are on the French flag?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747205324593,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "53ee31b5-5501-47eb-b4ad-dd50d485e7fc",
    "question": "Quiz Question 1: Which of these is a traditional French cheese?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747205324165,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "c6a8f298-95a4-46fe-9c08-90d92db44fd5",
    "question": "quiz",
    "response": "Started a new quiz session",
    "timestamp": 1747205323830,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "ac5a55cb-036b-486b-ad0b-82c51a98f206",
    "question": "What type of quiz would you like to take?",
    "response": "mcq",
    "timestamp": 1747205323773,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "language_question",
    "id": "824da692-47f3-48b8-9bd4-63d5157103c8",
    "question": "hi",
    "response": "What would you like to know about language learning? I can help with vocabulary, grammar, pronunciation, and more.",
    "timestamp": 1747205102480,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "unknown",
    "id": "c8e2fcc0-f45d-4a1e-85c7-8aecfb57c66c",
    "question": "",
    "response": "I'm not sure I understand. Try asking about quizzes, changing settings.",
    "timestamp": 1747205022051,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "unknown",
    "id": "94c20618-d06d-458e-a6ed-7f59ece3dd49",
    "question": "",
    "response": "I'm not sure I understand. Try asking about quizzes, changing settings.",
    "timestamp": 1747205021973,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "unknown",
    "id": "10929212-5c35-4431-ad67-54755efc0862",
    "question": "edit",
    "response": "I'm not sure I understand. Try asking about quizzes, changing settings.",
    "timestamp": 1747205021496,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "language_question",
    "id": "28271374-facc-4a6c-ba10-b65a7db28a75",
    "question": "hi",
    "response": "What would you like to know about language learning? I can help with vocabulary, grammar, pronunciation, and more.",
    "timestamp": 1747204760664,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "language_question",
    "id": "032e7b2b-011f-4b58-a306-453f5aeb73be",
    "question": "hi",
    "response": "What would you like to know about language learning? I can help with vocabulary, grammar, pronunciation, and more.",
    "timestamp": 1747204573630,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "d7738c92-72f1-49ea-b564-3fd4b42fd3c4",
    "question": "exit quiz",
    "response": "Cancelled quiz setup",
    "timestamp": 1747204508957,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "9c0be2fb-a7ee-423c-9460-f6e5fb55b119",
    "question": "What type of quiz would you like to take?",
    "response": "exit quiz",
    "timestamp": 1747204508950,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "2fe51540-6dcf-4958-a4cd-c24eed3fc53f",
    "question": "What type of quiz would you like to take?",
    "response": "exit",
    "timestamp": 1747204503260,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "851ea3a3-6d38-47b7-8181-78ef2bbcf7f7",
    "question": "exit quiz",
    "response": "Cancelled quiz setup",
    "timestamp": 1747204470495,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "99711b3a-32a7-4377-b8fe-d5d632fa7df4",
    "question": "What type of quiz would you like to take?",
    "response": "exit quiz",
    "timestamp": 1747204470476,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "language_question",
    "id": "99dc30d6-579b-4d35-88db-8783fb52fb3a",
    "question": "hi",
    "response": "I'd be happy to help with your language question. Could you be more specific?",
    "timestamp": 1747204404060,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "unknown",
    "id": "79d62b70-050b-4bd8-aa3b-e937df2b4ba3",
    "question": "hello",
    "response": "I'm not sure I understand. Try asking about quizzes, changing settings.",
    "timestamp": 1747204321389,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "language_question",
    "id": "eaeb0107-d413-4ee1-9868-2ff303a7867c",
    "question": "hi",
    "response": "I'd be happy to help with your language question. Could you be more specific?",
    "timestamp": 1747204318670,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "unknown",
    "id": "c7924b98-6d57-4708-a73a-773f25a61186",
    "question": "hello",
    "response": "I'm not sure I understand. Try asking about quizzes, changing settings.",
    "timestamp": 1747204313928,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "language_question",
    "id": "b250953d-f56e-484a-8d5d-66593074cd9c",
    "question": "hi",
    "response": "I'd be happy to help with your language question. Could you be more specific?",
    "timestamp": 1747204274890,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "unknown",
    "id": "c7473a9d-d708-49c3-91de-690f72981b0c",
    "question": "ji",
    "response": "I'm not sure I understand. Try asking about quizzes, changing settings.",
    "timestamp": 1747204269664,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "language_question",
    "id": "cb3ab58a-988f-49f8-a285-c45744cd933f",
    "question": "hi",
    "response": "I'd be happy to help with your language question. Could you be more specific?",
    "timestamp": 1747204268523,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "language_question",
    "id": "b453daf1-5e90-4ad7-a1c8-c8b33e5d7f3f",
    "question": "hi",
    "response": "I'd be happy to help with your language question. Could you be more specific?",
    "timestamp": 1747204265393,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "unknown",
    "id": "91323c68-8689-4f1e-a5fc-f7b1bab57c29",
    "question": "i want to take quiz",
    "response": "I'm not sure I understand. Try asking about quizzes, changing settings.",
    "timestamp": 1747204261355,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "language_question",
    "id": "4dc5452d-750a-4af4-8c52-f0fa3382fd2b",
    "question": "i want to learn french",
    "response": "I'd be happy to help with your language question. Could you be more specific?",
    "timestamp": 1747204248298,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "unknown",
    "id": "b395048c-7178-48ea-8df2-a44a6cd8f064",
    "question": "english",
    "response": "I'm not sure I understand. Try asking about quizzes, changing settings.",
    "timestamp": 1747204106810,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "language_question",
    "id": "09e5017c-87fa-4811-8724-a1f2694481ff",
    "question": "i want to learn",
    "response": "I'd be happy to help with your language question. Could you be more specific?",
    "timestamp": 1747204085711,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "36ca35d7-42cc-455f-82eb-4cee39cc22ff",
    "question": "quiz",
    "response": "Started a new quiz session",
    "timestamp": 1747174194306,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "8bee2d3e-d213-42cc-a77d-a6f5eeed36e1",
    "question": "exit quiz",
    "response": "Cancelled quiz setup",
    "timestamp": 1747174194300,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "12c9d495-718f-42f7-83ea-a0381913fb04",
    "question": "What type of quiz would you like to take?",
    "response": "exit quiz",
    "timestamp": 1747174194292,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "951919e1-427b-497c-b7a3-b44892de7645",
    "question": "exit quiz",
    "response": "Exited quiz mode",
    "timestamp": 1747174187692,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "0784fdb9-8dcb-4e5f-99f4-edded5c8c5ab",
    "question": "quiz",
    "response": "Started a new quiz session",
    "timestamp": 1747174180786,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "unknown",
    "id": "9f5c9cc0-6e07-490b-9e8e-7137ea777712",
    "question": "exif",
    "response": "I'm not sure I understand. Try asking about quizzes, changing settings.",
    "timestamp": 1747174059425,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "unknown",
    "id": "c2fa0a87-46ac-47be-a668-c2ea6fc40b21",
    "question": "eit",
    "response": "I'm not sure I understand. Try asking about quizzes, changing settings.",
    "timestamp": 1747174055828,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "5fd3e853-9082-486a-814f-f7737c58a507",
    "question": "exit quiz",
    "response": "Exited quiz mode",
    "timestamp": 1747174043574,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "e2c50369-c9ce-4f58-a936-413adcdbd283",
    "question": "Quiz Question 5: Which sea borders the south of France?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747173938890,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "a2c115f0-73d9-4315-9a81-f4b29fd5456d",
    "question": "Quiz Question 4: Which French region is known for its wine production?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747173938239,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "2e4b59ee-587f-46f8-b47e-0b77e3d09eb8",
    "question": "Quiz Question 3: Which mountain range is found in France?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747173937808,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "09d56af1-3f7e-4093-9f53-9caaa5a45e1d",
    "question": "Quiz Question 2: Which is NOT a neighboring country of France?",
    "response": "Answer: exit uz, Feedback: That's not correct. The correct answer is: Portugal",
    "timestamp": 1747173845283,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "75e78bff-9dce-4b54-aa2e-df6b016e97de",
    "question": "Quiz Question 1: Which is the longest river in France?",
    "response": "Answer: mwc, Feedback: That's not correct. The correct answer is: Loire",
    "timestamp": 1747173839459,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "unknown",
    "id": "d8df94aa-d1ac-43a3-8aac-f99807381a96",
    "question": "mcw",
    "response": "I'm not sure I understand. Try asking about quizzes, changing settings.",
    "timestamp": 1747173620663,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "209930af-e4fb-4d55-977e-746111778ac5",
    "question": "quiz",
    "response": "Started a new quiz session",
    "timestamp": 1747173615820,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "09734991-29f4-4548-b019-b6ae11de8f0d",
    "question": "exit quiz",
    "response": "Cancelled quiz setup",
    "timestamp": 1747173615817,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "81afba72-a5cd-4c9f-a0a5-152418e356fc",
    "question": "What type of quiz would you like to take?",
    "response": "exit quiz",
    "timestamp": 1747173615812,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "38a8f1fd-ec14-47c1-9911-5c7d3f76d348",
    "question": "What type of quiz would you like to take?",
    "response": "dd",
    "timestamp": 1747173611584,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "5580c593-48c3-42a1-98f3-8fc09baf2eb3",
    "question": "What type of quiz would you like to take?",
    "response": "dd",
    "timestamp": 1747173610524,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "4bc298f2-e88a-48e9-a82b-33a5cc7d05e9",
    "question": "What type of quiz would you like to take?",
    "response": "i want to start quiz",
    "timestamp": 1747173608949,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "9806fb8d-5731-4bd5-89ed-810feabece5a",
    "question": "What type of quiz would you like to take?",
    "response": "ss",
    "timestamp": 1747173606820,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "5392dc28-8f89-45a9-8779-45b81dc058e1",
    "question": "What type of quiz would you like to take?",
    "response": "ss",
    "timestamp": 1747173605637,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "98cf74fd-33e8-4e3c-a879-cd1929dd053d",
    "question": "What type of quiz would you like to take?",
    "response": "i want to start quiz",
    "timestamp": 1747173603531,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "121f5792-a81d-4030-9b6c-78394687d2e6",
    "question": "What type of quiz would you like to take?",
    "response": "mcw",
    "timestamp": 1747173588522,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "f7cb0bda-6a09-4e1f-98d9-f9d802e55fed",
    "question": "What type of quiz would you like to take?",
    "response": "ss",
    "timestamp": 1747173585724,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "ceff6717-5642-4a12-ba42-b90001e4224e",
    "question": "What type of quiz would you like to take?",
    "response": "ss",
    "timestamp": 1747173583879,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "unknown",
    "id": "ad2dcfcf-e2e6-408e-aaa3-6d9777b19ddb",
    "question": "d",
    "response": "I'm not sure I understand. Try asking about quizzes, changing settings.",
    "timestamp": 1747173551360,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "unknown",
    "id": "66828977-f178-4680-a08e-1fbdef20624d",
    "question": "mcw",
    "response": "I'm not sure I understand. Try asking about quizzes, changing settings.",
    "timestamp": 1747173523429,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz_request",
    "id": "a7d32275-0a5e-4d35-b1b1-54c003573869",
    "question": "i want to start quiz",
    "response": "I'd be happy to start a quiz! Types de quiz disponibles : vocabulaire, grammaire, traduction, choix multiple",
    "timestamp": 1747173520454,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "settings",
    "id": "b3b2ab52-262d-473d-8c39-91566122d532",
    "question": "set target langauge french",
    "response": "You can change your settings for:\n- Mother language\n- Target language\n- Difficulty level\nWhat would you like to update?",
    "timestamp": 1747173350334,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "unknown",
    "id": "46a5efaf-530a-43a5-bb24-ae684b16b3f0",
    "question": "language",
    "response": "I'm not sure I understand. Try asking about quizzes, changing settings.",
    "timestamp": 1747173327808,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "unknown",
    "id": "ea95d548-6715-413d-9eae-78da15154b4e",
    "question": "target",
    "response": "I'm not sure I understand. Try asking about quizzes, changing settings.",
    "timestamp": 1747173323488,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "settings",
    "id": "1826dfee-72bb-48fa-ae70-e52bf45a09b8",
    "question": "set target langauge french",
    "response": "You can change your settings for:\n- Mother language\n- Target language\n- Difficulty level\nWhat would you like to update?",
    "timestamp": 1747173039723,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "unknown",
    "id": "588af25d-a3b2-450c-93c4-5b3044465ecc",
    "question": "exif",
    "response": "I'm not sure I understand. Try asking about quizzes, changing settings.",
    "timestamp": 1747172883561,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "settings",
    "id": "e2fc7848-9f50-4176-ae72-bb51ca6b5e9b",
    "question": "set target langauge french",
    "response": "You can change your settings for:\n- Mother language\n- Target language\n- Difficulty level\nWhat would you like to update?",
    "timestamp": 1747172863749,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz_request",
    "id": "468407d4-9c59-46b5-8386-9e9e994a9439",
    "question": "i want to take quiz for my intern",
    "response": "I'd be happy to start a quiz! What type would you prefer? We offer:\n1. Vocabulary\n2. Grammar\n3. Translation\n4. Multiple Choice\n5. Correction",
    "timestamp": 1747172437433,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "b840cb76-31b6-4401-bc92-30c5d46aaf1b",
    "question": "exit quiz",
    "response": "Exited quiz mode",
    "timestamp": 1747168367061,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "414b5e5a-244f-4827-9c3d-78bfb1b55251",
    "question": "exit quiz",
    "response": "Exited quiz mode",
    "timestamp": 1747168356168,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz_request",
    "id": "9ea4a3a6-ebd3-4ca5-8b1b-198c529de46b",
    "question": "i want to take quiz for my intern",
    "response": "I'd be happy to start a quiz! What type would you prefer? We offer:\n1. Vocabulary\n2. Grammar\n3. Translation\n4. Multiple Choice\n5. Correction",
    "timestamp": 1747168336028,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "system",
    "id": "a5ec867a-72d4-4841-9401-3cf2ace585d7",
    "question": "analytics",
    "response": "Displayed user analytics",
    "timestamp": 1747168323026,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "54d29918-9bec-4ecb-9c82-337974aad29b",
    "question": "Quiz Question 5: Which of these is a traditional French cheese?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747168312613,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "84630097-984d-47cd-886f-384aa36be0d3",
    "question": "Quiz Question 4: Which city is the capital of France?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747168311446,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "29260841-57b4-4cd8-8ccc-266dd81ed508",
    "question": "Quiz Question 3: What colors are on the French flag?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747168311325,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "a0cd6e03-3329-44dc-9cec-a08912fabe50",
    "question": "Quiz Question 2: Which French dish consists of snails cooked with garlic and butter?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747168311164,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "58d806c0-7a4e-4b6d-8128-96f29e97fc06",
    "question": "Quiz Question 1: Which famous museum is located in Paris?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747168310962,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "46ee2097-3b29-4b24-a5d1-d4654a6fe406",
    "question": "What type of quiz would you like to take?",
    "response": "mcq",
    "timestamp": 1747168309391,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "unknown",
    "id": "4c4d5da7-1526-4e4a-b1c7-bc1f189c79e7",
    "question": "ee",
    "response": "I'm not sure I understand. Try asking about quizzes, changing settings.",
    "timestamp": 1747168286512,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "unknown",
    "id": "ea1eda89-a511-4ef2-afcd-facf5eaa5020",
    "question": "quizzes",
    "response": "I'm not sure I understand. Try asking about quizzes, changing settings, or asking a specific language question.",
    "timestamp": 1747168089262,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "unknown",
    "id": "0fad7e6e-a4c2-4711-b6c1-a121e07855cc",
    "question": "grammar",
    "response": "I'm not sure I understand. Try asking about quizzes, changing settings, or asking a specific language question.",
    "timestamp": 1747167923859,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "greeting",
    "id": "e48310bd-84d0-4e3e-b281-b3409cd70a33",
    "question": "hi",
    "response": "Hello, mazen! I'm your Language Learning Bot. Would you like to practice vocabulary, grammar, or start a quiz?",
    "timestamp": 1747167917919,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "192c57c4-e233-4632-bc4a-14f9c792bc09",
    "question": "Quiz Question 5: Who was the first Queen Elizabeth of England?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747167909900,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "9bc3ecfc-47d2-4c0e-ab21-accfbdb5a57c",
    "question": "Quiz Question 4: Which river runs through London?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747167909319,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "80956621-5cdb-4b8b-9360-1c9832875afc",
    "question": "Quiz Question 3: Which of these countries is NOT part of the United Kingdom?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747167907786,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "6cb5db03-1b62-4cdb-a4a0-e6aa2b5be225",
    "question": "Quiz Question 2: Which of these is a famous English university?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747167907610,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "9c21438b-2486-4446-9362-fc9ecd6be3e9",
    "question": "Quiz Question 1: What is the highest mountain in England?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747167907368,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "f0937ff5-9852-4827-93a9-e5af0cd01e6f",
    "question": "What type of quiz would you like to take?",
    "response": "mcq",
    "timestamp": 1747167906968,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "unknown",
    "id": "dcd27f95-1032-4af3-9200-adcc84ead6af",
    "question": "english",
    "response": "I'm not sure I understand. Try asking about quizzes, changing settings, or asking a specific language question.",
    "timestamp": 1747167761189,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "unknown",
    "id": "c10ef56a-ab60-4d86-89a9-27468a97c060",
    "question": "study",
    "response": "I'm not sure I understand. Try asking about quizzes, changing settings, or asking a specific language question.",
    "timestamp": 1747167575990,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "system",
    "id": "30febdda-971e-4482-8824-a45dd6e04153",
    "question": "analytics",
    "response": "Displayed user analytics",
    "timestamp": 1747167501817,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "unknown",
    "id": "5306a38c-cdf5-4853-a991-e57734664dd4",
    "question": "????",
    "response": "I'm not sure I understand. Try asking about quizzes, changing settings, or asking a specific language question.",
    "timestamp": 1747167403911,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "system",
    "id": "f96b8e8b-bda5-4254-a3c0-4a8a5ded6295",
    "question": "analytics",
    "response": "Displayed user analytics",
    "timestamp": 1747167295440,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "system",
    "id": "2a55309f-3be5-4f63-a331-4fd14d00b10f",
    "question": "analytics",
    "response": "Displayed user analytics",
    "timestamp": 1747167034593,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "a29aa5de-7425-472c-93c5-24b4239b2bb1",
    "question": "Quiz Question 5: Which of these is a British car brand?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747166734858,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "c89d7135-0f66-4205-93b4-4eec86555f3b",
    "question": "Quiz Question 4: What is the traditional British meal eaten on Sunday?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747166734256,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "5af168c2-5807-41f1-a4a6-0afeedfdc91d",
    "question": "Quiz Question 3: What is 'Cockney rhyming slang'?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747166733559,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "903e02e9-876f-4681-a5ec-2a51672b49e8",
    "question": "Quiz Question 2: What side of the road do the British drive on?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747166733088,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "b292a93e-e706-47bf-87cb-ea98fa771bde",
    "question": "Quiz Question 1: What is a 'pub' in England?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747166732692,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "915275fa-8e6a-40bd-85c5-56af6bb48584",
    "question": "quiz",
    "response": "Started a new quiz session",
    "timestamp": 1747166731865,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "0d7d1864-1b9f-4d98-a2d0-1a992d59c23b",
    "question": "What type of quiz would you like to take?",
    "response": "mcq",
    "timestamp": 1747166731815,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "language_selection",
    "id": "48c630cd-5aa7-4ebb-b08b-4fdcbb7b0724",
    "question": "study english",
    "response": "Great! I'll help you learn english. Would you like to take a quiz to practice?",
    "timestamp": 1747166715961,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "unknown",
    "id": "e4029925-d56f-4f0c-adef-6bb1dbbf7408",
    "question": "study",
    "response": "I'm not sure I understand. Try asking about quizzes, changing settings, or asking a specific language question.",
    "timestamp": 1747166711153,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "unknown",
    "id": "92a78579-f332-4a58-a07b-fcb81755b172",
    "question": "exit\\",
    "response": "I'm not sure I understand. Try asking about quizzes, changing settings, or asking a specific language question.",
    "timestamp": 1747166237132,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "greeting",
    "id": "d0855751-6b32-40f2-914d-b88e98c6dd1a",
    "question": "hi",
    "response": "Hello, mazen! I'm your Language Learning Bot. Would you like to practice vocabulary, grammar, or start a quiz?",
    "timestamp": 1747166221731,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "greeting",
    "id": "aaa5da40-6ab8-4bd4-9993-cf22a74026c2",
    "question": "hi",
    "response": "Hello, mazen! I'm your Language Learning Bot. Would you like to practice vocabulary, grammar, or start a quiz?",
    "timestamp": 1747164326225,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "unknown",
    "id": "7bc3edff-ab7a-4ae9-9149-90346448e1a8",
    "question": "hu",
    "response": "I'm not sure I understand. Try asking about quizzes, changing settings, or asking a specific language question.",
    "timestamp": 1747164324348,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "system",
    "id": "c8d2e8e8-b50e-4828-8e3c-a02af7708f82",
    "question": "help",
    "response": "\nAvailable commands:\n1. chat - Start a conversation\n2. quiz - Take a quiz\n3. history - View your learning history\n4. preferences - Set your language preferences\n5. help - Show this help message\n6. logout - Log out\n7. exit - Exit the application\n",
    "timestamp": 1747164321172,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "44db934d-2748-459d-8e50-d729ab31a9f2",
    "question": "quiz",
    "response": "Started a new quiz session",
    "timestamp": 1747164210010,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "442dc87b-ef5b-4499-abe3-7a6eb01c0b40",
    "question": "What type of quiz would you like to take?",
    "response": "mcq",
    "timestamp": 1747164209973,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "system",
    "id": "04ee2e3d-cdec-4199-b8dd-bad12282c5d8",
    "question": "help",
    "response": "\nAvailable commands:\n1. chat - Start a conversation\n2. quiz - Take a quiz\n3. history - View your learning history\n4. preferences - Set your language preferences\n5. help - Show this help message\n6. logout - Log out\n7. exit - Exit the application\n",
    "timestamp": 1747164205230,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "32d678fb-2b5e-409b-bac3-84a67ceeb9be",
    "question": "Quiz Question 5: What is the typical French greeting?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747163330978,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "5ae1c099-d351-499e-afb1-a913650d7076",
    "question": "Quiz Question 4: What is a 'baguette'?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747163330440,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "e82e17b5-6f49-49be-b9ab-fdc43f036a89",
    "question": "Quiz Question 3: What is the currency used in France?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747163329936,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "346f28dd-2ef8-4618-be9b-992c0d7cfc28",
    "question": "Quiz Question 2: Which of these is a famous French fashion brand?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747163329486,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "77e0a6ba-b047-4854-a96a-cd3e08014ff7",
    "question": "Quiz Question 1: What is the most widely spoken language in France?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747163329092,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "59b0081f-8198-4719-b0dc-03da5253c866",
    "question": "quiz",
    "response": "Started a new quiz session",
    "timestamp": 1747163327560,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "9717150e-f8db-4786-aea2-2ad2c40d2d3e",
    "question": "What type of quiz would you like to take?",
    "response": "mcq",
    "timestamp": 1747163327554,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "11cc430c-cc03-430b-824f-b7c92448163b",
    "question": "Quiz Question 5: Which mountain range is found in France?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747163321226,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "55370b92-a483-4e02-8458-2c1bd2de24a3",
    "question": "Quiz Question 4: Which sea borders the south of France?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747163320580,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "cde0066b-a777-4b5e-bb55-aaa8e3428a08",
    "question": "Quiz Question 3: Which is the longest river in France?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747163320156,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "a6428068-d9f5-45f9-9a06-e68189509772",
    "question": "Quiz Question 2: Which French region is known for its wine production?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747163319562,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "29502c52-1a81-43f1-a316-2ed8b21110ba",
    "question": "Quiz Question 1: Which is NOT a neighboring country of France?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747163318760,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "c9ad275e-d4cb-4054-bfcc-c144d6573315",
    "question": "quiz",
    "response": "Started a new quiz session",
    "timestamp": 1747163316644,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "6f589a2f-8ffe-4a9a-9426-602479ab26a5",
    "question": "What type of quiz would you like to take?",
    "response": "mcq",
    "timestamp": 1747163316569,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "system",
    "id": "2c080750-e7e0-480a-8dff-2e857f53b2f7",
    "question": "help",
    "response": "\nAvailable commands:\n1. chat - Start a conversation\n2. quiz - Take a quiz\n3. history - View your learning history\n4. preferences - Set your language preferences\n5. help - Show this help message\n6. logout - Log out\n7. exit - Exit the application\n",
    "timestamp": 1747162871926,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "system",
    "id": "4e308d50-ab25-4f58-a982-6bfe6e524350",
    "question": "settings",
    "response": "Displayed user settings",
    "timestamp": 1747162865778,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "system",
    "id": "08bf9218-d48a-456f-bc83-546472564cb8",
    "question": "help",
    "response": "\nAvailable commands:\n1. chat - Start a conversation\n2. quiz - Take a quiz\n3. history - View your learning history\n4. preferences - Set your language preferences\n5. help - Show this help message\n6. logout - Log out\n7. exit - Exit the application\n",
    "timestamp": 1747162853292,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "unknown",
    "id": "b6c97cf1-b407-4631-8bdb-5544aa9c62ab",
    "question": "chat",
    "response": "I'm not sure I understand. Try asking about quizzes, changing settings, or asking a specific language question.",
    "timestamp": 1747162849629,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "91720612-0532-411b-b3ec-301ee7caa0e2",
    "question": "quiz",
    "response": "Started a new quiz session",
    "timestamp": 1747162502624,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "707f4cee-cdc5-4ddb-b77f-01a4652d78a2",
    "question": "exit quiz",
    "response": "Cancelled quiz setup",
    "timestamp": 1747162502620,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "43846931-1504-4c11-a8fc-637e24b0c6a2",
    "question": "What type of quiz would you like to take?",
    "response": "exit quiz",
    "timestamp": 1747162502613,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "bc5b2af4-3ed4-4f7f-a9a5-47c0fa6ad661",
    "question": "quiz",
    "response": "Started a new quiz session",
    "timestamp": 1747162492996,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "422dbdb0-164a-4552-a70f-bef566b29901",
    "question": "cancel",
    "response": "Cancelled quiz setup",
    "timestamp": 1747162492991,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "d493b9c8-41a8-42fd-9553-87449553d6d4",
    "question": "What type of quiz would you like to take?",
    "response": "cancel",
    "timestamp": 1747162492985,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "97dd3de3-0c7a-4247-ae7d-88e8e890f0f4",
    "question": "exit quiz",
    "response": "Exited quiz mode",
    "timestamp": 1747162478659,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "7d7c93ca-70d5-4e8e-a189-19259779d3dd",
    "question": "quiz",
    "response": "Started a new quiz session",
    "timestamp": 1747162474876,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "a78259b7-4aee-4a34-9532-95589273b3cc",
    "question": "What type of quiz would you like to take?",
    "response": "mcq",
    "timestamp": 1747162474829,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "a85369fb-6d67-4c9f-b4c9-f483ef4c485c",
    "question": "quiz",
    "response": "Started a new quiz session",
    "timestamp": 1747162467617,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "5afc67d1-6805-4a13-85e7-4f455f27fc95",
    "question": "exit quiz",
    "response": "Cancelled quiz setup",
    "timestamp": 1747162467602,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "0f754c0b-892f-42f9-8ea6-428c3539e76f",
    "question": "What type of quiz would you like to take?",
    "response": "exit quiz",
    "timestamp": 1747162467537,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "f9961878-0826-496e-a1bc-f701a1ac31a2",
    "question": "exit quiz",
    "response": "Exited quiz mode",
    "timestamp": 1747162326609,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "88ec3e89-3313-4813-86cc-5d91e6424e5c",
    "question": "quiz",
    "response": "Started a new quiz session",
    "timestamp": 1747162323915,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "4acbb3ab-8eec-4222-bae0-558eeda31229",
    "question": "What type of quiz would you like to take?",
    "response": "mcq",
    "timestamp": 1747162323868,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "b34b4284-1f60-4399-b4eb-34d617551760",
    "question": "What type of quiz would you like to take?",
    "response": "exit quiz",
    "timestamp": 1747162299843,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "2bee9fe9-e5d0-4fd9-ae15-1ddf1a7c577f",
    "question": "What type of quiz would you like to take?",
    "response": "exit quiz",
    "timestamp": 1747162296032,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "38842db0-d86f-4f18-a8d1-15b1fac707e7",
    "question": "What type of quiz would you like to take?",
    "response": "exit quiz",
    "timestamp": 1747162290037,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "system",
    "id": "bd5c862e-d06a-42eb-9852-a86493c68572",
    "question": "help",
    "response": "\nAvailable commands:\n1. chat - Start a conversation\n2. quiz - Take a quiz\n3. history - View your learning history\n4. preferences - Set your language preferences\n5. help - Show this help message\n6. logout - Log out\n7. exit - Exit the application\n",
    "timestamp": 1747161999092,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "greeting",
    "id": "b9be2dc6-3ff1-49e5-8197-411f1430ecef",
    "question": "hi",
    "response": "Hello, mazen! I'm your Language Learning Bot. Would you like to practice vocabulary, grammar, or start a quiz?",
    "timestamp": 1747161996829,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "a17dc22e-4114-4f4d-b691-33bad9327c93",
    "question": "exit quiz",
    "response": "Exited quiz mode",
    "timestamp": 1747161990763,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "1cc2d9b5-2792-4daf-ba48-d7b33dce42d5",
    "question": "Quiz Question 1: Which of these is a traditional English dessert?",
    "response": "Answer: exitquiz, Feedback: That's not correct. The correct answer is: Trifle",
    "timestamp": 1747161987421,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "694ce33c-d9b7-4e93-8ad1-5b126f6b6eeb",
    "question": "quiz",
    "response": "Started a new quiz session",
    "timestamp": 1747161981840,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "2c23e062-eba2-4048-ac63-71b9e9f590cc",
    "question": "What type of quiz would you like to take?",
    "response": "mcq",
    "timestamp": 1747161981833,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz_request",
    "id": "f8778c97-ce00-4294-80b1-f82a8c045a37",
    "question": "exit quiz\\",
    "response": "I'd be happy to start a quiz! What type would you prefer? We offer:\n1. Vocabulary\n2. Grammar\n3. Translation\n4. Multiple Choice\n5. Correction",
    "timestamp": 1747161918547,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "greeting",
    "id": "8b0cd24f-b9ab-4b31-8e0f-3ba5a8064082",
    "question": "hi",
    "response": "Hello, mazen! I'm your Language Learning Bot. Would you like to practice vocabulary, grammar, or start a quiz?",
    "timestamp": 1747161863097,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz_request",
    "id": "848e298d-e756-46ad-98ef-e98e6f0e7c36",
    "question": "exit quiz",
    "response": "I'd be happy to start a quiz! What type would you prefer? We offer:\n1. Vocabulary\n2. Grammar\n3. Translation\n4. Multiple Choice\n5. Correction",
    "timestamp": 1747161807401,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "unknown",
    "id": "919e5965-6d26-4125-a47b-8df385c1c4e8",
    "question": "mcq",
    "response": "I'm not sure I understand. Try asking about quizzes, changing settings, or asking a specific language question.",
    "timestamp": 1747161788622,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "307115cc-2b6b-4660-975d-11a9fbace607",
    "question": "exit quiz",
    "response": "Exited quiz mode",
    "timestamp": 1747161768027,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "c8c27110-1808-42c6-89a7-e5d196c3114f",
    "question": "quiz",
    "response": "Started a new quiz session",
    "timestamp": 1747161764095,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "4494aafd-2f0f-42e9-a723-c96a56169d9a",
    "question": "What type of quiz would you like to take?",
    "response": "mcq",
    "timestamp": 1747161764089,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz_request",
    "id": "c2fa415d-5d85-42cc-b2b8-12613786f605",
    "question": "exit quiz",
    "response": "I'd be happy to start a quiz! What type would you prefer? We offer:\n1. Vocabulary\n2. Grammar\n3. Translation\n4. Multiple Choice\n5. Correction",
    "timestamp": 1747161714677,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz_request",
    "id": "a5034da9-a40d-4693-a512-e584720c8980",
    "question": "exit quiz",
    "response": "I'd be happy to start a quiz! What type would you prefer? We offer:\n1. Vocabulary\n2. Grammar\n3. Translation\n4. Multiple Choice\n5. Correction",
    "timestamp": 1747161703039,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "language_selection",
    "id": "7666cfb6-45e2-4218-907b-e2326cb2ce23",
    "question": "i want to master french",
    "response": "Great! I'll help you learn french. Would you like to take a quiz to practice?",
    "timestamp": 1747161523481,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "4c23da7d-87bf-4011-88bd-53695e3e6e84",
    "question": "exit quiz",
    "response": "Exited quiz mode",
    "timestamp": 1747161513980,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "a73ea917-0a75-4532-9436-09ddaea8ffd2",
    "question": "Quiz Question 1: What is the traditional Spanish midday rest called?",
    "response": "Answer: exit uiz, Feedback: That's not correct. The correct answer is: Siesta",
    "timestamp": 1747161508646,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "bc41a45f-7818-4c9e-98fb-186f25a8868a",
    "question": "quiz",
    "response": "Started a new quiz session",
    "timestamp": 1747161504327,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "03b4385e-23c4-43cd-9785-e4c1f3693a95",
    "question": "What type of quiz would you like to take?",
    "response": "mcq",
    "timestamp": 1747161504285,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "3c6ed5e8-85a8-4225-b414-0ba726106afc",
    "question": "What type of quiz would you like to take?",
    "response": "exit quiz",
    "timestamp": 1747161495978,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "017c4e3e-c53b-4a26-ba7a-c76ad8dbd0fb",
    "question": "What type of quiz would you like to take?",
    "response": "start quiz",
    "timestamp": 1747161438067,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "a8eae7d7-6d9f-4b91-8c6b-c1d668a43eb5",
    "question": "What type of quiz would you like to take?",
    "response": "quiz",
    "timestamp": 1747161432130,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "45a85f2b-0c8f-4d5f-9911-fe582afe9785",
    "question": "What type of quiz would you like to take?",
    "response": "start quiz",
    "timestamp": 1747161428115,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "8369fa2c-4bd1-4619-90c9-3d4c33fcd862",
    "question": "What type of quiz would you like to take?",
    "response": "quiz",
    "timestamp": 1747161424118,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "25d87433-ef6c-4e9f-bf37-5a0e880849ee",
    "question": "What type of quiz would you like to take?",
    "response": "quiz",
    "timestamp": 1747161412645,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "language_selection",
    "id": "93945b20-97e7-4624-a26b-641c849945dc",
    "question": "study spanish",
    "response": "Great! I'll help you learn spanish. Would you like to take a quiz to practice?",
    "timestamp": 1747161393444,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "greeting",
    "id": "a706f7f8-47a6-4b30-a106-9d8a677be6e8",
    "question": "how we say hello",
    "response": "Hello, mazen! I'm your Language Learning Bot. Would you like to practice vocabulary, grammar, or start a quiz?",
    "timestamp": 1747161213448,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "unknown",
    "id": "1ac46f36-228d-408e-97a9-b4ccaf327605",
    "question": "study",
    "response": "I'm not sure I understand. Try asking about quizzes, changing settings, or asking a specific language question.",
    "timestamp": 1747160447985,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "unknown",
    "id": "ff63b994-993e-4d2d-8258-b212a29ea3d0",
    "question": "learn",
    "response": "I'm not sure I understand. Try asking about quizzes, changing settings, or asking a specific language question.",
    "timestamp": 1747160445138,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "e1756e2b-94f0-4176-834b-fbb10daebf0f",
    "question": "exit quiz",
    "response": "Exited quiz mode",
    "timestamp": 1747160440883,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "c15d8029-c1a8-470d-9cc1-6cc36d935ef8",
    "question": "quiz",
    "response": "Started a new quiz session",
    "timestamp": 1747160424548,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "c93e7254-18f9-40f3-beb4-081932364736",
    "question": "What type of quiz would you like to take?",
    "response": "mcq",
    "timestamp": 1747160424496,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "3d86d66c-9ee8-4313-a8fa-447e06ca9261",
    "question": "What type of quiz would you like to take?",
    "response": "mcw",
    "timestamp": 1747160420801,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "3ab7a4f0-bc73-4a24-b47c-22f9fd6c4f14",
    "question": "What type of quiz would you like to take?",
    "response": "mcw",
    "timestamp": 1747160419414,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "ab744290-6525-44c3-9463-d86f4c90aee0",
    "question": "What type of quiz would you like to take?",
    "response": "mcw",
    "timestamp": 1747160414242,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "unknown",
    "id": "2a487b0a-e290-46e8-8139-696ac8621459",
    "question": "mcq",
    "response": "I'm not sure I understand. Try asking about quizzes, changing settings, or asking a specific language question.",
    "timestamp": 1747160148021,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "37b37e0d-856e-445a-8cec-a362dacef85f",
    "question": "quiz",
    "response": "Started a new quiz session",
    "timestamp": 1747160146832,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "13aa7a87-f24a-4544-82eb-21dec02cf25c",
    "question": "What type of quiz would you like to take?",
    "response": "mcw",
    "timestamp": 1747160146796,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "701116ef-2d09-443c-acc2-99d542ffa307",
    "question": "quiz",
    "response": "Started a new quiz session",
    "timestamp": 1747160050613,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "6d5e68c4-255c-4ebb-a1e8-c65108ef438b",
    "question": "What type of quiz would you like to take?",
    "response": "exit quiz",
    "timestamp": 1747160050608,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "unknown",
    "id": "db006b6b-77ac-42ff-88d2-28e9b153392d",
    "question": "mcq",
    "response": "I'm not sure I understand. Try asking about quizzes, changing settings, or asking a specific language question.",
    "timestamp": 1747160021585,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "b4abda41-d249-439c-80ce-93519b90a43e",
    "question": "quiz",
    "response": "Started a new quiz session",
    "timestamp": 1747160010617,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "12a6c8b2-8c31-4caa-89e8-c1a4bef9256d",
    "question": "What type of quiz would you like to take?",
    "response": "mcw",
    "timestamp": 1747160010613,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "ffcbab27-0ef0-41f3-9794-01fa1d8571b3",
    "question": "exit quiz",
    "response": "Exited quiz mode",
    "timestamp": 1747159995841,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "b39ea869-f22c-4552-8045-9d40b9971a98",
    "question": "quiz",
    "response": "Started a new quiz session",
    "timestamp": 1747159993233,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "d1cceb61-f9d1-48ef-8a38-d7a9b84f1c7a",
    "question": "What type of quiz would you like to take?",
    "response": "mcq",
    "timestamp": 1747159993225,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "8ca193ea-eb57-4c28-9a7c-2cbdd6976bac",
    "question": "exit quiz",
    "response": "Exited quiz mode",
    "timestamp": 1747159983545,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "9e205d36-4b3c-4bff-a0ad-f649fb955fbb",
    "question": "quiz",
    "response": "Started a new quiz session",
    "timestamp": 1747159980006,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "0b63ae82-22b8-42b2-a220-b9242c936a66",
    "question": "What type of quiz would you like to take?",
    "response": "mcq",
    "timestamp": 1747159979947,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "unknown",
    "id": "0aaa07a7-f2f5-4e37-bb0b-38378fa5ee19",
    "question": "yes",
    "response": "I'm not sure I understand. Try asking about quizzes, changing settings, or asking a specific language question.",
    "timestamp": 1747159972083,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "system",
    "id": "7fbcb46d-745f-470d-bdc8-9826ce220994",
    "question": "save settings",
    "response": "Attempted to save user settings",
    "timestamp": 1747159967532,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "system",
    "id": "cbe7b9c8-b26e-4a20-8034-5160851fc885",
    "question": "save settings",
    "response": "Attempted to save user settings",
    "timestamp": 1747159647241,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "d3db69bb-61d5-4239-beb4-3c9041bef028",
    "question": "Quiz Question 1: Which famous museum is located in Paris?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747158304748,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "698cd64c-1e44-4057-b198-2e84e2eb2432",
    "question": "quiz",
    "response": "Started a new quiz session",
    "timestamp": 1747158303648,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "e53cbdbf-d926-41db-9f4a-3f3ca370f961",
    "question": "What type of quiz would you like to take?",
    "response": "mcq",
    "timestamp": 1747158303585,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "system",
    "id": "90dfe180-e9f5-4356-b8f1-60205e22c56e",
    "question": "help",
    "response": "\r\nAvailable commands:\r\n1. chat - Start a conversation\r\n2. quiz - Take a quiz\r\n3. history - View your learning history\r\n4. preferences - Set your language preferences\r\n5. help - Show this help message\r\n6. logout - Log out\r\n7. exit - Exit the application\r\n",
    "timestamp": 1747158263496,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "unknown",
    "id": "efd270dd-8989-440f-9185-a6610f561cc1",
    "question": "hlep",
    "response": "I'm not sure I understand. Try asking about quizzes, changing settings, or asking a specific language question.",
    "timestamp": 1747158259503,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "9c858718-b31d-4b4e-8001-060d2c19ec3b",
    "question": "quiz",
    "response": "Started a new quiz session",
    "timestamp": 1747158252215,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "a0a3b13e-034e-4a07-9942-a9384764df40",
    "question": "What type of quiz would you like to take?",
    "response": "help",
    "timestamp": 1747158252201,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "settings",
    "id": "51daea19-6c82-4d1c-bf91-7c4156bf667b",
    "question": "set target langauge german",
    "response": "You can change your settings for:\n- Mother language\n- Target language\n- Difficulty level\nWhat would you like to update?",
    "timestamp": 1747158065620,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "6c4a5829-9244-4e26-b88d-dac1eabc4dee",
    "question": "quiz",
    "response": "Started a new quiz session",
    "timestamp": 1747157855356,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "265af891-6b7d-4835-a68c-f282a6b7577a",
    "question": "What type of quiz would you like to take?",
    "response": "grammar",
    "timestamp": 1747157855301,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "greeting",
    "id": "451e14cc-00c9-4752-b670-c3eb7dbc8695",
    "question": "hi",
    "response": "Hello, mazen! I'm your Language Learning Bot. Would you like to practice vocabulary, grammar, or start a quiz?",
    "timestamp": 1747157841160,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "greeting",
    "id": "def83745-8789-487d-95c9-adb2196f009b",
    "question": "hi",
    "response": "Hello, mazen! I'm your Language Learning Bot. Would you like to practice vocabulary, grammar, or start a quiz?",
    "timestamp": 1747157817362,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "unknown",
    "id": "6e38e74b-2f3e-42da-8881-40486bc81eb0",
    "question": "exix",
    "response": "I'm not sure I understand. Try asking about quizzes, changing settings, or asking a specific language question.",
    "timestamp": 1747157355280,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "c1fc948d-60a6-4f21-97f2-ed8d32ba6f31",
    "question": "Quiz Question 1: What color is the Spanish flag?",
    "response": "Answer: quit, Feedback: That's not correct. The correct answer is: Red and yellow",
    "timestamp": 1747040601007,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "b881b927-5bc9-45c2-805b-997a8eeeaf6b",
    "question": "quiz",
    "response": "Started a new quiz session",
    "timestamp": 1747040592933,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "2abebef8-c1a5-47ed-9dad-6eca97f08820",
    "question": "What type of quiz would you like to take?",
    "response": "mcq",
    "timestamp": 1747040592929,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "unknown",
    "id": "5e77e259-b6fe-4f21-ae59-4ea731f5b1ab",
    "question": "mcq",
    "response": "I'm not sure I understand. Try asking about quizzes, changing settings, or asking a specific language question.",
    "timestamp": 1747040586224,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "unknown",
    "id": "c2e014c5-357d-40ea-94d5-fba7055a6b76",
    "question": "vocabulary",
    "response": "I'm not sure I understand. Try asking about quizzes, changing settings, or asking a specific language question.",
    "timestamp": 1747040582711,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "unknown",
    "id": "a3edf6f3-cff7-4959-9f20-78b937f3381f",
    "question": "grammar",
    "response": "I'm not sure I understand. Try asking about quizzes, changing settings, or asking a specific language question.",
    "timestamp": 1747040568165,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "90bbc2d7-70c7-4fbb-ad0c-a907b69c7ab5",
    "question": "quiz",
    "response": "Started a new quiz session",
    "timestamp": 1747040561402,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "1113475f-2213-4c9e-8f2a-ec9ae41831df",
    "question": "What type of quiz would you like to take?",
    "response": "grammer",
    "timestamp": 1747040561398,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "unknown",
    "id": "b522a541-12ef-4b91-b7d3-35cea5d9f276",
    "question": "1",
    "response": "I'm not sure I understand. Try asking about quizzes, changing settings, or asking a specific language question.",
    "timestamp": 1747040551316,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz_request",
    "id": "f46461a7-f154-468d-86dd-e32fc3133796",
    "question": "can you giveanother quiz",
    "response": "I'd be happy to start a quiz! What type would you prefer? We offer:\n1. Vocabulary\n2. Grammar\n3. Translation\n4. Multiple Choice\n5. Correction",
    "timestamp": 1747040546237,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "8097b059-b7f0-4a57-8200-465a9af79350",
    "question": "Quiz Question 5: Which city is the capital of Spain?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747040535819,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "bd07dedf-9b3f-4d08-ba55-60990c9a9e57",
    "question": "Quiz Question 4: Which Spanish artist painted 'Guernica'?",
    "response": "Answer: Joan Mr, Feedback: That's not correct. The correct answer is: Pablo Picasso",
    "timestamp": 1747040509425,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "cfd58a63-2d83-4984-882f-62847db463d2",
    "question": "Quiz Question 3: Which Spanish dish is made with rice and seafood?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747040501061,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "c78984ff-eed8-4595-80c1-e00d69b65c61",
    "question": "Quiz Question 2: Which Spanish football club has won the most UEFA Champions League titles?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747040497849,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "c45bb191-ccd5-4ad4-a141-55f26c5c96f4",
    "question": "Quiz Question 1: On which day do Spaniards traditionally eat twelve grapes at midnight?",
    "response": "Answer: easter, Feedback: That's not correct. The correct answer is: New Year's Eve",
    "timestamp": 1747040495611,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "fec997ef-a4ac-4122-8316-01b42576c315",
    "question": "quiz",
    "response": "Started a new quiz session",
    "timestamp": 1747040379181,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "846ef032-e19d-4d6d-84c5-94e228557d1b",
    "question": "What type of quiz would you like to take?",
    "response": "mcq",
    "timestamp": 1747040379126,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz_request",
    "id": "d7d40cd4-8718-4ab0-a6fe-1d0c93a3caa7",
    "question": "i want to take correction quiz",
    "response": "I'd be happy to start a quiz! What type would you prefer? We offer:\n1. Vocabulary\n2. Grammar\n3. Translation\n4. Multiple Choice\n5. Correction",
    "timestamp": 1747040352388,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz_request",
    "id": "22aa73a4-4e48-41ed-8d06-464d7f4616df",
    "question": "i want to take a quiz",
    "response": "I'd be happy to start a quiz! What type would you prefer? We offer:\n1. Vocabulary\n2. Grammar\n3. Translation\n4. Multiple Choice\n5. Correction",
    "timestamp": 1747040288177,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "unknown",
    "id": "5abc3c57-a06b-4644-b034-e163eb493818",
    "question": "i want to learn",
    "response": "I'm not sure I understand. Try asking about quizzes, changing settings, or asking a specific language question.",
    "timestamp": 1747040261407,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "greeting",
    "id": "304217e7-c9d0-4e42-9a07-7eb4ff4c53ac",
    "question": "hello",
    "response": "Hello, mazen! I'm your Language Learning Bot. Would you like to practice vocabulary, grammar, or start a quiz?",
    "timestamp": 1747040248735,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "settings",
    "id": "ce08d467-54f5-474f-a0ba-5b4a58b1c633",
    "question": "set target langauge drench",
    "response": "You can change your settings for:\n- Mother language\n- Target language\n- Difficulty level\nWhat would you like to update?",
    "timestamp": 1747039250363,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "settings",
    "id": "363a3666-e108-439a-8404-e47a9f0f04b7",
    "question": "set mother langauge french",
    "response": "You can change your settings for:\n- Mother language\n- Target language\n- Difficulty level\nWhat would you like to update?",
    "timestamp": 1747039165394,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "c89ef31f-e331-4113-b455-189229fbf4e7",
    "question": "Quiz Question 5: Which mountain range runs along the border between Spain and France?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1746900285124,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "4fc751a3-2790-4618-a83f-ddb3d73b4e66",
    "question": "Quiz Question 4: Which Spanish city is famous for the 'Running of the Bulls'?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1746900284717,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "6ace25c5-5ff1-47f1-bda0-7b85434822f6",
    "question": "Quiz Question 3: Which is the longest river in Spain?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1746900284157,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "3f345c81-0001-4f91-8a73-71178749dcad",
    "question": "Quiz Question 2: Which of these Spanish islands is located in the Mediterranean Sea?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1746900283889,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "e8aa0247-a666-49f1-ac95-90058a69857c",
    "question": "Quiz Question 1: Which animal is featured on the Spanish coat of arms?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1746900283547,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "58eb860c-861a-453b-af96-75ba09249e27",
    "question": "quiz",
    "response": "Started a new quiz session",
    "timestamp": 1746900281242,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "e20707fe-18d9-40a0-986a-376048a44863",
    "question": "What type of quiz would you like to take?",
    "response": "mcq",
    "timestamp": 1746900281237,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "ddfd1e32-d85c-4821-bca4-3669de43a505",
    "question": "Quiz Question 5: What color is the Spanish flag?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1746900269541,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "ff1df452-86e5-4655-9305-69dfe2477fdf",
    "question": "Quiz Question 4: Which of these is a traditional Spanish dance?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1746900269117,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "7000aa3a-c623-4ddf-87ec-59414b38d038",
    "question": "Quiz Question 3: What is the traditional Spanish midday rest called?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1746900268611,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "84f3132d-15c4-4fec-9ad4-f18e6a4c0722",
    "question": "Quiz Question 2: What is the currency used in Spain?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1746900268163,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "30d971cd-074b-47d4-b5ac-983d12487815",
    "question": "Quiz Question 1: What time do Spaniards typically eat dinner?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1746900267613,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "848f891e-e641-4972-b18d-ea5e84ea5124",
    "question": "quiz",
    "response": "Started a new quiz session",
    "timestamp": 1746900266117,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "0cdec352-9037-4639-a877-6d6f94044f99",
    "question": "What type of quiz would you like to take?",
    "response": "mcq",
    "timestamp": 1746900266055,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "a0aab5dd-cbc6-4af0-8134-960c7b28d421",
    "question": "Quiz Question 5: Which preposition completes: 'Hablo ___ mi amigo'?",
    "response": "Answer: b, Feedback: That's not correct. The correct answer is: con",
    "timestamp": 1746900033943,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "7e5eb89e-9250-4a03-a993-066a7dc2b682",
    "question": "Quiz Question 4: Which preposition completes: 'Vivo ___ España'?",
    "response": "Answer: b, Feedback: That's not correct. The correct answer is: en",
    "timestamp": 1746900033545,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "9346939e-64b8-4ec1-8d7b-f07d8a0a3643",
    "question": "Quiz Question 3: Which preposition completes: 'Voy ___ Madrid'?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1746900032480,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "336448d2-bfa2-483d-be1c-eb84bacbae73",
    "question": "Quiz Question 2: Which preposition completes: 'Viajo ___ tren'?",
    "response": "Answer: b, Feedback: That's not correct. The correct answer is: en",
    "timestamp": 1746900030999,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "be9ac6e0-0af5-40ca-9e6f-610f06a4afe0",
    "question": "Quiz Question 1: Which preposition completes: 'El libro es ___ Juan'?",
    "response": "Answer: b, Feedback: That's not correct. The correct answer is: de",
    "timestamp": 1746900030652,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "f77ca6b5-2428-44cb-ae32-4a177ea3f862",
    "question": "quiz",
    "response": "Started a new quiz session",
    "timestamp": 1746900029916,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "057e0502-1f5d-467f-a153-2b8cf18e9269",
    "question": "What type of quiz would you like to take?",
    "response": "grammar",
    "timestamp": 1746900029908,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "c13fe6f4-69f0-44bb-86ad-6f3e027f07d1",
    "question": "Quiz Question 5: Which Spanish football club has won the most UEFA Champions League titles?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1746900007591,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "3eaa03e7-245b-437e-bdf7-9b3ef99e42f2",
    "question": "Quiz Question 4: On which day do Spaniards traditionally eat twelve grapes at midnight?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1746900005154,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "55e27a5c-10cb-452b-96dd-bc967fd745eb",
    "question": "Quiz Question 3: Which Spanish dish is made with rice and seafood?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1746900004580,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "5f39327c-8ba0-4fe8-99f4-27d2f5bb529f",
    "question": "Quiz Question 2: Which city is the capital of Spain?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1746900003974,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "7419a1db-cf1b-4387-909e-06ac6ce9b0b4",
    "question": "Quiz Question 1: Which Spanish artist painted 'Guernica'?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1746900002487,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "10edc48a-a467-4f2c-ac49-5e9ef437d623",
    "question": "quiz",
    "response": "Started a new quiz session",
    "timestamp": 1746899998185,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "b49e54b2-67e4-411f-b7a4-2a00fd6a608b",
    "question": "What type of quiz would you like to take?",
    "response": "mcq",
    "timestamp": 1746899998104,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "unknown",
    "id": "aa261d82-471d-405e-a578-4f4c0d2487cd",
    "question": "a",
    "response": "I'm not sure I understand. Try asking about quizzes, changing settings, or asking a specific language question.",
    "timestamp": 1746898565349,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "0da9a899-8a4f-4057-bf14-c1aab96d2d92",
    "question": "Quiz Question 5: Which animal is featured on the Spanish coat of arms?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1746898564624,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "bc03c8a0-4a21-45b4-b7b6-a2427a100f04",
    "question": "Quiz Question 4: Which of these Spanish islands is located in the Mediterranean Sea?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1746898563887,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "ec9ac5ef-b49a-42f2-9be1-21f675340c76",
    "question": "Quiz Question 3: Which is the longest river in Spain?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1746898563490,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "9450d6cf-9ea7-4a65-b974-0c425600f6ad",
    "question": "Quiz Question 2: Which mountain range runs along the border between Spain and France?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1746898563189,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "37758ed9-7cfd-4488-adae-f619176a1583",
    "question": "Quiz Question 1: Which Spanish city is famous for the 'Running of the Bulls'?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1746898562384,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "95247731-d95b-4195-8b0c-ff914e0ef9a2",
    "question": "quiz",
    "response": "Started a new quiz session",
    "timestamp": 1746898540091,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "6b55f358-b059-4f60-a00c-1c09b5f7696f",
    "question": "What type of quiz would you like to take?",
    "response": "mcq",
    "timestamp": 1746898540086,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "unknown",
    "id": "387ee90b-550e-4abd-98ce-90d1b23df112",
    "question": "a",
    "response": "I'm not sure I understand. Try asking about quizzes, changing settings, or asking a specific language question.",
    "timestamp": 1746898368511,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "5195ed7e-f88a-467e-bc4a-e5a03f1b2c6e",
    "question": "Quiz Question 5: Which is the longest river in Spain?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1746898368317,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "cf56cf2b-3473-4232-9740-659fca5dd0c6",
    "question": "Quiz Question 4: Which animal is featured on the Spanish coat of arms?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1746898368109,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "f2208693-4f00-47c1-a34b-36998a248eb2",
    "question": "Quiz Question 3: Which Spanish city is famous for the 'Running of the Bulls'?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1746898367898,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "f29bbe32-da9d-4a9a-939a-309b59cd070b",
    "question": "Quiz Question 2: Which mountain range runs along the border between Spain and France?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1746898367669,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "dd4b0614-51e2-4214-b3e0-d6f47fca14d0",
    "question": "Quiz Question 1: Which of these Spanish islands is located in the Mediterranean Sea?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1746898366482,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "5420f234-f7ab-4b51-b98c-cfb2d80c0106",
    "question": "quiz",
    "response": "Started a new quiz session",
    "timestamp": 1746898364679,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "7cecd8fe-b4f0-4709-a02d-1a0cd3663ace",
    "question": "What type of quiz would you like to take?",
    "response": "mcq",
    "timestamp": 1746898364636,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "settings",
    "id": "80fd81b7-889a-4f67-a8fd-589894f909dc",
    "question": "set target english",
    "response": "You can change your settings for:\n- Mother language\n- Target language\n- Difficulty level\nWhat would you like to update?",
    "timestamp": 1746898360555,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "unknown",
    "id": "6e99fe3f-85f7-4906-a3c9-8eaf44dfa2f9",
    "question": "",
    "response": "I'm not sure I understand. Try asking about quizzes, changing settings, or asking a specific language question.",
    "timestamp": 1746898294030,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "settings",
    "id": "75e5c4ec-fb4b-4949-8925-e2882cc49976",
    "question": "set mother laungauge english",
    "response": "You can change your settings for:\n- Mother language\n- Target language\n- Difficulty level\nWhat would you like to update?",
    "timestamp": 1746898283635,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "unknown",
    "id": "98bc2f2f-c71c-40dc-a8ff-2836dd5dd4e3",
    "question": "elp",
    "response": "I'm not sure I understand. Try asking about quizzes, changing settings, or asking a specific language question.",
    "timestamp": 1746898259769,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "system",
    "id": "2c24aad7-2990-42c9-a43e-18606cb7562c",
    "question": "help",
    "response": "\r\nAvailable commands:\r\n1. chat - Start a conversation\r\n2. quiz - Take a quiz\r\n3. history - View your learning history\r\n4. preferences - Set your language preferences\r\n5. help - Show this help message\r\n6. logout - Log out\r\n7. exit - Exit the application\r\n",
    "timestamp": 1746898029531,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "system",
    "id": "e2431fb1-3785-4b49-a297-450aef588cc4",
    "question": "help",
    "response": "\r\nAvailable commands:\r\n1. chat - Start a conversation\r\n2. quiz - Take a quiz\r\n3. history - View your learning history\r\n4. preferences - Set your language preferences\r\n5. help - Show this help message\r\n6. logout - Log out\r\n7. exit - Exit the application\r\n",
    "timestamp": 1746898020611,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "647d75c9-e720-4ad2-8d46-3d7d9c2008b1",
    "question": "quiz",
    "response": "Started a new quiz session",
    "timestamp": 1746889205089,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "unknown",
    "id": "34e85455-0d45-4134-8d6a-692d01457c41",
    "question": "mcq",
    "response": "I'm not sure I understand. Try asking about quizzes, changing settings, or asking a specific language question.",
    "timestamp": 1746889199054,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "647a7c28-6c5a-421c-981e-5138c2f003c7",
    "question": "quiz",
    "response": "Started a new quiz session",
    "timestamp": 1746889066770,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "greeting",
    "id": "c15349d3-fde4-4db6-a956-f77dac2f8198",
    "question": "hi",
    "response": "Hello, mazen! I'm your Language Learning Bot. Would you like to practice vocabulary, grammar, or start a quiz?",
    "timestamp": 1746889053385,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "db661e33-928a-47de-9f34-621665f7da31",
    "question": "quiz",
    "response": "Started a new quiz session",
    "timestamp": 1746889046283,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "greeting",
    "id": "462cd87d-e081-46a5-aefa-3c56468e2a51",
    "question": "hi",
    "response": "Hello, mazen! I'm your Language Learning Bot. Would you like to practice vocabulary, grammar, or start a quiz?",
    "timestamp": 1746889036482,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "greeting",
    "id": "2066589d-aac8-49c6-b7cd-af1c0be15468",
    "question": "hi",
    "response": "Hello, mazen! I'm your Language Learning Bot. Would you like to practice vocabulary, grammar, or start a quiz?",
    "timestamp": 1746889034010,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "24a53b5f-da3e-49c4-ae5b-369d3219876d",
    "question": "quiz",
    "response": "Started a new quiz session",
    "timestamp": 1746889027486,
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }],
  "quizResults": [{
    "correctAnswers": 5,
    "id": "67e74e06-732a-4609-917a-308cc837d873",
    "questions": [{
      "correctAnswer": "klein",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Was ist 'small' auf Deutsch?",
      "userAnswer": "klein"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "groß",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Was ist 'big' auf Deutsch?",
      "userAnswer": "groß"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "schön",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Was ist 'beautiful' auf Deutsch?",
      "userAnswer": "schön"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "jung",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Was ist 'young' auf Deutsch?",
      "userAnswer": "jung"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "alt",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Was ist 'old' auf Deutsch?",
      "userAnswer": "alt"
    }],
    "quizType": "Vocabulary",
    "score": 5.0,
    "timestamp": 1747410113823,
    "totalQuestions": 5,
    "userAnswers": ["klein", "groß", "schön", "jung", "alt"],
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "correctAnswers": 2,
    "id": "f644bd90-de56-462e-b58e-c50d904ad6ba",
    "questions": [{
      "correctAnswer": "Option B",
      "isCorrect": false,
      "question": "Example question 2?",
      "userAnswer": "Option A"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Option D",
      "isCorrect": false,
      "question": "Example question 4?",
      "userAnswer": "Option A"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Option C",
      "isCorrect": false,
      "question": "Example question 3?",
      "userAnswer": "Option A"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Option A",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Example question 1?",
      "userAnswer": "Option A"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Option A",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Example question 5?",
      "userAnswer": "Option A"
    }],
    "quizType": "Vocabulary",
    "score": 2.0,
    "timestamp": 1747409515451,
    "totalQuestions": 5,
    "userAnswers": ["Option A", "Option A", "Option A", "Option A", "Option A"],
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "correctAnswers": 5,
    "id": "c9bb45d3-e563-4b17-8de3-b7226a2067f7",
    "questions": [{
      "correctAnswer": "Euro",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "What is the currency used in Spain?",
      "userAnswer": "Euro"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Siesta",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "What is the traditional Spanish midday rest called?",
      "userAnswer": "Siesta"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Red and yellow",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "What color is the Spanish flag?",
      "userAnswer": "Red and yellow"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Flamenco",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Which of these is a traditional Spanish dance?",
      "userAnswer": "Flamenco"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "9-10 PM",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "What time do Spaniards typically eat dinner?",
      "userAnswer": "9-10 PM"
    }],
    "quizType": "MCQ",
    "score": 5.0,
    "timestamp": 1747409469988,
    "totalQuestions": 5,
    "userAnswers": ["Euro", "Siesta", "Red and yellow", "Flamenco", "9-10 PM"],
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "correctAnswers": 5,
    "id": "bac07fb9-7b57-42d6-9748-66e7bfb5df3d",
    "questions": [{
      "correctAnswer": "Die Rechnung, bitte",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "How do you say 'The bill, please' in German?",
      "userAnswer": "Die Rechnung, bitte"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Gibt es vegetarische Optionen?",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Translate 'Is there a vegetarian option?' to German",
      "userAnswer": "Gibt es vegetarische Optionen?"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Ich bin allergisch gegen Nüsse",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Translate 'I am allergic to nuts' to German",
      "userAnswer": "Ich bin allergisch gegen Nüsse"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Dieses Essen ist köstlich",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "How do you say 'This food is delicious' in German?",
      "userAnswer": "Dieses Essen ist köstlich"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Ich möchte bestellen",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Translate 'I would like to order' to German",
      "userAnswer": "Ich möchte bestellen"
    }],
    "quizType": "Translation",
    "score": 5.0,
    "timestamp": 1747403850049,
    "totalQuestions": 5,
    "userAnswers": ["Die Rechnung, bitte", "Gibt es vegetarische Optionen?", "Ich bin allergisch gegen Nüsse", "Dieses Essen ist köstlich", "Ich möchte bestellen"],
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "correctAnswers": 5,
    "id": "e75bb361-c95b-4941-996b-b443b314a70a",
    "questions": [{
      "correctAnswer": "Bordeaux",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Which French region is known for its wine production?",
      "userAnswer": "Bordeaux"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Mediterranean Sea",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Which sea borders the south of France?",
      "userAnswer": "Mediterranean Sea"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Loire",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Which is the longest river in France?",
      "userAnswer": "Loire"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "The Alps",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Which mountain range is found in France?",
      "userAnswer": "The Alps"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Portugal",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Which is NOT a neighboring country of France?",
      "userAnswer": "Portugal"
    }],
    "quizType": "MCQ",
    "score": 5.0,
    "timestamp": 1747403791636,
    "totalQuestions": 5,
    "userAnswers": ["Bordeaux", "Mediterranean Sea", "Loire", "The Alps", "Portugal"],
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "correctAnswers": 4,
    "id": "fd2d95a7-5bf7-41b1-a8fc-828bad308633",
    "questions": [{
      "correctAnswer": "Euro",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "What is the currency used in France?",
      "userAnswer": "Euro"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "French",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "What is the most widely spoken language in France?",
      "userAnswer": "French"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Bonjour",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "What is the typical French greeting?",
      "userAnswer": "Bonjour"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "A type of bread",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "What is a 'baguette'?",
      "userAnswer": "A type of bread"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Chanel",
      "isCorrect": false,
      "question": "Which of these is a famous French fashion brand?",
      "userAnswer": "i"
    }],
    "quizType": "MCQ",
    "score": 4.0,
    "timestamp": 1747403760845,
    "totalQuestions": 5,
    "userAnswers": ["Euro", "French", "Bonjour", "A type of bread", "i"],
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "correctAnswers": 5,
    "id": "21de6fa7-e00f-44cf-8068-12a98051c61c",
    "questions": [{
      "correctAnswer": "A type of bread",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "What is a 'baguette'?",
      "userAnswer": "A type of bread"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "French",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "What is the most widely spoken language in France?",
      "userAnswer": "French"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Euro",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "What is the currency used in France?",
      "userAnswer": "Euro"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Bonjour",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "What is the typical French greeting?",
      "userAnswer": "Bonjour"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Chanel",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Which of these is a famous French fashion brand?",
      "userAnswer": "Chanel"
    }],
    "quizType": "MCQ",
    "score": 5.0,
    "timestamp": 1747403448507,
    "totalQuestions": 5,
    "userAnswers": ["A type of bread", "French", "Euro", "Bonjour", "Chanel"],
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "correctAnswers": 5,
    "id": "6db715de-6a9a-4ff0-b737-0e22c0bd7d15",
    "questions": [{
      "correctAnswer": "The Alps",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Which mountain range is found in France?",
      "userAnswer": "The Alps"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Mediterranean Sea",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Which sea borders the south of France?",
      "userAnswer": "Mediterranean Sea"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Bordeaux",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Which French region is known for its wine production?",
      "userAnswer": "Bordeaux"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Loire",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Which is the longest river in France?",
      "userAnswer": "Loire"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Portugal",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Which is NOT a neighboring country of France?",
      "userAnswer": "Portugal"
    }],
    "quizType": "MCQ",
    "score": 5.0,
    "timestamp": 1747403330208,
    "totalQuestions": 5,
    "userAnswers": ["The Alps", "Mediterranean Sea", "Bordeaux", "Loire", "Portugal"],
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "correctAnswers": 5,
    "id": "104b0e19-9d85-4df0-bf7c-905b6309d26b",
    "questions": [{
      "correctAnswer": "The Louvre",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Which famous museum is located in Paris?",
      "userAnswer": "The Louvre"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Camembert",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Which of these is a traditional French cheese?",
      "userAnswer": "Camembert"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Escargots",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Which French dish consists of snails cooked with garlic and butter?",
      "userAnswer": "Escargots"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Paris",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Which city is the capital of France?",
      "userAnswer": "Paris"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Blue, white, and red",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "What colors are on the French flag?",
      "userAnswer": "Blue, white, and red"
    }],
    "quizType": "MCQ",
    "score": 5.0,
    "timestamp": 1747403304875,
    "totalQuestions": 5,
    "userAnswers": ["The Louvre", "Camembert", "Escargots", "Paris", "Blue, white, and red"],
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "correctAnswers": 5,
    "id": "1440e80b-5f44-402c-9934-1ee22bb582e2",
    "questions": [{
      "correctAnswer": "The Alps",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Which mountain range is found in France?",
      "userAnswer": "The Alps"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Mediterranean Sea",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Which sea borders the south of France?",
      "userAnswer": "Mediterranean Sea"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Loire",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Which is the longest river in France?",
      "userAnswer": "Loire"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Bordeaux",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Which French region is known for its wine production?",
      "userAnswer": "Bordeaux"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Portugal",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Which is NOT a neighboring country of France?",
      "userAnswer": "Portugal"
    }],
    "quizType": "MCQ",
    "score": 5.0,
    "timestamp": 1747402805599,
    "totalQuestions": 5,
    "userAnswers": ["The Alps", "Mediterranean Sea", "Loire", "Bordeaux", "Portugal"],
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "correctAnswers": 5,
    "id": "11b74ace-5c8e-4d5a-9997-f1e65ef968d2",
    "questions": [{
      "correctAnswer": "Portugal",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Which is NOT a neighboring country of France?",
      "userAnswer": "Portugal"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Mediterranean Sea",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Which sea borders the south of France?",
      "userAnswer": "Mediterranean Sea"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "The Alps",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Which mountain range is found in France?",
      "userAnswer": "The Alps"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Bordeaux",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Which French region is known for its wine production?",
      "userAnswer": "Bordeaux"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Loire",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Which is the longest river in France?",
      "userAnswer": "Loire"
    }],
    "quizType": "MCQ",
    "score": 5.0,
    "timestamp": 1747402722298,
    "totalQuestions": 5,
    "userAnswers": ["Portugal", "Mediterranean Sea", "The Alps", "Bordeaux", "Loire"],
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "correctAnswers": 3,
    "id": "ae142bbd-e6f9-4f8b-b92e-b1743715883a",
    "questions": [{
      "correctAnswer": "Mallorca",
      "isCorrect": false,
      "question": "Which of these Spanish islands is located in the Mediterranean Sea?",
      "userAnswer": ""
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Ebro",
      "isCorrect": false,
      "question": "Which is the longest river in Spain?",
      "userAnswer": "exit uz"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Eagle",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Which animal is featured on the Spanish coat of arms?",
      "userAnswer": "Eagle"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Pyrenees",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Which mountain range runs along the border between Spain and France?",
      "userAnswer": "Pyrenees"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Pamplona",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Which Spanish city is famous for the 'Running of the Bulls'?",
      "userAnswer": "Pamplona"
    }],
    "quizType": "MCQ",
    "score": 3.0,
    "timestamp": 1747402517756,
    "totalQuestions": 5,
    "userAnswers": ["", "exit uz", "Eagle", "Pyrenees", "Pamplona"],
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "correctAnswers": 5,
    "id": "6b1b6800-1634-427a-a787-f9d69c62398b",
    "questions": [{
      "correctAnswer": "A type of bread",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "What is a 'baguette'?",
      "userAnswer": "A type of bread"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Chanel",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Which of these is a famous French fashion brand?",
      "userAnswer": "Chanel"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "French",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "What is the most widely spoken language in France?",
      "userAnswer": "French"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Euro",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "What is the currency used in France?",
      "userAnswer": "Euro"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Bonjour",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "What is the typical French greeting?",
      "userAnswer": "Bonjour"
    }],
    "quizType": "MCQ",
    "score": 5.0,
    "timestamp": 1747400628348,
    "totalQuestions": 5,
    "userAnswers": ["A type of bread", "Chanel", "French", "Euro", "Bonjour"],
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "correctAnswers": 5,
    "id": "d3692870-4dba-4043-b777-c3cb8b8f9763",
    "questions": [{
      "correctAnswer": "Paris",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Which city is the capital of France?",
      "userAnswer": "Paris"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Camembert",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Which of these is a traditional French cheese?",
      "userAnswer": "Camembert"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Escargots",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Which French dish consists of snails cooked with garlic and butter?",
      "userAnswer": "Escargots"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Blue, white, and red",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "What colors are on the French flag?",
      "userAnswer": "Blue, white, and red"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "The Louvre",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Which famous museum is located in Paris?",
      "userAnswer": "The Louvre"
    }],
    "quizType": "MCQ",
    "score": 5.0,
    "timestamp": 1747400463819,
    "totalQuestions": 5,
    "userAnswers": ["Paris", "Camembert", "Escargots", "Blue, white, and red", "The Louvre"],
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "correctAnswers": 5,
    "id": "1c5913fc-0f6a-43e2-bc63-968160297f01",
    "questions": [{
      "correctAnswer": "des animaux",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Which is the correct plural form of 'un animal'?",
      "userAnswer": "des animaux"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "le",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Which article is correct: ___ livre",
      "userAnswer": "le"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "une amie",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Which is the correct feminine form of 'un ami'?",
      "userAnswer": "une amie"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "la",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Which article is correct: ___ voiture",
      "userAnswer": "la"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "l'",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Which article is correct: ___ ami",
      "userAnswer": "l'"
    }],
    "quizType": "Grammar",
    "score": 5.0,
    "timestamp": 1747400449572,
    "totalQuestions": 5,
    "userAnswers": ["des animaux", "le", "une amie", "la", "l'"],
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "correctAnswers": 0,
    "id": "99ee99b8-acf6-4086-b35c-622f2fbc1194",
    "questions": [{
      "correctAnswer": "The Alps",
      "isCorrect": false,
      "question": "Which mountain range is found in France?",
      "userAnswer": "4"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Bordeaux",
      "isCorrect": false,
      "question": "Which French region is known for its wine production?",
      "userAnswer": "4"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Loire",
      "isCorrect": false,
      "question": "Which is the longest river in France?",
      "userAnswer": "4"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Portugal",
      "isCorrect": false,
      "question": "Which is NOT a neighboring country of France?",
      "userAnswer": "4"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Mediterranean Sea",
      "isCorrect": false,
      "question": "Which sea borders the south of France?",
      "userAnswer": "4"
    }],
    "quizType": "MCQ",
    "score": 0.0,
    "timestamp": 1747400111098,
    "totalQuestions": 5,
    "userAnswers": ["4", "4", "4", "4", "4"],
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "correctAnswers": 4,
    "id": "209a8294-b703-4cdc-b082-153b1bfde537",
    "questions": [{
      "correctAnswer": "Portugal",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Which is NOT a neighboring country of France?",
      "userAnswer": "Portugal"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Loire",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Which is the longest river in France?",
      "userAnswer": "Loire"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Bordeaux",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Which French region is known for its wine production?",
      "userAnswer": "Bordeaux"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "The Alps",
      "isCorrect": false,
      "question": "Which mountain range is found in France?",
      "userAnswer": "aa"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Mediterranean Sea",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Which sea borders the south of France?",
      "userAnswer": "Mediterranean Sea"
    }],
    "quizType": "MCQ",
    "score": 4.0,
    "timestamp": 1747400097906,
    "totalQuestions": 5,
    "userAnswers": ["Portugal", "Loire", "Bordeaux", "aa", "Mediterranean Sea"],
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "correctAnswers": 4,
    "id": "14fabba4-747f-45aa-bdc2-5d87902aeca8",
    "questions": [{
      "correctAnswer": "en",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Which preposition completes: 'Je vais ___ France'?",
      "userAnswer": "en"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "en",
      "isCorrect": false,
      "question": "Which preposition completes: 'Je voyage ___ avion'?",
      "userAnswer": ""
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "sur",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Which preposition completes: 'Le livre est ___ la table'?",
      "userAnswer": "sur"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "du",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Which preposition completes: 'Je viens ___ Canada'?",
      "userAnswer": "du"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "à",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Which preposition completes: 'Je vais ___ Paris'?",
      "userAnswer": "à"
    }],
    "quizType": "Grammar",
    "score": 4.0,
    "timestamp": 1747399756860,
    "totalQuestions": 5,
    "userAnswers": ["en", "", "sur", "du", "à"],
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "correctAnswers": 5,
    "id": "2855ab14-b851-44de-8906-b746f61060c0",
    "questions": [{
      "correctAnswer": "à",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Which preposition completes: 'Je vais ___ Paris'?",
      "userAnswer": "à"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "sur",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Which preposition completes: 'Le livre est ___ la table'?",
      "userAnswer": "sur"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "en",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Which preposition completes: 'Je voyage ___ avion'?",
      "userAnswer": "en"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "du",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Which preposition completes: 'Je viens ___ Canada'?",
      "userAnswer": "du"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "en",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Which preposition completes: 'Je vais ___ France'?",
      "userAnswer": "en"
    }],
    "quizType": "Grammar",
    "score": 5.0,
    "timestamp": 1747340094275,
    "totalQuestions": 5,
    "userAnswers": ["à", "sur", "en", "du", "en"],
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "correctAnswers": 4,
    "id": "4a7d3d79-ab1e-44a3-8d3b-1c7f650001c2",
    "questions": [{
      "correctAnswer": "The Louvre",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Which famous museum is located in Paris?",
      "userAnswer": "The Louvre"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Escargots",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Which French dish consists of snails cooked with garlic and butter?",
      "userAnswer": "Escargots"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Blue, white, and red",
      "isCorrect": false,
      "question": "What colors are on the French flag?",
      "userAnswer": ""
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Camembert",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Which of these is a traditional French cheese?",
      "userAnswer": "Camembert"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Paris",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Which city is the capital of France?",
      "userAnswer": "Paris"
    }],
    "quizType": "MCQ",
    "score": 4.0,
    "timestamp": 1747215553638,
    "totalQuestions": 5,
    "userAnswers": ["The Louvre", "Escargots", "", "Camembert", "Paris"],
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "correctAnswers": 5,
    "id": "ce575314-32a1-41db-a323-496213866970",
    "questions": [{
      "correctAnswer": "la",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Which article is correct: ___ voiture",
      "userAnswer": "la"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "le",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Which article is correct: ___ livre",
      "userAnswer": "le"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "des animaux",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Which is the correct plural form of 'un animal'?",
      "userAnswer": "des animaux"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "une amie",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Which is the correct feminine form of 'un ami'?",
      "userAnswer": "une amie"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "l'",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Which article is correct: ___ ami",
      "userAnswer": "l'"
    }],
    "quizType": "Grammar",
    "score": 5.0,
    "timestamp": 1747215546525,
    "totalQuestions": 5,
    "userAnswers": ["la", "le", "des animaux", "une amie", "l'"],
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "correctAnswers": 5,
    "id": "53f4e7bc-6a07-421b-adbc-d58f65514836",
    "questions": [{
      "correctAnswer": "French",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "What is the most widely spoken language in France?",
      "userAnswer": "French"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "A type of bread",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "What is a 'baguette'?",
      "userAnswer": "A type of bread"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Euro",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "What is the currency used in France?",
      "userAnswer": "Euro"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Chanel",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Which of these is a famous French fashion brand?",
      "userAnswer": "Chanel"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Bonjour",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "What is the typical French greeting?",
      "userAnswer": "Bonjour"
    }],
    "quizType": "MCQ",
    "score": 5.0,
    "timestamp": 1747215525470,
    "totalQuestions": 5,
    "userAnswers": ["French", "A type of bread", "Euro", "Chanel", "Bonjour"],
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "correctAnswers": 5,
    "id": "847bbcf9-533e-4b66-8ab2-c145b725eb05",
    "questions": [{
      "correctAnswer": "Mediterranean Sea",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Which sea borders the south of France?",
      "userAnswer": "Mediterranean Sea"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Bordeaux",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Which French region is known for its wine production?",
      "userAnswer": "Bordeaux"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Portugal",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Which is NOT a neighboring country of France?",
      "userAnswer": "Portugal"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "The Alps",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Which mountain range is found in France?",
      "userAnswer": "The Alps"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Loire",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Which is the longest river in France?",
      "userAnswer": "Loire"
    }],
    "quizType": "MCQ",
    "score": 5.0,
    "timestamp": 1747213300293,
    "totalQuestions": 5,
    "userAnswers": ["Mediterranean Sea", "Bordeaux", "Portugal", "The Alps", "Loire"],
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "correctAnswers": 4,
    "id": "a385fa7d-4cc5-406b-8f55-1536bc27d65c",
    "questions": [{
      "correctAnswer": "Bonjour",
      "isCorrect": false,
      "question": "What is the typical French greeting?",
      "userAnswer": ""
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Euro",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "What is the currency used in France?",
      "userAnswer": "Euro"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "A type of bread",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "What is a 'baguette'?",
      "userAnswer": "A type of bread"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Chanel",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Which of these is a famous French fashion brand?",
      "userAnswer": "Chanel"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "French",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "What is the most widely spoken language in France?",
      "userAnswer": "French"
    }],
    "quizType": "MCQ",
    "score": 4.0,
    "timestamp": 1747211200653,
    "totalQuestions": 5,
    "userAnswers": ["", "Euro", "A type of bread", "Chanel", "French"],
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "correctAnswers": 4,
    "id": "1848cea6-5fb3-43f0-bddb-b90cb3334386",
    "questions": [{
      "correctAnswer": "Blue, white, and red",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "What colors are on the French flag?",
      "userAnswer": "Blue, white, and red"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Camembert",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Which of these is a traditional French cheese?",
      "userAnswer": "Camembert"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Escargots",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Which French dish consists of snails cooked with garlic and butter?",
      "userAnswer": "Escargots"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "The Louvre",
      "isCorrect": false,
      "question": "Which famous museum is located in Paris?",
      "userAnswer": "sdsd"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Paris",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Which city is the capital of France?",
      "userAnswer": "Paris"
    }],
    "quizType": "MCQ",
    "score": 4.0,
    "timestamp": 1747211107902,
    "totalQuestions": 5,
    "userAnswers": ["Blue, white, and red", "Camembert", "Escargots", "sdsd", "Paris"],
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "correctAnswers": 5,
    "id": "612234b2-7faa-4485-9a0b-b2564480ee2c",
    "questions": [{
      "correctAnswer": "Camembert",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Which of these is a traditional French cheese?",
      "userAnswer": "Camembert"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Blue, white, and red",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "What colors are on the French flag?",
      "userAnswer": "Blue, white, and red"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "The Louvre",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Which famous museum is located in Paris?",
      "userAnswer": "The Louvre"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Escargots",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Which French dish consists of snails cooked with garlic and butter?",
      "userAnswer": "Escargots"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Paris",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Which city is the capital of France?",
      "userAnswer": "Paris"
    }],
    "quizType": "MCQ",
    "score": 5.0,
    "timestamp": 1747205326374,
    "totalQuestions": 5,
    "userAnswers": ["Camembert", "Blue, white, and red", "The Louvre", "Escargots", "Paris"],
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "correctAnswers": 3,
    "id": "559c1aa3-59c3-460e-b1ac-168381ac2570",
    "questions": [{
      "correctAnswer": "Loire",
      "isCorrect": false,
      "question": "Which is the longest river in France?",
      "userAnswer": "mwc"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Portugal",
      "isCorrect": false,
      "question": "Which is NOT a neighboring country of France?",
      "userAnswer": "exit uz"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "The Alps",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Which mountain range is found in France?",
      "userAnswer": "The Alps"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Bordeaux",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Which French region is known for its wine production?",
      "userAnswer": "Bordeaux"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Mediterranean Sea",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Which sea borders the south of France?",
      "userAnswer": "Mediterranean Sea"
    }],
    "quizType": "MCQ",
    "score": 3.0,
    "timestamp": 1747173938898,
    "totalQuestions": 5,
    "userAnswers": ["mwc", "exit uz", "The Alps", "Bordeaux", "Mediterranean Sea"],
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "correctAnswers": 5,
    "id": "f2e06d34-48e7-4b88-b00d-324096d8676c",
    "questions": [{
      "correctAnswer": "The Louvre",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Which famous museum is located in Paris?",
      "userAnswer": "The Louvre"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Escargots",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Which French dish consists of snails cooked with garlic and butter?",
      "userAnswer": "Escargots"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Blue, white, and red",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "What colors are on the French flag?",
      "userAnswer": "Blue, white, and red"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Paris",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Which city is the capital of France?",
      "userAnswer": "Paris"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Camembert",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Which of these is a traditional French cheese?",
      "userAnswer": "Camembert"
    }],
    "quizType": "MCQ",
    "score": 5.0,
    "timestamp": 1747168312621,
    "totalQuestions": 5,
    "userAnswers": ["The Louvre", "Escargots", "Blue, white, and red", "Paris", "Camembert"],
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "correctAnswers": 5,
    "id": "6f350b48-db6f-4c22-b995-2335368c2827",
    "questions": [{
      "correctAnswer": "Scafell Pike",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "What is the highest mountain in England?",
      "userAnswer": "Scafell Pike"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Oxford",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Which of these is a famous English university?",
      "userAnswer": "Oxford"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Ireland",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Which of these countries is NOT part of the United Kingdom?",
      "userAnswer": "Ireland"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Thames",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Which river runs through London?",
      "userAnswer": "Thames"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Elizabeth I",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Who was the first Queen Elizabeth of England?",
      "userAnswer": "Elizabeth I"
    }],
    "quizType": "MCQ",
    "score": 5.0,
    "timestamp": 1747167909920,
    "totalQuestions": 5,
    "userAnswers": ["Scafell Pike", "Oxford", "Ireland", "Thames", "Elizabeth I"],
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "correctAnswers": 5,
    "id": "76a197ee-e87a-4f3f-bee1-ebcb2bf0c0c7",
    "questions": [{
      "correctAnswer": "A public house (bar)",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "What is a 'pub' in England?",
      "userAnswer": "A public house (bar)"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Left",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "What side of the road do the British drive on?",
      "userAnswer": "Left"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "A type of English dialect",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "What is 'Cockney rhyming slang'?",
      "userAnswer": "A type of English dialect"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Sunday roast",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "What is the traditional British meal eaten on Sunday?",
      "userAnswer": "Sunday roast"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Aston Martin",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Which of these is a British car brand?",
      "userAnswer": "Aston Martin"
    }],
    "quizType": "MCQ",
    "score": 5.0,
    "timestamp": 1747166734868,
    "totalQuestions": 5,
    "userAnswers": ["A public house (bar)", "Left", "A type of English dialect", "Sunday roast", "Aston Martin"],
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "correctAnswers": 4,
    "id": "583c2bbf-2fa5-4026-b744-c15ef478d724",
    "questions": [{
      "correctAnswer": "A type of bread",
      "isCorrect": false,
      "question": "What is a 'baguette'?",
      "userAnswer": ""
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "French",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "What is the most widely spoken language in France?",
      "userAnswer": "French"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Bonjour",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "What is the typical French greeting?",
      "userAnswer": "Bonjour"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Chanel",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Which of these is a famous French fashion brand?",
      "userAnswer": "Chanel"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Euro",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "What is the currency used in France?",
      "userAnswer": "Euro"
    }],
    "quizType": "MCQ",
    "score": 80.0,
    "timestamp": 1747164231425,
    "totalQuestions": 5,
    "userAnswers": ["", "French", "Bonjour", "Chanel", "Euro"],
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "correctAnswers": 5,
    "id": "507a730b-b446-4e9c-887b-ef8aff62a8f3",
    "questions": [{
      "correctAnswer": "French",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "What is the most widely spoken language in France?",
      "userAnswer": "French"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Chanel",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Which of these is a famous French fashion brand?",
      "userAnswer": "Chanel"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Euro",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "What is the currency used in France?",
      "userAnswer": "Euro"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "A type of bread",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "What is a 'baguette'?",
      "userAnswer": "A type of bread"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Bonjour",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "What is the typical French greeting?",
      "userAnswer": "Bonjour"
    }],
    "quizType": "MCQ",
    "score": 5.0,
    "timestamp": 1747163330983,
    "totalQuestions": 5,
    "userAnswers": ["French", "Chanel", "Euro", "A type of bread", "Bonjour"],
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "correctAnswers": 5,
    "id": "69717dce-2890-41b0-87c8-393fe11a21e5",
    "questions": [{
      "correctAnswer": "Portugal",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Which is NOT a neighboring country of France?",
      "userAnswer": "Portugal"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Bordeaux",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Which French region is known for its wine production?",
      "userAnswer": "Bordeaux"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Loire",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Which is the longest river in France?",
      "userAnswer": "Loire"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Mediterranean Sea",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Which sea borders the south of France?",
      "userAnswer": "Mediterranean Sea"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "The Alps",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Which mountain range is found in France?",
      "userAnswer": "The Alps"
    }],
    "quizType": "MCQ",
    "score": 5.0,
    "timestamp": 1747163321235,
    "totalQuestions": 5,
    "userAnswers": ["Portugal", "Bordeaux", "Loire", "Mediterranean Sea", "The Alps"],
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "correctAnswers": 3,
    "id": "581c3b4e-defe-4106-b012-0a362dc014f5",
    "questions": [{
      "correctAnswer": "New Year's Eve",
      "isCorrect": false,
      "question": "On which day do Spaniards traditionally eat twelve grapes at midnight?",
      "userAnswer": "easter"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Real Madrid",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Which Spanish football club has won the most UEFA Champions League titles?",
      "userAnswer": "Real Madrid"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Paella",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Which Spanish dish is made with rice and seafood?",
      "userAnswer": "Paella"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Pablo Picasso",
      "isCorrect": false,
      "question": "Which Spanish artist painted 'Guernica'?",
      "userAnswer": "Joan Mr"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Madrid",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Which city is the capital of Spain?",
      "userAnswer": "Madrid"
    }],
    "quizType": "MCQ",
    "score": 3.0,
    "timestamp": 1747040535827,
    "totalQuestions": 5,
    "userAnswers": ["easter", "Real Madrid", "Paella", "Joan Mr", "Madrid"],
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "correctAnswers": 5,
    "id": "8d7fbb46-30d3-4eb7-8653-e60089aa9856",
    "questions": [{
      "correctAnswer": "Eagle",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Which animal is featured on the Spanish coat of arms?",
      "userAnswer": "Eagle"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Mallorca",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Which of these Spanish islands is located in the Mediterranean Sea?",
      "userAnswer": "Mallorca"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Ebro",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Which is the longest river in Spain?",
      "userAnswer": "Ebro"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Pamplona",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Which Spanish city is famous for the 'Running of the Bulls'?",
      "userAnswer": "Pamplona"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Pyrenees",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Which mountain range runs along the border between Spain and France?",
      "userAnswer": "Pyrenees"
    }],
    "quizType": "MCQ",
    "score": 5.0,
    "timestamp": 1746900285128,
    "totalQuestions": 5,
    "userAnswers": ["Eagle", "Mallorca", "Ebro", "Pamplona", "Pyrenees"],
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "correctAnswers": 5,
    "id": "9288feeb-b3a7-4be9-ae95-a5e800fa83ed",
    "questions": [{
      "correctAnswer": "9-10 PM",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "What time do Spaniards typically eat dinner?",
      "userAnswer": "9-10 PM"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Euro",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "What is the currency used in Spain?",
      "userAnswer": "Euro"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Siesta",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "What is the traditional Spanish midday rest called?",
      "userAnswer": "Siesta"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Flamenco",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Which of these is a traditional Spanish dance?",
      "userAnswer": "Flamenco"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Red and yellow",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "What color is the Spanish flag?",
      "userAnswer": "Red and yellow"
    }],
    "quizType": "MCQ",
    "score": 5.0,
    "timestamp": 1746900269548,
    "totalQuestions": 5,
    "userAnswers": ["9-10 PM", "Euro", "Siesta", "Flamenco", "Red and yellow"],
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "correctAnswers": 1,
    "id": "bb5ea3a4-8476-479d-b79a-3c9c1e7285a5",
    "questions": [{
      "correctAnswer": "de",
      "isCorrect": false,
      "question": "Which preposition completes: 'El libro es ___ Juan'?",
      "userAnswer": "a"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "en",
      "isCorrect": false,
      "question": "Which preposition completes: 'Viajo ___ tren'?",
      "userAnswer": "a"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "a",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Which preposition completes: 'Voy ___ Madrid'?",
      "userAnswer": "a"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "en",
      "isCorrect": false,
      "question": "Which preposition completes: 'Vivo ___ España'?",
      "userAnswer": "a"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "con",
      "isCorrect": false,
      "question": "Which preposition completes: 'Hablo ___ mi amigo'?",
      "userAnswer": "a"
    }],
    "quizType": "Grammar",
    "score": 1.0,
    "timestamp": 1746900033948,
    "totalQuestions": 5,
    "userAnswers": ["a", "a", "a", "a", "a"],
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "correctAnswers": 5,
    "id": "764b9f8e-d1ee-4304-a3cb-1620aa5d091a",
    "questions": [{
      "correctAnswer": "Pablo Picasso",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Which Spanish artist painted 'Guernica'?",
      "userAnswer": "Pablo Picasso"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Madrid",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Which city is the capital of Spain?",
      "userAnswer": "Madrid"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Paella",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Which Spanish dish is made with rice and seafood?",
      "userAnswer": "Paella"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "New Year's Eve",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "On which day do Spaniards traditionally eat twelve grapes at midnight?",
      "userAnswer": "New Year's Eve"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Real Madrid",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Which Spanish football club has won the most UEFA Champions League titles?",
      "userAnswer": "Real Madrid"
    }],
    "quizType": "MCQ",
    "score": 5.0,
    "timestamp": 1746900007598,
    "totalQuestions": 5,
    "userAnswers": ["Pablo Picasso", "Madrid", "Paella", "New Year's Eve", "Real Madrid"],
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "correctAnswers": 1,
    "id": "900e8e40-7435-4e12-a59b-ecbe758490c9",
    "questions": [{
      "correctAnswer": "Pamplona",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Which Spanish city is famous for the 'Running of the Bulls'?",
      "userAnswer": "Pamplona"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Pyrenees",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Which mountain range runs along the border between Spain and France?",
      "userAnswer": "Pyrenees"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Ebro",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Which is the longest river in Spain?",
      "userAnswer": "Ebro"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Mallorca",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Which of these Spanish islands is located in the Mediterranean Sea?",
      "userAnswer": "Mallorca"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Eagle",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Which animal is featured on the Spanish coat of arms?",
      "userAnswer": "Eagle"
    }],
    "quizType": "MCQ",
    "score": 5.0,
    "timestamp": 1746898564628,
    "totalQuestions": 5,
    "userAnswers": ["Pamplona", "Pyrenees", "Ebro", "Mallorca", "Eagle"],
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }, {
    "correctAnswers": 1,
    "id": "4b32b14b-a143-4ed4-a07b-5a87767648b0",
    "questions": [{
      "correctAnswer": "Mallorca",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Which of these Spanish islands is located in the Mediterranean Sea?",
      "userAnswer": "Mallorca"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Pyrenees",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Which mountain range runs along the border between Spain and France?",
      "userAnswer": "Pyrenees"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Pamplona",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Which Spanish city is famous for the 'Running of the Bulls'?",
      "userAnswer": "Pamplona"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Eagle",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Which animal is featured on the Spanish coat of arms?",
      "userAnswer": "Eagle"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Ebro",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Which is the longest river in Spain?",
      "userAnswer": "Ebro"
    }],
    "quizType": "MCQ",
    "score": 5.0,
    "timestamp": 1746898368325,
    "totalQuestions": 5,
    "userAnswers": ["Mallorca", "Pyrenees", "Pamplona", "Eagle", "Ebro"],
    "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465"
  }],
  "userId": "fb3f2991-2a99-4217-838a-71013cf35465",
  "username": "mazen"
}, {
  "email": "uua",
  "interactions": [{
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "e24b82cc-4a55-426a-ae1a-01f00d397516",
    "question": "What type of quiz would you like to take?",
    "response": "vocabulary",
    "timestamp": 1747424984174,
    "userId": "9aaf8a6d-9ba2-4fe3-9f84-0c300339ffd9"
  }, {
    "category": "system",
    "id": "0539f6c2-3d11-4519-9dd5-94907c643657",
    "question": "settings",
    "response": "Displayed user settings",
    "timestamp": 1747424972049,
    "userId": "9aaf8a6d-9ba2-4fe3-9f84-0c300339ffd9"
  }, {
    "category": "system",
    "id": "c39ec566-4a1d-4762-adb0-8d97f24a6b28",
    "question": "help",
    "response": "\r\nAvailable commands:\r\n1. chat - Start a conversation\r\n2. quiz - Take a quiz\r\n3. history - View your learning history\r\n4. preferences - Set your language preferences\r\n5. help - Show this help message\r\n6. logout - Log out\r\n7. exit - Exit the application\r\n",
    "timestamp": 1747424965153,
    "userId": "9aaf8a6d-9ba2-4fe3-9f84-0c300339ffd9"
  }],
  "quizResults": [],
  "userId": "9aaf8a6d-9ba2-4fe3-9f84-0c300339ffd9",
  "username": "mo"
}, {
  "email": "123",
  "interactions": [{
    "category": "thanks",
    "id": "c6252df0-37e5-4270-a43f-913b4628c4b5",
    "question": "set difficulty level Medium",
    "response": "I'm not sure I understand. Try asking about quizzes, changing settings.",
    "timestamp": 1747587432450,
    "userId": "10d8bcc5-2a0c-4c99-bdab-bb912abee69b"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "d8393806-b872-4248-b9e2-8c4dfeb6d60e",
    "question": "exit quiz",
    "response": "Cancelled quiz setup",
    "timestamp": 1747587420334,
    "userId": "10d8bcc5-2a0c-4c99-bdab-bb912abee69b"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "8bd5d210-013e-4c86-9285-f7c815b9f2ba",
    "question": "What type of quiz would you like to take?",
    "response": "exit quiz",
    "timestamp": 1747587420328,
    "userId": "10d8bcc5-2a0c-4c99-bdab-bb912abee69b"
  }, {
    "category": "system",
    "id": "67a1db76-7ce2-4183-a418-7a67490ecbc9",
    "question": "settings",
    "response": "Displayed user settings",
    "timestamp": 1747587408879,
    "userId": "10d8bcc5-2a0c-4c99-bdab-bb912abee69b"
  }, {
    "category": "settings",
    "id": "0e1ae04a-e20d-4753-a48a-d791bd5d3355",
    "question": "set target language spanish",
    "response": "Target language set to Spanish",
    "timestamp": 1747587404837,
    "userId": "10d8bcc5-2a0c-4c99-bdab-bb912abee69b"
  }, {
    "category": "settings",
    "id": "a2f98e96-933c-47c4-a653-96b445a8b3bc",
    "question": "set mother language english",
    "response": "Mother language set to English",
    "timestamp": 1747587393716,
    "userId": "10d8bcc5-2a0c-4c99-bdab-bb912abee69b"
  }, {
    "category": "system",
    "id": "e5728801-6778-49e2-bd8b-6be14804e786",
    "question": "settings",
    "response": "Displayed user settings",
    "timestamp": 1747587373463,
    "userId": "10d8bcc5-2a0c-4c99-bdab-bb912abee69b"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "ef08fb2f-af98-4847-945f-08ab32de0e42",
    "question": "exit quiz",
    "response": "Cancelled quiz setup",
    "timestamp": 1747587368701,
    "userId": "10d8bcc5-2a0c-4c99-bdab-bb912abee69b"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "29bf27ec-5399-4315-be0a-f7de1cb8a03d",
    "question": "What type of quiz would you like to take?",
    "response": "exit quiz",
    "timestamp": 1747587368683,
    "userId": "10d8bcc5-2a0c-4c99-bdab-bb912abee69b"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "bb4aa99f-9376-44de-8a54-24e972fdd08f",
    "question": "What type of quiz would you like to take?",
    "response": "settings",
    "timestamp": 1747587361523,
    "userId": "10d8bcc5-2a0c-4c99-bdab-bb912abee69b"
  }, {
    "category": "thanks",
    "id": "eb54c43e-9ec0-4675-a781-0ee6f382e217",
    "question": "set difficulty hard",
    "response": "I'm not sure I understand. Try asking about quizzes, changing settings.",
    "timestamp": 1747586186944,
    "userId": "10d8bcc5-2a0c-4c99-bdab-bb912abee69b"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "ce878262-1b56-453d-8492-48331a6519f0",
    "question": "exit quiz",
    "response": "Cancelled quiz setup",
    "timestamp": 1747586175228,
    "userId": "10d8bcc5-2a0c-4c99-bdab-bb912abee69b"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "e924166c-fae2-48ee-b9e6-e767ba3093f5",
    "question": "What type of quiz would you like to take?",
    "response": "exit quiz",
    "timestamp": 1747586175223,
    "userId": "10d8bcc5-2a0c-4c99-bdab-bb912abee69b"
  }, {
    "category": "settings",
    "id": "3d144311-ccfd-4e8e-a5ad-a1caac6bbd42",
    "question": "set target language spanish",
    "response": "Target language set to Spanish",
    "timestamp": 1747586163292,
    "userId": "10d8bcc5-2a0c-4c99-bdab-bb912abee69b"
  }, {
    "category": "settings",
    "id": "e2378fb4-18fe-46ab-a627-980ae00c381a",
    "question": "set mother language french",
    "response": "Mother language set to French",
    "timestamp": 1747586156733,
    "userId": "10d8bcc5-2a0c-4c99-bdab-bb912abee69b"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "7d542fcb-8382-4e04-b722-ab5d0b92c82a",
    "question": "exit quiz",
    "response": "Cancelled quiz setup",
    "timestamp": 1747586145377,
    "userId": "10d8bcc5-2a0c-4c99-bdab-bb912abee69b"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "f2926508-1677-499b-9776-2ecf896c104a",
    "question": "What type of quiz would you like to take?",
    "response": "exit quiz",
    "timestamp": 1747586145371,
    "userId": "10d8bcc5-2a0c-4c99-bdab-bb912abee69b"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "f6555c87-91a5-45e8-87ba-2462cd002e7c",
    "question": "exit quiz",
    "response": "Cancelled quiz setup",
    "timestamp": 1747586134974,
    "userId": "10d8bcc5-2a0c-4c99-bdab-bb912abee69b"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "8972cde8-17b5-4734-81b9-67af0209532a",
    "question": "What type of quiz would you like to take?",
    "response": "exit quiz",
    "timestamp": 1747586134969,
    "userId": "10d8bcc5-2a0c-4c99-bdab-bb912abee69b"
  }, {
    "category": "system",
    "id": "16408153-3050-446e-a86e-b492e9d4d1fd",
    "question": "settings",
    "response": "Displayed user settings",
    "timestamp": 1747586103479,
    "userId": "10d8bcc5-2a0c-4c99-bdab-bb912abee69b"
  }, {
    "category": "settings",
    "id": "fcb3bc99-6fb2-4315-8ef7-145e189afdc3",
    "question": "set target language french",
    "response": "Target language set to French",
    "timestamp": 1747586098250,
    "userId": "10d8bcc5-2a0c-4c99-bdab-bb912abee69b"
  }, {
    "category": "settings",
    "id": "8ab5115f-98d9-453f-b00b-f7ad8826a61e",
    "question": "set mother language spanish",
    "response": "Mother language set to Spanish",
    "timestamp": 1747586088068,
    "userId": "10d8bcc5-2a0c-4c99-bdab-bb912abee69b"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "ccfeefb1-d0f0-4d5f-b2a5-21f410c6e0a7",
    "question": "exit quiz",
    "response": "Cancelled quiz setup",
    "timestamp": 1747586077150,
    "userId": "10d8bcc5-2a0c-4c99-bdab-bb912abee69b"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "8c993695-3b82-4cdc-ae9c-e80b9f87155a",
    "question": "What type of quiz would you like to take?",
    "response": "exit quiz",
    "timestamp": 1747586077144,
    "userId": "10d8bcc5-2a0c-4c99-bdab-bb912abee69b"
  }, {
    "category": "system",
    "id": "78eef653-4c94-4ccc-8741-b5f325a96fc0",
    "question": "analytics",
    "response": "Displayed user analytics",
    "timestamp": 1747586030816,
    "userId": "10d8bcc5-2a0c-4c99-bdab-bb912abee69b"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "00665f1d-8705-45ad-b7e8-e8806c64bd60",
    "question": "Quiz Question 5: What is 'door' in Spanish?",
    "response": "Answer: c, Feedback: That's not correct. The correct answer is: puerta",
    "timestamp": 1747586020973,
    "userId": "10d8bcc5-2a0c-4c99-bdab-bb912abee69b"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "28f32178-4b6b-41c8-a946-e53f9d03f6bc",
    "question": "Quiz Question 4: What is 'house' in Spanish?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747586020409,
    "userId": "10d8bcc5-2a0c-4c99-bdab-bb912abee69b"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "2c4191fd-b6a0-4e12-ad96-5d0cb1f27ca7",
    "question": "Quiz Question 3: What is 'cshair' in Spanish?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747586019130,
    "userId": "10d8bcc5-2a0c-4c99-bdab-bb912abee69b"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "5dd77767-a357-4d54-87cd-350817c59491",
    "question": "Quiz Question 2: What is 'table' in Spanish?",
    "response": "Answer: c, Feedback: That's not correct. The correct answer is: mesa",
    "timestamp": 1747586018445,
    "userId": "10d8bcc5-2a0c-4c99-bdab-bb912abee69b"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "c4761574-b07e-4d22-b6b6-f4ba15af029c",
    "question": "Quiz Question 1: What is 'bed' in Spanish?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747586015227,
    "userId": "10d8bcc5-2a0c-4c99-bdab-bb912abee69b"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "36392839-ba94-4b4b-a25c-8c002429a72a",
    "question": "What type of quiz would you like to take?",
    "response": "1",
    "timestamp": 1747586014383,
    "userId": "10d8bcc5-2a0c-4c99-bdab-bb912abee69b"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "07451afe-c766-468f-b625-80497f8ef551",
    "question": "exit quiz",
    "response": "Cancelled quiz setup",
    "timestamp": 1747585989899,
    "userId": "10d8bcc5-2a0c-4c99-bdab-bb912abee69b"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "3d1b0d7b-3899-4cc9-ac4b-193d71e1d3b5",
    "question": "What type of quiz would you like to take?",
    "response": "exit quiz",
    "timestamp": 1747585989891,
    "userId": "10d8bcc5-2a0c-4c99-bdab-bb912abee69b"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "8ce920dc-5e65-425f-a97b-1515c8e4d3b2",
    "question": "What type of quiz would you like to take?",
    "response": "exit the quiz",
    "timestamp": 1747585984095,
    "userId": "10d8bcc5-2a0c-4c99-bdab-bb912abee69b"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "c6f83663-00e8-484e-bf7f-793d8d7531db",
    "question": "exit quiz",
    "response": "Cancelled quiz setup",
    "timestamp": 1747585960846,
    "userId": "10d8bcc5-2a0c-4c99-bdab-bb912abee69b"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "1232bf67-bc73-4f57-80dc-9744293ab71b",
    "question": "What type of quiz would you like to take?",
    "response": "exit quiz",
    "timestamp": 1747585960809,
    "userId": "10d8bcc5-2a0c-4c99-bdab-bb912abee69b"
  }, {
    "category": "unknown",
    "id": "54ce8309-92d4-4216-8646-c02575790ee3",
    "question": "",
    "response": "I'm not sure I understand. Try asking about quizzes, changing settings.",
    "timestamp": 1747585536595,
    "userId": "10d8bcc5-2a0c-4c99-bdab-bb912abee69b"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz_request",
    "id": "97cee379-b8b6-44d0-a745-088a68698893",
    "question": "i want start quiz",
    "response": "¿Qué tipo de cuestionario te gustaría realizar? Ofrecemos:\r\n1. Vocabulario - Pon a prueba tu conocimiento de palabras\r\n2. Gramática - Practica reglas del lenguaje\r\n3. Traducción - Traduce entre idiomas\r\n4. Opción múltiple (MCQ) - Preguntas generales de idioma\r\n\r\nPor favor, escribe el número (1-4) o el nombre del cuestionario que deseas realizar.",
    "timestamp": 1747585536478,
    "userId": "10d8bcc5-2a0c-4c99-bdab-bb912abee69b"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "1ec5b793-9243-40c3-b7aa-1105e7d45a1b",
    "question": "exit quiz",
    "response": "Cancelled quiz setup",
    "timestamp": 1747585530531,
    "userId": "10d8bcc5-2a0c-4c99-bdab-bb912abee69b"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "50fe61a8-f3c0-414b-bd1e-fe424dc9b0aa",
    "question": "What type of quiz would you like to take?",
    "response": "exit quiz",
    "timestamp": 1747585530526,
    "userId": "10d8bcc5-2a0c-4c99-bdab-bb912abee69b"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "860bcc8b-0477-4890-a135-c386d57dab78",
    "question": "What type of quiz would you like to take?",
    "response": "i want quiz",
    "timestamp": 1747585523470,
    "userId": "10d8bcc5-2a0c-4c99-bdab-bb912abee69b"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "8087c15d-035a-4d2e-b0fb-fff1965fdf82",
    "question": "Quiz Question 5: What is 'banana' in Spanish?",
    "response": "Answer: f, Feedback: That's not correct. The correct answer is: plátano",
    "timestamp": 1747585464938,
    "userId": "10d8bcc5-2a0c-4c99-bdab-bb912abee69b"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "51ce1c67-14aa-4b45-865a-3ba94c2525c2",
    "question": "Quiz Question 4: What is 'bread' in Spanish?",
    "response": "Answer: d, Feedback: That's not correct. The correct answer is: pan",
    "timestamp": 1747585464260,
    "userId": "10d8bcc5-2a0c-4c99-bdab-bb912abee69b"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "cc62be34-8941-4366-9cf0-99766484c058",
    "question": "Quiz Question 3: What is 'apple' in Spanish?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747585463709,
    "userId": "10d8bcc5-2a0c-4c99-bdab-bb912abee69b"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "275a5e09-d347-4f25-82ad-c874d2d74406",
    "question": "Quiz Question 2: What is 'cheese' in Spanish?",
    "response": "Answer: s, Feedback: That's not correct. The correct answer is: queso",
    "timestamp": 1747585462321,
    "userId": "10d8bcc5-2a0c-4c99-bdab-bb912abee69b"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "73905411-1e99-4cf0-b89d-58ed15aecbc2",
    "question": "Quiz Question 1: What is 'water' in Spanish?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747585461765,
    "userId": "10d8bcc5-2a0c-4c99-bdab-bb912abee69b"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "dea043b3-e152-4b57-88dd-935e34b86e93",
    "question": "What type of quiz would you like to take?",
    "response": "vocab",
    "timestamp": 1747585459972,
    "userId": "10d8bcc5-2a0c-4c99-bdab-bb912abee69b"
  }, {
    "category": "system",
    "id": "79254d84-f526-4536-a093-b86b7aacfe7d",
    "question": "save settings",
    "response": "Attempted to save user settings",
    "timestamp": 1747585448205,
    "userId": "10d8bcc5-2a0c-4c99-bdab-bb912abee69b"
  }, {
    "category": "settings",
    "id": "76f6d62c-7f34-490b-9ce3-0f2279629cc3",
    "question": "set target language spanish",
    "response": "Target language set to Spanish",
    "timestamp": 1747585440006,
    "userId": "10d8bcc5-2a0c-4c99-bdab-bb912abee69b"
  }, {
    "category": "settings",
    "id": "1cd14041-4492-4610-b942-697aae902992",
    "question": "set mother language english",
    "response": "Mother language set to English",
    "timestamp": 1747585426601,
    "userId": "10d8bcc5-2a0c-4c99-bdab-bb912abee69b"
  }, {
    "category": "thanks",
    "id": "167c8d67-2f79-4c5b-897b-9ea0a2c66c62",
    "question": "set difficulty hard",
    "response": "I'm not sure I understand. Try asking about quizzes, changing settings.",
    "timestamp": 1747585400370,
    "userId": "10d8bcc5-2a0c-4c99-bdab-bb912abee69b"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz_request",
    "id": "dfe0d58c-93b4-4b10-a353-67d54bc3ce6d",
    "question": "uiz",
    "response": "¿Qué tipo de cuestionario te gustaría realizar? Ofrecemos:\r\n1. Vocabulario - Pon a prueba tu conocimiento de palabras\r\n2. Gramática - Practica reglas del lenguaje\r\n3. Traducción - Traduce entre idiomas\r\n4. Opción múltiple (MCQ) - Preguntas generales de idioma\r\n\r\nPor favor, escribe el número (1-4) o el nombre del cuestionario que deseas realizar.",
    "timestamp": 1747585039566,
    "userId": "10d8bcc5-2a0c-4c99-bdab-bb912abee69b"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "93a65bcf-b9a7-4f33-a3b6-b0ec96d34f47",
    "question": "Quiz Question 5: Which city is the capital of Spain?",
    "response": "Answer: d, Feedback: That's not correct. The correct answer is: Madrid",
    "timestamp": 1747585012357,
    "userId": "10d8bcc5-2a0c-4c99-bdab-bb912abee69b"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "9506fa2b-d27a-4220-89a1-8c25c48d99a0",
    "question": "Quiz Question 4: Which Spanish dish is made with rice and seafood?",
    "response": "Answer: s, Feedback: That's not correct. The correct answer is: Paella",
    "timestamp": 1747585011816,
    "userId": "10d8bcc5-2a0c-4c99-bdab-bb912abee69b"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "2acf9fde-54b9-443f-9060-7a53557020ab",
    "question": "Quiz Question 3: On which day do Spaniards traditionally eat twelve grapes at midnight?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747585011223,
    "userId": "10d8bcc5-2a0c-4c99-bdab-bb912abee69b"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "64c40c8a-22d8-4287-9108-43715171f0ca",
    "question": "Quiz Question 2: Which Spanish football club has won the most UEFA Champions League titles?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747585008876,
    "userId": "10d8bcc5-2a0c-4c99-bdab-bb912abee69b"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "cf5c5355-f82d-48fc-b4fb-f538ce3151c8",
    "question": "Quiz Question 1: Which Spanish artist painted 'Guernica'?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747585008558,
    "userId": "10d8bcc5-2a0c-4c99-bdab-bb912abee69b"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "d8a4a6a1-9425-4f35-ac3c-fa590266c7ee",
    "question": "What type of quiz would you like to take?",
    "response": "4",
    "timestamp": 1747585005905,
    "userId": "10d8bcc5-2a0c-4c99-bdab-bb912abee69b"
  }, {
    "category": "thanks",
    "id": "86c7c5df-3bda-4d38-8439-837553adc426",
    "question": "set difficulty Medium",
    "response": "I'm not sure I understand. Try asking about quizzes, changing settings.",
    "timestamp": 1747584995270,
    "userId": "10d8bcc5-2a0c-4c99-bdab-bb912abee69b"
  }, {
    "category": "system",
    "id": "bf4db56b-8dc8-421a-8476-0909c9b1f843",
    "question": "settings",
    "response": "Displayed user settings",
    "timestamp": 1747584985021,
    "userId": "10d8bcc5-2a0c-4c99-bdab-bb912abee69b"
  }, {
    "category": "thanks",
    "id": "1810d061-10e7-4aa1-8cfa-a8f611038920",
    "question": "set difficulty medium",
    "response": "I'm not sure I understand. Try asking about quizzes, changing settings.",
    "timestamp": 1747584968677,
    "userId": "10d8bcc5-2a0c-4c99-bdab-bb912abee69b"
  }, {
    "category": "settings",
    "id": "fa6137d8-04e7-486c-a4a0-b7e49f1aba78",
    "question": "set target language spanish",
    "response": "Target language set to Spanish",
    "timestamp": 1747584958675,
    "userId": "10d8bcc5-2a0c-4c99-bdab-bb912abee69b"
  }, {
    "category": "settings",
    "id": "a9a73bfc-e841-4e63-a848-ef02a357ec7e",
    "question": "set mother language english",
    "response": "Mother language set to English",
    "timestamp": 1747584950072,
    "userId": "10d8bcc5-2a0c-4c99-bdab-bb912abee69b"
  }, {
    "category": "thanks",
    "id": "96a8c453-b8f3-49f6-9d63-418a3c64cf2e",
    "question": "set difficulty level hard",
    "response": "I'm not sure I understand. Try asking about quizzes, changing settings.",
    "timestamp": 1747584701688,
    "userId": "10d8bcc5-2a0c-4c99-bdab-bb912abee69b"
  }, {
    "category": "thanks",
    "id": "eca0a554-5d37-483f-9499-f5650a32c146",
    "question": "set difficulty hard",
    "response": "I'm not sure I understand. Try asking about quizzes, changing settings.",
    "timestamp": 1747584679973,
    "userId": "10d8bcc5-2a0c-4c99-bdab-bb912abee69b"
  }, {
    "category": "thanks",
    "id": "6c45c466-3a1f-407d-9db4-f60a02caad7f",
    "question": "set difficulty medium",
    "response": "I'm not sure I understand. Try asking about quizzes, changing settings.",
    "timestamp": 1747584624662,
    "userId": "10d8bcc5-2a0c-4c99-bdab-bb912abee69b"
  }, {
    "category": "settings",
    "id": "3d2432a1-1b95-4bd4-9f80-fff680df2825",
    "question": "set target language spanish",
    "response": "Target language set to Spanish",
    "timestamp": 1747584614252,
    "userId": "10d8bcc5-2a0c-4c99-bdab-bb912abee69b"
  }, {
    "category": "settings",
    "id": "f18adaed-897c-4d23-9e4f-9488a54cb689",
    "question": "set mother language english",
    "response": "Mother language set to English",
    "timestamp": 1747584600842,
    "userId": "10d8bcc5-2a0c-4c99-bdab-bb912abee69b"
  }, {
    "category": "thanks",
    "id": "08e149ab-23a4-4f02-95e8-125b722195bb",
    "question": "set difficulty medium",
    "response": "You can change your settings for:\n- Mother language\n- Target language\n- Difficulty level\nWhat would you like to update?",
    "timestamp": 1747584344287,
    "userId": "10d8bcc5-2a0c-4c99-bdab-bb912abee69b"
  }, {
    "category": "system",
    "id": "ba8f317d-72ae-4a5f-a943-f8432542d946",
    "question": "settings",
    "response": "Displayed user settings",
    "timestamp": 1747584330615,
    "userId": "10d8bcc5-2a0c-4c99-bdab-bb912abee69b"
  }, {
    "category": "system",
    "id": "7d6d1812-e7ed-4942-bb1e-872408cedb5a",
    "question": "help",
    "response": "\r\nAvailable commands:\r\n1. chat - Start a conversation\r\n2. quiz - Take a quiz\r\n3. history - View your learning history\r\n4. preferences - Set your language preferences\r\n5. help - Show this help message\r\n6. logout - Log out\r\n7. exit - Exit the application\r\n",
    "timestamp": 1747584320951,
    "userId": "10d8bcc5-2a0c-4c99-bdab-bb912abee69b"
  }, {
    "category": "thanks",
    "id": "dfb69581-b809-482c-9c38-37d0c8e2f33a",
    "question": "set difficulty hard",
    "response": "You can change your settings for:\n- Mother language\n- Target language\n- Difficulty level\nWhat would you like to update?",
    "timestamp": 1747584030159,
    "userId": "10d8bcc5-2a0c-4c99-bdab-bb912abee69b"
  }],
  "quizResults": [{
    "correctAnswers": 3,
    "id": "2343abd3-5716-4199-a3ca-033e725a0cb2",
    "questions": [{
      "correctAnswer": "cama",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "What is 'bed' in Spanish?",
      "userAnswer": "cama"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "mesa",
      "isCorrect": false,
      "question": "What is 'table' in Spanish?",
      "userAnswer": "cama"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "silla",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "What is 'cshair' in Spanish?",
      "userAnswer": "silla"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "casa",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "What is 'house' in Spanish?",
      "userAnswer": "casa"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "puerta",
      "isCorrect": false,
      "question": "What is 'door' in Spanish?",
      "userAnswer": "pared"
    }],
    "quizType": "Vocabulary",
    "score": 3.0,
    "timestamp": 1747586020981,
    "totalQuestions": 5,
    "userAnswers": ["cama", "cama", "silla", "casa", "pared"],
    "userId": "10d8bcc5-2a0c-4c99-bdab-bb912abee69b"
  }, {
    "correctAnswers": 2,
    "id": "50c123d9-b33e-47e0-9638-2297e3f24fcc",
    "questions": [{
      "correctAnswer": "agua",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "What is 'water' in Spanish?",
      "userAnswer": "agua"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "queso",
      "isCorrect": false,
      "question": "What is 'cheese' in Spanish?",
      "userAnswer": "s"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "manzana",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "What is 'apple' in Spanish?",
      "userAnswer": "manzana"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "pan",
      "isCorrect": false,
      "question": "What is 'bread' in Spanish?",
      "userAnswer": "agua"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "plátano",
      "isCorrect": false,
      "question": "What is 'banana' in Spanish?",
      "userAnswer": "f"
    }],
    "quizType": "Vocabulary",
    "score": 2.0,
    "timestamp": 1747585464947,
    "totalQuestions": 5,
    "userAnswers": ["agua", "s", "manzana", "agua", "f"],
    "userId": "10d8bcc5-2a0c-4c99-bdab-bb912abee69b"
  }, {
    "correctAnswers": 3,
    "id": "55676745-5592-441d-9d42-3e2e6ee10dc4",
    "questions": [{
      "correctAnswer": "Pablo Picasso",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Which Spanish artist painted 'Guernica'?",
      "userAnswer": "Pablo Picasso"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Real Madrid",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Which Spanish football club has won the most UEFA Champions League titles?",
      "userAnswer": "Real Madrid"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "New Year's Eve",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "On which day do Spaniards traditionally eat twelve grapes at midnight?",
      "userAnswer": "New Year's Eve"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Paella",
      "isCorrect": false,
      "question": "Which Spanish dish is made with rice and seafood?",
      "userAnswer": "s"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Madrid",
      "isCorrect": false,
      "question": "Which city is the capital of Spain?",
      "userAnswer": "Valencia"
    }],
    "quizType": "MCQ",
    "score": 3.0,
    "timestamp": 1747585012367,
    "totalQuestions": 5,
    "userAnswers": ["Pablo Picasso", "Real Madrid", "New Year's Eve", "s", "Valencia"],
    "userId": "10d8bcc5-2a0c-4c99-bdab-bb912abee69b"
  }],
  "userId": "10d8bcc5-2a0c-4c99-bdab-bb912abee69b",
  "username": "mazen"
}, {
  "email": "yasso",
  "interactions": [{
    "category": "system",
    "id": "097eb756-d0ef-4efe-8df4-53a544a6c69c",
    "question": "help",
    "response": "\nAvailable commands:\n1. chat - Start a conversation\n2. quiz - Take a quiz\n3. history - View your learning history\n4. preferences - Set your language preferences\n5. help - Show this help message\n6. logout - Log out\n7. exit - Exit the application\n",
    "timestamp": 1747594301083,
    "userId": "241fb087-ba02-45f2-9af9-2ba74c56cefd"
  }, {
    "category": "unknown",
    "id": "e535d65f-40f8-404b-87b2-4ba2ead0d7b6",
    "question": "good morning",
    "response": "I'm not sure I understand. Try asking about quizzes, changing settings.",
    "timestamp": 1747594297386,
    "userId": "241fb087-ba02-45f2-9af9-2ba74c56cefd"
  }, {
    "category": "unknown",
    "id": "a99fde1c-9c07-4179-a5f9-05d489ed045f",
    "question": "hello",
    "response": "Hello, yasso! I'm your Language Learning Bot. Would you like to practice vocabulary, grammar, or start a quiz?",
    "timestamp": 1747594291618,
    "userId": "241fb087-ba02-45f2-9af9-2ba74c56cefd"
  }, {
    "category": "language_question",
    "id": "e433f906-9fc0-43ad-8969-e5b6498ff3db",
    "question": "hi",
    "response": "Hello, yasso! I'm your Language Learning Bot. Would you like to practice vocabulary, grammar, or start a quiz?",
    "timestamp": 1747594288861,
    "userId": "241fb087-ba02-45f2-9af9-2ba74c56cefd"
  }, {
    "category": "system",
    "id": "041928d0-a8e4-4bae-a4ae-0bed6006bfa3",
    "question": "analytics",
    "response": "Displayed user analytics",
    "timestamp": 1747594268126,
    "userId": "241fb087-ba02-45f2-9af9-2ba74c56cefd"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "2e0cc2cd-bd8f-4aaa-b34b-5208f322eaad",
    "question": "Quiz Question 5: How do you say 'goodbye' in Spanish?",
    "response": "Answer: c, Feedback: That's not correct. The correct answer is: adiós",
    "timestamp": 1747594263164,
    "userId": "241fb087-ba02-45f2-9af9-2ba74c56cefd"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "2ebc6363-2dc8-49d1-85ae-fdccca7f3777",
    "question": "Quiz Question 4: What is 'water' in Spanish?",
    "response": "Answer: v, Feedback: That's not correct. The correct answer is: agua",
    "timestamp": 1747594261303,
    "userId": "241fb087-ba02-45f2-9af9-2ba74c56cefd"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "2a741fe8-25f5-4f8f-af20-08f7fc807c6c",
    "question": "Quiz Question 3: What does 'gracias' mean?",
    "response": "Answer: c, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747594260046,
    "userId": "241fb087-ba02-45f2-9af9-2ba74c56cefd"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "bf8e1e41-91e3-43b5-8a99-5e1633fe123e",
    "question": "Quiz Question 2: What is 'friend' in Spanish?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: That's not correct. The correct answer is: amigo",
    "timestamp": 1747594258414,
    "userId": "241fb087-ba02-45f2-9af9-2ba74c56cefd"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "ff536996-65dc-440b-a6f3-0014a6ecd843",
    "question": "Quiz Question 1: How do you say 'hello' in Spanish?",
    "response": "Answer: b, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747594257443,
    "userId": "241fb087-ba02-45f2-9af9-2ba74c56cefd"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "2d0d98b2-4dbe-494d-bf62-4540a936374d",
    "question": "What type of quiz would you like to take?",
    "response": "1",
    "timestamp": 1747594253793,
    "userId": "241fb087-ba02-45f2-9af9-2ba74c56cefd"
  }, {
    "category": "system",
    "id": "92babd3f-bb64-431b-a9d4-ab72c2dc77b3",
    "question": "settings",
    "response": "Displayed user settings",
    "timestamp": 1747594235148,
    "userId": "241fb087-ba02-45f2-9af9-2ba74c56cefd"
  }, {
    "category": "settings",
    "id": "7ff8d597-4099-4e27-adc8-700bccda43b6",
    "question": "settings",
    "response": "You can change your settings for:\n- Mother language\n- Target language\nWhat would you like to update?",
    "timestamp": 1747594235107,
    "userId": "241fb087-ba02-45f2-9af9-2ba74c56cefd"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "4c6f6680-5b03-4d46-8275-c6968c33940c",
    "question": "exit quiz",
    "response": "Cancelled quiz setup",
    "timestamp": 1747594189384,
    "userId": "241fb087-ba02-45f2-9af9-2ba74c56cefd"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "43065915-e081-449f-9a09-2fb79a08946e",
    "question": "What type of quiz would you like to take?",
    "response": "exit quiz",
    "timestamp": 1747594189378,
    "userId": "241fb087-ba02-45f2-9af9-2ba74c56cefd"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "a1b40eff-e4a7-427e-b4e9-78509e42b158",
    "question": "What type of quiz would you like to take?",
    "response": "exit",
    "timestamp": 1747594186403,
    "userId": "241fb087-ba02-45f2-9af9-2ba74c56cefd"
  }, {
    "category": "system",
    "id": "50db06b2-cc2d-4713-999f-86b644eb2326",
    "question": "settings",
    "response": "Displayed user settings",
    "timestamp": 1747594018926,
    "userId": "241fb087-ba02-45f2-9af9-2ba74c56cefd"
  }, {
    "category": "settings",
    "id": "655086c3-c300-49da-b27d-8f1cb53d4575",
    "question": "settings",
    "response": "You can change your settings for:\n- Mother language\n- Target language\nWhat would you like to update?",
    "timestamp": 1747594018916,
    "userId": "241fb087-ba02-45f2-9af9-2ba74c56cefd"
  }, {
    "category": "settings",
    "id": "74c3a46c-b32c-4bd4-9cc0-ce9a0684c8ae",
    "question": "set target language spanish",
    "response": "Target language set to Spanish",
    "timestamp": 1747594015332,
    "userId": "241fb087-ba02-45f2-9af9-2ba74c56cefd"
  }, {
    "category": "settings",
    "id": "08cba184-4dae-4365-9a94-2ec5a34e9544",
    "question": "set mother language english",
    "response": "Mother language set to English",
    "timestamp": 1747594003435,
    "userId": "241fb087-ba02-45f2-9af9-2ba74c56cefd"
  }],
  "quizResults": [{
    "correctAnswers": 2,
    "id": "76a7e3af-5d0a-4198-a08f-a7ecbea89a46",
    "questions": [{
      "correctAnswer": "hola",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "How do you say 'hello' in Spanish?",
      "userAnswer": "hola"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "amigo",
      "isCorrect": false,
      "question": "What is 'friend' in Spanish?",
      "userAnswer": "familia"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "thank you",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "What does 'gracias' mean?",
      "userAnswer": "thank you"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "agua",
      "isCorrect": false,
      "question": "What is 'water' in Spanish?",
      "userAnswer": "v"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "adiós",
      "isCorrect": false,
      "question": "How do you say 'goodbye' in Spanish?",
      "userAnswer": "buenos días"
    }],
    "quizType": "Vocabulary",
    "score": 2.0,
    "timestamp": 1747594263172,
    "totalQuestions": 5,
    "userAnswers": ["hola", "familia", "thank you", "v", "buenos días"],
    "userId": "241fb087-ba02-45f2-9af9-2ba74c56cefd"
  }],
  "userId": "241fb087-ba02-45f2-9af9-2ba74c56cefd",
  "username": "yasso"
}, {
  "email": "222",
  "interactions": [{
    "category": "system",
    "id": "c3f3ce6d-7f0b-4cab-b3ee-cf21a6993694",
    "question": "settings",
    "response": "Displayed user settings",
    "timestamp": 1747419259029,
    "userId": "f0890699-4285-4b57-b710-0db0cf0643fb"
  }, {
    "category": "thanks",
    "id": "a3fc6771-96e8-4b0c-af66-ff66bb02aa34",
    "question": "set difficulty hard",
    "response": "You can change your settings for:\n- Mother language\n- Target language\n- Difficulty level\nWhat would you like to update?",
    "timestamp": 1747419255794,
    "userId": "f0890699-4285-4b57-b710-0db0cf0643fb"
  }, {
    "category": "thanks",
    "id": "9668fe32-5354-43cc-8e99-e121dc3aa2ee",
    "question": "set difficulty level medium",
    "response": "You can change your settings for:\n- Mother language\n- Target language\n- Difficulty level\nWhat would you like to update?",
    "timestamp": 1747419245375,
    "userId": "f0890699-4285-4b57-b710-0db0cf0643fb"
  }, {
    "category": "system",
    "id": "64db8942-99ba-4c07-b956-b29edee47500",
    "question": "settings",
    "response": "Displayed user settings",
    "timestamp": 1747419232059,
    "userId": "f0890699-4285-4b57-b710-0db0cf0643fb"
  }, {
    "category": "thanks",
    "id": "941c5b4c-c302-46fa-889f-a9e661ec122c",
    "question": "set difficulty Medium",
    "response": "You can change your settings for:\n- Mother language\n- Target language\n- Difficulty level\nWhat would you like to update?",
    "timestamp": 1747419053053,
    "userId": "f0890699-4285-4b57-b710-0db0cf0643fb"
  }, {
    "category": "system",
    "id": "ed2ac08a-5816-4502-96d6-74e78ae85112",
    "question": "settings",
    "response": "Displayed user settings",
    "timestamp": 1747419036239,
    "userId": "f0890699-4285-4b57-b710-0db0cf0643fb"
  }, {
    "category": "system",
    "id": "276c42b6-4c8e-434e-b9b3-94da53a7bbed",
    "question": "settings",
    "response": "Displayed user settings",
    "timestamp": 1747419014404,
    "userId": "f0890699-4285-4b57-b710-0db0cf0643fb"
  }, {
    "category": "settings",
    "id": "a4083e4b-7580-4a2a-a92e-c57ba25cd2e2",
    "question": "set mother langage spanish",
    "response": "You can change your settings for:\n- Mother language\n- Target language\n- Difficulty level\nWhat would you like to update?",
    "timestamp": 1747418998764,
    "userId": "f0890699-4285-4b57-b710-0db0cf0643fb"
  }, {
    "category": "system",
    "id": "5c376e3b-0810-432d-a132-07e423e8be8b",
    "question": "settings",
    "response": "Displayed user settings",
    "timestamp": 1747418972666,
    "userId": "f0890699-4285-4b57-b710-0db0cf0643fb"
  }, {
    "category": "system",
    "id": "53083ff3-e66f-45fc-8187-c978f7751434",
    "question": "settings",
    "response": "Displayed user settings",
    "timestamp": 1747418822748,
    "userId": "f0890699-4285-4b57-b710-0db0cf0643fb"
  }, {
    "category": "thanks",
    "id": "f89cdab2-dc28-4929-81ba-71f122aa5bf6",
    "question": "set difficulty Medium",
    "response": "You can change your settings for:\n- Mother language\n- Target language\n- Difficulty level\nWhat would you like to update?",
    "timestamp": 1747418817329,
    "userId": "f0890699-4285-4b57-b710-0db0cf0643fb"
  }, {
    "category": "system",
    "id": "a01401bb-23a3-4060-8c87-f68a2c7d32e2",
    "question": "settings",
    "response": "Displayed user settings",
    "timestamp": 1747418802251,
    "userId": "f0890699-4285-4b57-b710-0db0cf0643fb"
  }, {
    "category": "thanks",
    "id": "bcf96d3f-2678-4901-9e60-bcda6c157d25",
    "question": "set difficulty hard",
    "response": "You can change your settings for:\n- Mother language\n- Target language\n- Difficulty level\nWhat would you like to update?",
    "timestamp": 1747418308773,
    "userId": "f0890699-4285-4b57-b710-0db0cf0643fb"
  }, {
    "category": "system",
    "id": "13ac91ea-35db-40a7-b764-c6e9057e65a2",
    "question": "settings",
    "response": "Displayed user settings",
    "timestamp": 1747418295522,
    "userId": "f0890699-4285-4b57-b710-0db0cf0643fb"
  }, {
    "category": "thanks",
    "id": "bd927729-f473-480b-9a0a-3a79cf1e7886",
    "question": "set difficulty hard",
    "response": "You can change your settings for:\n- Mother language\n- Target language\n- Difficulty level\nWhat would you like to update?",
    "timestamp": 1747418289049,
    "userId": "f0890699-4285-4b57-b710-0db0cf0643fb"
  }, {
    "category": "settings",
    "id": "13448431-3ba3-46e2-9f49-24714a6375e1",
    "question": "set difficult level hard",
    "response": "You can change your settings for:\n- Mother language\n- Target language\n- Difficulty level\nWhat would you like to update?",
    "timestamp": 1747417854344,
    "userId": "f0890699-4285-4b57-b710-0db0cf0643fb"
  }, {
    "category": "system",
    "id": "11bab645-ecc8-456d-9121-f24a5df76985",
    "question": "settings",
    "response": "Displayed user settings",
    "timestamp": 1747417831227,
    "userId": "f0890699-4285-4b57-b710-0db0cf0643fb"
  }, {
    "category": "system",
    "id": "e95ded1a-936e-4341-a58f-42ad25f50b8f",
    "question": "settings",
    "response": "Displayed user settings",
    "timestamp": 1747417806987,
    "userId": "f0890699-4285-4b57-b710-0db0cf0643fb"
  }, {
    "category": "settings",
    "id": "d925a976-8d12-4e81-89d8-ae8db5c8a432",
    "question": "settigs",
    "response": "You can change your settings for:\n- Mother language\n- Target language\n- Difficulty level\nWhat would you like to update?",
    "timestamp": 1747417798811,
    "userId": "f0890699-4285-4b57-b710-0db0cf0643fb"
  }, {
    "category": "thanks",
    "id": "7eaff5ad-69dc-4d02-88b0-de3f1fb665a5",
    "question": "set difficulty hard",
    "response": "You can change your settings for:\n- Mother language\n- Target language\n- Difficulty level\nWhat would you like to update?",
    "timestamp": 1747417793222,
    "userId": "f0890699-4285-4b57-b710-0db0cf0643fb"
  }, {
    "category": "system",
    "id": "f79ac649-b779-4970-a166-52add1681cd8",
    "question": "settings",
    "response": "Displayed user settings",
    "timestamp": 1747417778082,
    "userId": "f0890699-4285-4b57-b710-0db0cf0643fb"
  }, {
    "category": "thanks",
    "id": "f478db06-9e86-43c3-8ed8-daa156914d88",
    "question": "set difficulty medium",
    "response": "You can change your settings for:\n- Mother language\n- Target language\n- Difficulty level\nWhat would you like to update?",
    "timestamp": 1747417773688,
    "userId": "f0890699-4285-4b57-b710-0db0cf0643fb"
  }, {
    "category": "system",
    "id": "00fae220-f0b5-4553-94a0-a260759174fb",
    "question": "settings",
    "response": "Displayed user settings",
    "timestamp": 1747417758134,
    "userId": "f0890699-4285-4b57-b710-0db0cf0643fb"
  }, {
    "category": "system",
    "id": "9f510d6d-8124-43fa-ac80-5aabaaacc541",
    "question": "settings",
    "response": "Displayed user settings",
    "timestamp": 1747417608835,
    "userId": "f0890699-4285-4b57-b710-0db0cf0643fb"
  }, {
    "category": "thanks",
    "id": "32142f2f-0e42-4bd1-b493-edd1fad11b0f",
    "question": "set difficulty Medium",
    "response": "You can change your settings for:\n- Mother language\n- Target language\n- Difficulty level\nWhat would you like to update?",
    "timestamp": 1747417605366,
    "userId": "f0890699-4285-4b57-b710-0db0cf0643fb"
  }, {
    "category": "system",
    "id": "9c1ad97a-c87f-4573-8ad9-13db13afe3ba",
    "question": "settings",
    "response": "Displayed user settings",
    "timestamp": 1747417590101,
    "userId": "f0890699-4285-4b57-b710-0db0cf0643fb"
  }, {
    "category": "system",
    "id": "7ddba405-4016-460d-b040-1c2a5d1db578",
    "question": "settings",
    "response": "Displayed user settings",
    "timestamp": 1747417436099,
    "userId": "f0890699-4285-4b57-b710-0db0cf0643fb"
  }, {
    "category": "thanks",
    "id": "2a0ce8e2-6ca0-4459-95de-0d536631e4ee",
    "question": "change Difficulty hard",
    "response": "You can change your settings for:\n- Mother language\n- Target language\n- Difficulty level\nWhat would you like to update?",
    "timestamp": 1747417432135,
    "userId": "f0890699-4285-4b57-b710-0db0cf0643fb"
  }, {
    "category": "thanks",
    "id": "43a1820b-b5cc-495c-8640-3c6b2eb33f17",
    "question": "Difficulty hard",
    "response": "I'm not sure I understand. Try asking about quizzes, changing settings.",
    "timestamp": 1747417420733,
    "userId": "f0890699-4285-4b57-b710-0db0cf0643fb"
  }, {
    "category": "system",
    "id": "80770de7-ca9a-4be8-a378-f992650d2863",
    "question": "settings",
    "response": "Displayed user settings",
    "timestamp": 1747417407525,
    "userId": "f0890699-4285-4b57-b710-0db0cf0643fb"
  }, {
    "category": "thanks",
    "id": "b1ddbb99-8646-4751-9981-564acb7a6725",
    "question": "set difficulty hard",
    "response": "You can change your settings for:\n- Mother language\n- Target language\n- Difficulty level\nWhat would you like to update?",
    "timestamp": 1747417403633,
    "userId": "f0890699-4285-4b57-b710-0db0cf0643fb"
  }, {
    "category": "thanks",
    "id": "ecb8610d-8c52-44a7-9844-4570deaa8d96",
    "question": "change difficulty level easy",
    "response": "You can change your settings for:\n- Mother language\n- Target language\n- Difficulty level\nWhat would you like to update?",
    "timestamp": 1747417145246,
    "userId": "f0890699-4285-4b57-b710-0db0cf0643fb"
  }, {
    "category": "thanks",
    "id": "0fafb109-eaf1-4a38-a0ee-d7468aba1c21",
    "question": "set difficulty level hard",
    "response": "You can change your settings for:\n- Mother language\n- Target language\n- Difficulty level\nWhat would you like to update?",
    "timestamp": 1747417069804,
    "userId": "f0890699-4285-4b57-b710-0db0cf0643fb"
  }, {
    "category": "unknown",
    "id": "644967a2-fcb2-48ca-8cd5-9ea0319ecb34",
    "question": "hello",
    "response": "Hello, yassin! I'm your Language Learning Bot. Would you like to practice vocabulary, grammar, or start a quiz?",
    "timestamp": 1747417032690,
    "userId": "f0890699-4285-4b57-b710-0db0cf0643fb"
  }, {
    "category": "language_question",
    "id": "04def02a-cca3-42ab-b5cb-4c8d6a5fe343",
    "question": "hi",
    "response": "Hello, yassin! I'm your Language Learning Bot. Would you like to practice vocabulary, grammar, or start a quiz?",
    "timestamp": 1747417030532,
    "userId": "f0890699-4285-4b57-b710-0db0cf0643fb"
  }, {
    "category": "thanks",
    "id": "25a98198-dd63-41fa-919e-bd8a6f03cb6f",
    "question": "set difficulty easy",
    "response": "You can change your settings for:\n- Mother language\n- Target language\n- Difficulty level\nWhat would you like to update?",
    "timestamp": 1747416686568,
    "userId": "f0890699-4285-4b57-b710-0db0cf0643fb"
  }, {
    "category": "thanks",
    "id": "50a6a6e6-4709-4116-8ff1-bc9442ac4870",
    "question": "change difficulty level hard",
    "response": "You can change your settings for:\n- Mother language\n- Target language\n- Difficulty level\nWhat would you like to update?",
    "timestamp": 1747416574981,
    "userId": "f0890699-4285-4b57-b710-0db0cf0643fb"
  }, {
    "category": "thanks",
    "id": "4206e137-f31d-4b80-b034-f90568f7e3ef",
    "question": "difficlty level medium",
    "response": "I'm not sure I understand. Try asking about quizzes, changing settings.",
    "timestamp": 1747416554973,
    "userId": "f0890699-4285-4b57-b710-0db0cf0643fb"
  }, {
    "category": "thanks",
    "id": "94e38634-e453-421e-ba4a-0f2ad73d2f14",
    "question": "set difficulty easy",
    "response": "You can change your settings for:\n- Mother language\n- Target language\n- Difficulty level\nWhat would you like to update?",
    "timestamp": 1747416539162,
    "userId": "f0890699-4285-4b57-b710-0db0cf0643fb"
  }, {
    "category": "thanks",
    "id": "70f2f219-cd37-4855-bb4a-991c86849529",
    "question": "set Difficulty level hard",
    "response": "You can change your settings for:\n- Mother language\n- Target language\n- Difficulty level\nWhat would you like to update?",
    "timestamp": 1747411607484,
    "userId": "f0890699-4285-4b57-b710-0db0cf0643fb"
  }, {
    "category": "thanks",
    "id": "c57294e9-b752-4f41-99f7-fc2577fb4487",
    "question": "set difficulty hard",
    "response": "You can change your settings for:\n- Mother language\n- Target language\n- Difficulty level\nWhat would you like to update?",
    "timestamp": 1747411588017,
    "userId": "f0890699-4285-4b57-b710-0db0cf0643fb"
  }, {
    "category": "unknown",
    "id": "f8cdb140-d34f-4fc8-9bbf-9bbca3431f32",
    "question": "",
    "response": "I'm not sure I understand. Try asking about quizzes, changing settings.",
    "timestamp": 1747411572885,
    "userId": "f0890699-4285-4b57-b710-0db0cf0643fb"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "8e3be2ba-13a0-4fe5-bed3-cb6d6c157220",
    "question": "Quiz Question 5: What is 'yes' in French?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747411563370,
    "userId": "f0890699-4285-4b57-b710-0db0cf0643fb"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "633b534d-d882-49ea-a1af-7b33a65444f9",
    "question": "Quiz Question 4: What is 'thank you' in French?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747411563039,
    "userId": "f0890699-4285-4b57-b710-0db0cf0643fb"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "04346be3-679e-4331-b589-e96cd3934837",
    "question": "Quiz Question 3: What is 'please' in French?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747411562753,
    "userId": "f0890699-4285-4b57-b710-0db0cf0643fb"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "639ea1fa-ebe3-4079-aadb-38ec2aa3d90d",
    "question": "Quiz Question 2: What is 'hello' in French?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747411562457,
    "userId": "f0890699-4285-4b57-b710-0db0cf0643fb"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "8b3fb9c0-b418-4f1a-8579-0028bcc80ee9",
    "question": "Quiz Question 1: What is 'no' in French?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747411562148,
    "userId": "f0890699-4285-4b57-b710-0db0cf0643fb"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "d89bb22c-68f7-4708-a8eb-83d99fcef51e",
    "question": "vocabulary",
    "response": "Started a Vocabulary quiz",
    "timestamp": 1747411559961,
    "userId": "f0890699-4285-4b57-b710-0db0cf0643fb"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz_request",
    "id": "f186fa76-7d58-4d7b-9915-7fee989d953a",
    "question": "i want french quiz",
    "response": "Quel type de quiz souhaitez-vous passer ? Nous proposons :\r\n1. Vocabulaire - Testez votre connaissance des mots\r\n2. Grammaire - Pratiquez les règles de langue\r\n3. Traduction - Traduisez entre les langues\r\n4. Choix multiple (MCQ) - Questions générales sur la langue\r\n\r\nVeuillez taper le numéro (1-4) ou le nom du quiz que vous souhaitez passer.",
    "timestamp": 1747411548433,
    "userId": "f0890699-4285-4b57-b710-0db0cf0643fb"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "6543ae4f-660a-4623-9c5b-a3a1bd0e2b08",
    "question": "Quiz Question 5: What is 'banana' in Spanish?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747411395508,
    "userId": "f0890699-4285-4b57-b710-0db0cf0643fb"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "0b43582b-1973-4a48-bb44-dfa5a06a6eb7",
    "question": "Quiz Question 4: What is 'cheese' in Spanish?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747411395135,
    "userId": "f0890699-4285-4b57-b710-0db0cf0643fb"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "0a63a5a0-9974-4b10-928f-29fe7878766b",
    "question": "Quiz Question 3: What is 'apple' in Spanish?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747411394780,
    "userId": "f0890699-4285-4b57-b710-0db0cf0643fb"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "08190608-fe7b-4f0d-b63d-9765fe7659c3",
    "question": "Quiz Question 2: What is 'bread' in Spanish?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747411394474,
    "userId": "f0890699-4285-4b57-b710-0db0cf0643fb"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "656459c9-a2f2-41a5-a64e-55dc8298b093",
    "question": "Quiz Question 1: What is 'water' in Spanish?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747411393928,
    "userId": "f0890699-4285-4b57-b710-0db0cf0643fb"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "8c3e64e7-613a-48b2-9307-2e97fd158e02",
    "question": "vocabulary",
    "response": "Started a Vocabulary quiz",
    "timestamp": 1747411389884,
    "userId": "f0890699-4285-4b57-b710-0db0cf0643fb"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz_request",
    "id": "359e448c-1302-4223-a09e-e765bfa58971",
    "question": "i want quiz",
    "response": "¿Qué tipo de cuestionario te gustaría realizar? Ofrecemos:\r\n1. Vocabulario - Pon a prueba tu conocimiento de palabras\r\n2. Gramática - Practica reglas del lenguaje\r\n3. Traducción - Traduce entre idiomas\r\n4. Opción múltiple (MCQ) - Preguntas generales de idioma\r\n\r\nPor favor, escribe el número (1-4) o el nombre del cuestionario que deseas realizar.",
    "timestamp": 1747411371050,
    "userId": "f0890699-4285-4b57-b710-0db0cf0643fb"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "4d9c041c-9c1b-41cd-a6b9-ddc6ed9d5778",
    "question": "exit quiz",
    "response": "Exited quiz mode",
    "timestamp": 1747411240231,
    "userId": "f0890699-4285-4b57-b710-0db0cf0643fb"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "2be5a56c-791e-46ab-bb99-e729b8497285",
    "question": "vocabulaire",
    "response": "Started a Vocabulary quiz",
    "timestamp": 1747411118424,
    "userId": "f0890699-4285-4b57-b710-0db0cf0643fb"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz_request",
    "id": "a4be5182-8e5b-4c7a-8dfc-63c7a91ac82a",
    "question": "i want english quiz",
    "response": "Quel type de quiz souhaitez-vous passer ? Nous proposons :\r\n1. Vocabulaire - Testez votre connaissance des mots\r\n2. Grammaire - Pratiquez les règles de langue\r\n3. Traduction - Traduisez entre les langues\r\n4. Choix multiple (MCQ) - Questions générales sur la langue\r\n\r\nVeuillez taper le numéro (1-4) ou le nom du quiz que vous souhaitez passer.",
    "timestamp": 1747411102310,
    "userId": "f0890699-4285-4b57-b710-0db0cf0643fb"
  }],
  "quizResults": [{
    "correctAnswers": 5,
    "id": "a802f985-7e7d-479c-9be1-a3cce0d692c9",
    "questions": [{
      "correctAnswer": "non",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "What is 'no' in French?",
      "userAnswer": "non"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "bonjour",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "What is 'hello' in French?",
      "userAnswer": "bonjour"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "s'il vous plaît",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "What is 'please' in French?",
      "userAnswer": "s'il vous plaît"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "merci",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "What is 'thank you' in French?",
      "userAnswer": "merci"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "oui",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "What is 'yes' in French?",
      "userAnswer": "oui"
    }],
    "quizType": "Vocabulary",
    "score": 5.0,
    "timestamp": 1747411563383,
    "totalQuestions": 5,
    "userAnswers": ["non", "bonjour", "s'il vous plaît", "merci", "oui"],
    "userId": "f0890699-4285-4b57-b710-0db0cf0643fb"
  }, {
    "correctAnswers": 5,
    "id": "b59fc129-1637-49fc-9d56-cd3aef5b618f",
    "questions": [{
      "correctAnswer": "agua",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "What is 'water' in Spanish?",
      "userAnswer": "agua"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "pan",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "What is 'bread' in Spanish?",
      "userAnswer": "pan"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "manzana",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "What is 'apple' in Spanish?",
      "userAnswer": "manzana"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "queso",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "What is 'cheese' in Spanish?",
      "userAnswer": "queso"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "plátano",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "What is 'banana' in Spanish?",
      "userAnswer": "plátano"
    }],
    "quizType": "Vocabulary",
    "score": 5.0,
    "timestamp": 1747411395520,
    "totalQuestions": 5,
    "userAnswers": ["agua", "pan", "manzana", "queso", "plátano"],
    "userId": "f0890699-4285-4b57-b710-0db0cf0643fb"
  }],
  "userId": "f0890699-4285-4b57-b710-0db0cf0643fb",
  "username": "yassin"
}, {
  "email": "33",
  "interactions": [{
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "cad02482-4004-4a51-a33d-7a38ea85c05c",
    "question": "Quiz Question 5: Translate: 'She works at a hospital'",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747597080264,
    "userId": "7906637e-27a9-4678-8724-fd231365c4a8"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "2273c270-bb6e-4001-a3f6-c53e955acd79",
    "question": "Quiz Question 4: Translate: 'I like to travel'",
    "response": "Answer: aa, Feedback: That's not correct. The correct answer is: J'aime voyager",
    "timestamp": 1747597079887,
    "userId": "7906637e-27a9-4678-8724-fd231365c4a8"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "82650018-b444-4d12-a74c-92e341e10154",
    "question": "Quiz Question 3: Translate: 'My name is John'",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: That's not correct. The correct answer is: Je m'appelle John",
    "timestamp": 1747597079243,
    "userId": "7906637e-27a9-4678-8724-fd231365c4a8"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "de5d9936-ee60-4469-9eec-9a4bce9356b3",
    "question": "Quiz Question 2: Translate: 'Where is the bathroom?'",
    "response": "Answer: , Feedback: That's not correct. The correct answer is: Où sont les toilettes?",
    "timestamp": 1747597078908,
    "userId": "7906637e-27a9-4678-8724-fd231365c4a8"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "01ae9d3c-afb0-404e-b5bd-c9886bb23b63",
    "question": "Quiz Question 1: Translate: 'I eat breakfast every day'",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747597078621,
    "userId": "7906637e-27a9-4678-8724-fd231365c4a8"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "fd9a240e-103b-4268-bb8d-761024f9b9d4",
    "question": "What type of quiz would you like to take?",
    "response": "3",
    "timestamp": 1747597074668,
    "userId": "7906637e-27a9-4678-8724-fd231365c4a8"
  }, {
    "category": "settings",
    "id": "46d96684-24a8-4816-8c7b-4694aa9f9a20",
    "question": "set target language french",
    "response": "Target language set to French",
    "timestamp": 1747597059302,
    "userId": "7906637e-27a9-4678-8724-fd231365c4a8"
  }, {
    "category": "settings",
    "id": "e2dc96ba-e459-47e3-9416-97fc2e9b52a0",
    "question": "set mother language english",
    "response": "Mother language set to English",
    "timestamp": 1747597049721,
    "userId": "7906637e-27a9-4678-8724-fd231365c4a8"
  }, {
    "category": "system",
    "id": "93920d95-18e0-4037-b9f1-e88c868916ab",
    "question": "prefrences",
    "response": "Displayed user settings",
    "timestamp": 1747597035236,
    "userId": "7906637e-27a9-4678-8724-fd231365c4a8"
  }, {
    "category": "settings",
    "id": "2a66ceb6-9a57-4ce8-8599-9d5f0a34a800",
    "question": "settings",
    "response": "You can change your settings for:\n- Mother language\n- Target language\nWhat would you like to update?",
    "timestamp": 1747597035232,
    "userId": "7906637e-27a9-4678-8724-fd231365c4a8"
  }, {
    "category": "system",
    "id": "e3b98004-8c40-40f9-935f-bb9908803a26",
    "question": "help",
    "response": "\nAvailable commands:\n1. chat - Start a conversation\n2. quiz - Take a quiz\n3. history - View your learning history\n4. preferences - Set your language preferences\n5. help - Show this help message\n6. logout - Log out\n7. exit - Exit the application\n",
    "timestamp": 1747597025528,
    "userId": "7906637e-27a9-4678-8724-fd231365c4a8"
  }],
  "quizResults": [{
    "correctAnswers": 2,
    "id": "56eceeec-009e-4413-adfa-d1742b27e289",
    "questions": [{
      "correctAnswer": "Je mange le petit déjeuner tous les jours",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Translate: 'I eat breakfast every day'",
      "userAnswer": "Je mange le petit déjeuner tous les jours"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Où sont les toilettes?",
      "isCorrect": false,
      "question": "Translate: 'Where is the bathroom?'",
      "userAnswer": ""
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Je m'appelle John",
      "isCorrect": false,
      "question": "Translate: 'My name is John'",
      "userAnswer": "mon nom est john"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "J'aime voyager",
      "isCorrect": false,
      "question": "Translate: 'I like to travel'",
      "userAnswer": "aa"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Elle travaille dans un hôpital",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Translate: 'She works at a hospital'",
      "userAnswer": "Elle travaille dans un hôpital"
    }],
    "quizType": "Translation",
    "score": 2.0,
    "timestamp": 1747597080272,
    "totalQuestions": 5,
    "userAnswers": ["Je mange le petit déjeuner tous les jours", "", "mon nom est john", "aa", "Elle travaille dans un hôpital"],
    "userId": "7906637e-27a9-4678-8724-fd231365c4a8"
  }],
  "userId": "7906637e-27a9-4678-8724-fd231365c4a8",
  "username": "ahmed"
}, {
  "email": "ali@gmail.com",
  "interactions": [{
    "category": "language_question",
    "id": "7dce77a2-c278-44b0-954d-331446c5427a",
    "question": "aa",
    "response": "What would you like to know about language learning? I can help with vocabulary, grammar, and more.",
    "timestamp": 1747600531941,
    "userId": "e4985904-bf06-4c07-a4f5-09020441d27b"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "7ec427d0-d6d1-4b58-ae1e-430279cde3ea",
    "question": "Quiz Question 5: Which German car manufacturer makes the 911 model?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747600529803,
    "userId": "e4985904-bf06-4c07-a4f5-09020441d27b"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "3e34375c-1021-4c8d-9240-2c1b5fc8348c",
    "question": "Quiz Question 4: Which German composer wrote 'Symphony No. 9'?",
    "response": "Answer: c, Feedback: That's not correct. The correct answer is: Ludwig van Beethoven",
    "timestamp": 1747600529340,
    "userId": "e4985904-bf06-4c07-a4f5-09020441d27b"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "7df2e9ca-ee7e-46d2-8921-6cc6946c60e9",
    "question": "Quiz Question 3: What is the currency of Germany?",
    "response": "Answer: , Feedback: That's not correct. The correct answer is: Euro",
    "timestamp": 1747600527875,
    "userId": "e4985904-bf06-4c07-a4f5-09020441d27b"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "be8945b7-feb7-4a8c-9bd1-036f08e73982",
    "question": "Quiz Question 2: Which German festival is celebrated in October?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747600527227,
    "userId": "e4985904-bf06-4c07-a4f5-09020441d27b"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "f5c933fd-7eb1-4c7e-a8ab-e7df81e8d14e",
    "question": "Quiz Question 1: Which city is the capital of Germany?",
    "response": "Answer: aa, Feedback: That's not correct. The correct answer is: Berlin",
    "timestamp": 1747600526781,
    "userId": "e4985904-bf06-4c07-a4f5-09020441d27b"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "2b38fe8e-99d6-482f-be3c-000b133f3c4e",
    "question": "What type of quiz would you like to take?",
    "response": "4",
    "timestamp": 1747600519994,
    "userId": "e4985904-bf06-4c07-a4f5-09020441d27b"
  }],
  "quizResults": [{
    "correctAnswers": 2,
    "id": "e6713bc1-8717-478e-aa16-5dc88f964d9b",
    "questions": [{
      "correctAnswer": "Berlin",
      "isCorrect": false,
      "question": "Which city is the capital of Germany?",
      "userAnswer": "aa"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Oktoberfest",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Which German festival is celebrated in October?",
      "userAnswer": "Oktoberfest"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Euro",
      "isCorrect": false,
      "question": "What is the currency of Germany?",
      "userAnswer": ""
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Ludwig van Beethoven",
      "isCorrect": false,
      "question": "Which German composer wrote 'Symphony No. 9'?",
      "userAnswer": "wolfgang amadeus mozart"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Porsche",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Which German car manufacturer makes the 911 model?",
      "userAnswer": "Porsche"
    }],
    "quizType": "MCQ",
    "score": 40.0,
    "timestamp": 1747600529813,
    "totalQuestions": 5,
    "userAnswers": ["aa", "Oktoberfest", "", "wolfgang amadeus mozart", "Porsche"],
    "userId": "e4985904-bf06-4c07-a4f5-09020441d27b"
  }],
  "userId": "e4985904-bf06-4c07-a4f5-09020441d27b",
  "username": "ali"
}, {
  "email": "yyy",
  "interactions": [{
    "category": "quiz_request",
    "id": "3c668bee-6e0a-4a1c-bb69-4785e261f5d9",
    "question": "i want take a quiz",
    "response": "Quel type de quiz souhaitez-vous passer ? Nous proposons :\r\n1. Vocabulaire - Testez votre connaissance des mots\r\n2. Grammaire - Pratiquez les règles de langue\r\n3. Traduction - Traduisez entre les langues\r\n4. Choix multiple (MCQ) - Questions générales sur la langue\r\n\r\nVeuillez taper le numéro (1-4) ou le nom du quiz que vous souhaitez passer.",
    "timestamp": 1747424176118,
    "userId": "490c80a7-a01e-424c-8f4e-2cc020f145bd"
  }, {
    "category": "system",
    "id": "dab76f5a-2bcf-4f95-9952-a6021ed8549c",
    "question": "settings",
    "response": "Displayed user settings",
    "timestamp": 1747424098315,
    "userId": "490c80a7-a01e-424c-8f4e-2cc020f145bd"
  }, {
    "category": "thanks",
    "id": "bb4ccaad-af87-4c9c-bbd2-c82bbf7e55d1",
    "question": "set difficulty easy",
    "response": "You can change your settings for:\n- Mother language\n- Target language\n- Difficulty level\nWhat would you like to update?",
    "timestamp": 1747424095314,
    "userId": "490c80a7-a01e-424c-8f4e-2cc020f145bd"
  }, {
    "category": "system",
    "id": "d93cb4d5-1223-4be8-ba34-c9802a658b25",
    "question": "settings",
    "response": "Displayed user settings",
    "timestamp": 1747424059533,
    "userId": "490c80a7-a01e-424c-8f4e-2cc020f145bd"
  }, {
    "category": "system",
    "id": "463c538c-55ef-46ee-b0db-ac08e73c3b34",
    "question": "help",
    "response": "\r\nAvailable commands:\r\n1. chat - Start a conversation\r\n2. quiz - Take a quiz\r\n3. history - View your learning history\r\n4. preferences - Set your language preferences\r\n5. help - Show this help message\r\n6. logout - Log out\r\n7. exit - Exit the application\r\n",
    "timestamp": 1747424043651,
    "userId": "490c80a7-a01e-424c-8f4e-2cc020f145bd"
  }],
  "quizResults": [],
  "userId": "490c80a7-a01e-424c-8f4e-2cc020f145bd",
  "username": "yasso"
}, {
  "email": "kkk",
  "interactions": [{
    "category": "system",
    "id": "8c3413a0-8fdf-4245-8907-00f57ff02f5d",
    "question": "settings",
    "response": "Displayed user settings",
    "timestamp": 1747424456341,
    "userId": "93efc046-c600-48b9-8521-e6bc1271c245"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz_request",
    "id": "175b5a47-a2f0-4690-b873-3bbed08222e0",
    "question": "i want to start quiz",
    "response": "¿Qué tipo de cuestionario te gustaría realizar? Ofrecemos:\r\n1. Vocabulario - Pon a prueba tu conocimiento de palabras\r\n2. Gramática - Practica reglas del lenguaje\r\n3. Traducción - Traduce entre idiomas\r\n4. Opción múltiple (MCQ) - Preguntas generales de idioma\r\n\r\nPor favor, escribe el número (1-4) o el nombre del cuestionario que deseas realizar.",
    "timestamp": 1747424434378,
    "userId": "93efc046-c600-48b9-8521-e6bc1271c245"
  }, {
    "category": "system",
    "id": "a2f31727-996c-4ed6-8689-88d948eb4fa0",
    "question": "settings",
    "response": "Displayed user settings",
    "timestamp": 1747424427924,
    "userId": "93efc046-c600-48b9-8521-e6bc1271c245"
  }, {
    "category": "thanks",
    "id": "69498884-5223-4d03-965f-92fce2e01159",
    "question": "set difficulty easy",
    "response": "You can change your settings for:\n- Mother language\n- Target language\n- Difficulty level\nWhat would you like to update?",
    "timestamp": 1747424424498,
    "userId": "93efc046-c600-48b9-8521-e6bc1271c245"
  }, {
    "category": "system",
    "id": "da82cb65-d2dd-4b1a-9a1c-ff0faac65f9e",
    "question": "settings",
    "response": "Displayed user settings",
    "timestamp": 1747424389748,
    "userId": "93efc046-c600-48b9-8521-e6bc1271c245"
  }, {
    "category": "settings",
    "id": "ea654792-c825-42e5-97d2-7f22c52159d4",
    "question": "prefrences",
    "response": "You can change your settings for:\n- Mother language\n- Target language\n- Difficulty level\nWhat would you like to update?",
    "timestamp": 1747424367532,
    "userId": "93efc046-c600-48b9-8521-e6bc1271c245"
  }, {
    "category": "system",
    "id": "096c1acd-8f99-4684-addb-3f530b602eda",
    "question": "help",
    "response": "\r\nAvailable commands:\r\n1. chat - Start a conversation\r\n2. quiz - Take a quiz\r\n3. history - View your learning history\r\n4. preferences - Set your language preferences\r\n5. help - Show this help message\r\n6. logout - Log out\r\n7. exit - Exit the application\r\n",
    "timestamp": 1747424363839,
    "userId": "93efc046-c600-48b9-8521-e6bc1271c245"
  }],
  "quizResults": [],
  "userId": "93efc046-c600-48b9-8521-e6bc1271c245",
  "username": "abdo"
}, {
  "email": "mohamedSaafan@gmail.com",
  "interactions": [{
    "category": "system",
    "id": "9089fc51-4519-4bcb-b15c-58e6425dce3e",
    "question": "analytics",
    "response": "Displayed user analytics",
    "timestamp": 1747601711674,
    "userId": "6c2c017a-e854-44aa-8a61-e05d38a3af1e"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "578b38e9-423f-4492-bd54-e14d4312c467",
    "question": "Quiz Question 5: Translate: 'I have a question'",
    "response": "Answer: d, Feedback: That's not correct. The correct answer is: Ich habe eine Frage",
    "timestamp": 1747601704699,
    "userId": "6c2c017a-e854-44aa-8a61-e05d38a3af1e"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "0ad2ca5b-ab25-40eb-98e2-939a0c9e54d0",
    "question": "Quiz Question 4: Translate: 'I'm learning German'",
    "response": "Answer: , Feedback: That's not correct. The correct answer is: Ich lerne Deutsch",
    "timestamp": 1747601703561,
    "userId": "6c2c017a-e854-44aa-8a61-e05d38a3af1e"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "42b17f86-0be5-4367-a755-12c4bad0ec26",
    "question": "Quiz Question 3: Translate: 'Have a nice day'",
    "response": "Answer: b, Feedback: That's not correct. The correct answer is: Einen schönen Tag",
    "timestamp": 1747601701876,
    "userId": "6c2c017a-e854-44aa-8a61-e05d38a3af1e"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "bfdcc20c-11b1-4e03-8c34-7a4d20e04922",
    "question": "Quiz Question 2: Translate: 'What's your name?'",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747601700085,
    "userId": "6c2c017a-e854-44aa-8a61-e05d38a3af1e"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "416f1d6d-0ea9-47d7-bb05-4ed8d003bbd4",
    "question": "Quiz Question 1: Translate: 'Can you help me?'",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747601699162,
    "userId": "6c2c017a-e854-44aa-8a61-e05d38a3af1e"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "74aae6aa-e3b6-490a-bca9-edf74721568e",
    "question": "What type of quiz would you like to take?",
    "response": "3",
    "timestamp": 1747601685777,
    "userId": "6c2c017a-e854-44aa-8a61-e05d38a3af1e"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "b75ea918-6193-40fe-af33-959336ede450",
    "question": "Quiz Question 5: Translate: 'I don't understand'",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747601678375,
    "userId": "6c2c017a-e854-44aa-8a61-e05d38a3af1e"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "6cce391b-2b03-424a-897e-5ef05ef925c1",
    "question": "Quiz Question 4: Translate: 'See you tomorrow'",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747601677908,
    "userId": "6c2c017a-e854-44aa-8a61-e05d38a3af1e"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "0918ef56-0007-46d3-8759-dd6d33c2f731",
    "question": "Quiz Question 3: Translate: 'What time is it?'",
    "response": "Answer: aa, Feedback: That's not correct. The correct answer is: Wie spät ist es?",
    "timestamp": 1747601677370,
    "userId": "6c2c017a-e854-44aa-8a61-e05d38a3af1e"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "cc3a3348-2749-4fff-b997-ad2ecc65bfd1",
    "question": "Quiz Question 2: Translate: 'I would like a coffee'",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747601676775,
    "userId": "6c2c017a-e854-44aa-8a61-e05d38a3af1e"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "524fbd30-8847-464a-8abe-8b9ce6d843de",
    "question": "Quiz Question 1: Translate: 'How are you?'",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747601676465,
    "userId": "6c2c017a-e854-44aa-8a61-e05d38a3af1e"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "22638740-867d-4947-88a1-be4c6a08b9fc",
    "question": "What type of quiz would you like to take?",
    "response": "3",
    "timestamp": 1747601674638,
    "userId": "6c2c017a-e854-44aa-8a61-e05d38a3af1e"
  }, {
    "category": "chat",
    "id": "959d4e6b-451e-4edd-9d7b-279c4164f68a",
    "question": "What's your favorite season?",
    "response": "happy",
    "timestamp": 1747601629941,
    "userId": "6c2c017a-e854-44aa-8a61-e05d38a3af1e"
  }, {
    "category": "chat",
    "id": "86d6c47c-2fde-4569-ae07-050047ae8a3e",
    "question": "What's your favorite season?",
    "response": "heavy clothing",
    "timestamp": 1747601616355,
    "userId": "6c2c017a-e854-44aa-8a61-e05d38a3af1e"
  }, {
    "category": "chat",
    "id": "66808486-8b67-4cb3-9d08-348ed9820c19",
    "question": "What's your favorite season?",
    "response": "cold",
    "timestamp": 1747601604504,
    "userId": "6c2c017a-e854-44aa-8a61-e05d38a3af1e"
  }, {
    "category": "chat",
    "id": "3dff2af8-1209-4f99-bc89-15ffe182d48a",
    "question": "What's your favorite season?",
    "response": "summer",
    "timestamp": 1747601599843,
    "userId": "6c2c017a-e854-44aa-8a61-e05d38a3af1e"
  }, {
    "category": "settings",
    "id": "c497f384-30f6-4b7b-8436-5e21dae4b658",
    "question": "set target language german",
    "response": "Target language set to German",
    "timestamp": 1747601589230,
    "userId": "6c2c017a-e854-44aa-8a61-e05d38a3af1e"
  }, {
    "category": "chat",
    "id": "d1b0e9fc-25c1-4727-8f9f-ad5c73d9ff45",
    "question": "What's your favorite season?",
    "response": "white color",
    "timestamp": 1747601559295,
    "userId": "6c2c017a-e854-44aa-8a61-e05d38a3af1e"
  }, {
    "category": "chat",
    "id": "905fdc60-c12a-442d-8ed8-26d4d2258596",
    "question": "What's your favorite season?",
    "response": "light clothes",
    "timestamp": 1747601548282,
    "userId": "6c2c017a-e854-44aa-8a61-e05d38a3af1e"
  }, {
    "category": "chat",
    "id": "b4499688-f666-450e-b5a8-3220194db8a9",
    "question": "What's your favorite season?",
    "response": "warm",
    "timestamp": 1747601534726,
    "userId": "6c2c017a-e854-44aa-8a61-e05d38a3af1e"
  }, {
    "category": "chat",
    "id": "c9080b77-5231-44f4-bfc7-8e5b97d4b67d",
    "question": "What's your favorite season?",
    "response": "summer",
    "timestamp": 1747601520224,
    "userId": "6c2c017a-e854-44aa-8a61-e05d38a3af1e"
  }, {
    "category": "system",
    "id": "40f1db2c-0f52-484d-b1b5-6c2f0284e7d1",
    "question": "help",
    "response": "\nAvailable commands:\n1. chat - Start a conversation\n2. quiz - Take a quiz\n3. history - View your learning history\n4. preferences - Set your language preferences\n5. help - Show this help message\n6. logout - Log out\n7. exit - Exit the application\n",
    "timestamp": 1747601500464,
    "userId": "6c2c017a-e854-44aa-8a61-e05d38a3af1e"
  }, {
    "category": "system",
    "id": "cb4f0217-9149-4928-8d11-10dda0213a58",
    "question": "settings",
    "response": "Displayed user settings",
    "timestamp": 1747601495157,
    "userId": "6c2c017a-e854-44aa-8a61-e05d38a3af1e"
  }, {
    "category": "settings",
    "id": "225e99cc-c665-49b1-a759-dba4bc7dbf01",
    "question": "settings",
    "response": "You can change your settings for:\n- Mother language\n- Target language\nWhat would you like to update?",
    "timestamp": 1747601495150,
    "userId": "6c2c017a-e854-44aa-8a61-e05d38a3af1e"
  }, {
    "category": "settings",
    "id": "7a3dca74-9013-436d-b4b9-4eac17e4bbf3",
    "question": "set target language spanish",
    "response": "Target language set to Spanish",
    "timestamp": 1747601491941,
    "userId": "6c2c017a-e854-44aa-8a61-e05d38a3af1e"
  }, {
    "category": "settings",
    "id": "a2ee50d0-9910-46aa-abc8-101e3f3f065f",
    "question": "set mother language english",
    "response": "Mother language set to English",
    "timestamp": 1747601483494,
    "userId": "6c2c017a-e854-44aa-8a61-e05d38a3af1e"
  }, {
    "category": "unknown",
    "id": "f2407741-5196-4f55-8f37-4e39c728fa5a",
    "question": "set mother english",
    "response": "I'm not sure I understand. Try asking about quizzes, changing settings.",
    "timestamp": 1747601472526,
    "userId": "6c2c017a-e854-44aa-8a61-e05d38a3af1e"
  }, {
    "category": "system",
    "id": "4b74fbf0-0eb7-4adb-b8c9-8c55cbaf0431",
    "question": "prefrences",
    "response": "Displayed user settings",
    "timestamp": 1747601459834,
    "userId": "6c2c017a-e854-44aa-8a61-e05d38a3af1e"
  }, {
    "category": "settings",
    "id": "a2a88aca-f107-4cfc-9bf4-83728c5e90e5",
    "question": "settings",
    "response": "You can change your settings for:\n- Mother language\n- Target language\nWhat would you like to update?",
    "timestamp": 1747601459817,
    "userId": "6c2c017a-e854-44aa-8a61-e05d38a3af1e"
  }, {
    "category": "system",
    "id": "07ed5cc3-0e71-4fcd-9d64-6288b771876e",
    "question": "help",
    "response": "\nAvailable commands:\n1. chat - Start a conversation\n2. quiz - Take a quiz\n3. history - View your learning history\n4. preferences - Set your language preferences\n5. help - Show this help message\n6. logout - Log out\n7. exit - Exit the application\n",
    "timestamp": 1747601450801,
    "userId": "6c2c017a-e854-44aa-8a61-e05d38a3af1e"
  }],
  "quizResults": [{
    "correctAnswers": 2,
    "id": "ef635f0b-fe8d-4a50-90b5-8a24957dc554",
    "questions": [{
      "correctAnswer": "Können Sie mir helfen?",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Translate: 'Can you help me?'",
      "userAnswer": "Können Sie mir helfen?"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Wie heißt du?",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Translate: 'What's your name?'",
      "userAnswer": "Wie heißt du?"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Einen schönen Tag",
      "isCorrect": false,
      "question": "Translate: 'Have a nice day'",
      "userAnswer": "guten tag"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Ich lerne Deutsch",
      "isCorrect": false,
      "question": "Translate: 'I'm learning German'",
      "userAnswer": ""
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Ich habe eine Frage",
      "isCorrect": false,
      "question": "Translate: 'I have a question'",
      "userAnswer": "ich brauche antwort"
    }],
    "quizType": "Translation",
    "score": 40.0,
    "timestamp": 1747601704705,
    "totalQuestions": 5,
    "userAnswers": ["Können Sie mir helfen?", "Wie heißt du?", "guten tag", "", "ich brauche antwort"],
    "userId": "6c2c017a-e854-44aa-8a61-e05d38a3af1e"
  }, {
    "correctAnswers": 4,
    "id": "07ef23a0-a699-418a-86d0-59d954b5af2d",
    "questions": [{
      "correctAnswer": "Wie geht es dir?",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Translate: 'How are you?'",
      "userAnswer": "Wie geht es dir?"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Ich möchte einen Kaffee",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Translate: 'I would like a coffee'",
      "userAnswer": "Ich möchte einen Kaffee"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Wie spät ist es?",
      "isCorrect": false,
      "question": "Translate: 'What time is it?'",
      "userAnswer": "aa"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Bis morgen",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Translate: 'See you tomorrow'",
      "userAnswer": "Bis morgen"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Ich verstehe nicht",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Translate: 'I don't understand'",
      "userAnswer": "Ich verstehe nicht"
    }],
    "quizType": "Translation",
    "score": 80.0,
    "timestamp": 1747601678384,
    "totalQuestions": 5,
    "userAnswers": ["Wie geht es dir?", "Ich möchte einen Kaffee", "aa", "Bis morgen", "Ich verstehe nicht"],
    "userId": "6c2c017a-e854-44aa-8a61-e05d38a3af1e"
  }],
  "userId": "6c2c017a-e854-44aa-8a61-e05d38a3af1e",
  "username": "saafan"
}, {
  "email": "messi",
  "interactions": [{
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "19c29581-f978-4a0a-867a-2467effe269d",
    "question": "Quiz Question 5: Translate: 'My name is John'",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: That's not correct. The correct answer is: Me llamo John",
    "timestamp": 1747599385352,
    "userId": "230f9120-7be8-43a3-9066-42b79164e05b"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "54ab95fa-128f-4b28-9375-28d25ca35cf7",
    "question": "Quiz Question 4: Translate: 'I eat breakfast every day'",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747599384702,
    "userId": "230f9120-7be8-43a3-9066-42b79164e05b"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "1d0e9bc5-d52d-4cbe-af24-daf7d2b28144",
    "question": "Quiz Question 3: Translate: 'Where is the bathroom?'",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: That's not correct. The correct answer is: ¿Dónde está el baño?",
    "timestamp": 1747599384293,
    "userId": "230f9120-7be8-43a3-9066-42b79164e05b"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "c9cd4b18-ac58-4f22-8716-a4958bca1be2",
    "question": "Quiz Question 2: Translate: 'She works at a hospital'",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747599383903,
    "userId": "230f9120-7be8-43a3-9066-42b79164e05b"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "789cf227-2ccb-4c84-a808-40e92513a971",
    "question": "Quiz Question 1: Translate: 'I like to travel'",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747599383334,
    "userId": "230f9120-7be8-43a3-9066-42b79164e05b"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "b5002c00-6f18-45ac-80f8-163e56183bbb",
    "question": "What type of quiz would you like to take?",
    "response": "3",
    "timestamp": 1747599380815,
    "userId": "230f9120-7be8-43a3-9066-42b79164e05b"
  }, {
    "category": "system",
    "id": "d6621020-3c56-435b-9fd2-163313185faa",
    "question": "settings",
    "response": "Displayed user settings",
    "timestamp": 1747599372067,
    "userId": "230f9120-7be8-43a3-9066-42b79164e05b"
  }, {
    "category": "settings",
    "id": "8e3a336a-91d6-42dc-910d-866fa2908f01",
    "question": "settings",
    "response": "You can change your settings for:\n- Mother language\n- Target language\nWhat would you like to update?",
    "timestamp": 1747599372061,
    "userId": "230f9120-7be8-43a3-9066-42b79164e05b"
  }, {
    "category": "chat",
    "id": "9d3d258f-98d4-4669-88d9-74acf1bf6bf8",
    "question": "Do you like this weather?",
    "response": "shirt",
    "timestamp": 1747599359073,
    "userId": "230f9120-7be8-43a3-9066-42b79164e05b"
  }, {
    "category": "chat",
    "id": "5cd893a8-0e16-41f0-b270-d67691609d84",
    "question": "Do you like this weather?",
    "response": "light clothing",
    "timestamp": 1747599352691,
    "userId": "230f9120-7be8-43a3-9066-42b79164e05b"
  }, {
    "category": "chat",
    "id": "f62fd028-e3c0-4500-ad1a-34438e2d97d5",
    "question": "Do you like this weather?",
    "response": "its hot",
    "timestamp": 1747599339517,
    "userId": "230f9120-7be8-43a3-9066-42b79164e05b"
  }, {
    "category": "chat",
    "id": "ad6df5d5-ae07-4337-8490-3a0320e907b1",
    "question": "Do you like this weather?",
    "response": "yes",
    "timestamp": 1747599326154,
    "userId": "230f9120-7be8-43a3-9066-42b79164e05b"
  }, {
    "category": "system",
    "id": "cf78f65a-ae74-406b-ad24-d242bcf58d42",
    "question": "settings",
    "response": "Displayed user settings",
    "timestamp": 1747599152429,
    "userId": "230f9120-7be8-43a3-9066-42b79164e05b"
  }, {
    "category": "settings",
    "id": "a39d6341-e459-4ca0-92a6-986062c8fc44",
    "question": "settings",
    "response": "You can change your settings for:\n- Mother language\n- Target language\nWhat would you like to update?",
    "timestamp": 1747599152421,
    "userId": "230f9120-7be8-43a3-9066-42b79164e05b"
  }, {
    "category": "settings",
    "id": "f9c59015-6b26-4e73-9c23-1e7f34a16180",
    "question": "set target language spanish",
    "response": "Target language set to Spanish",
    "timestamp": 1747599146453,
    "userId": "230f9120-7be8-43a3-9066-42b79164e05b"
  }, {
    "category": "settings",
    "id": "831093c9-3857-4188-9e95-e507c73e9dba",
    "question": "set mother language english",
    "response": "Mother language set to English",
    "timestamp": 1747599137770,
    "userId": "230f9120-7be8-43a3-9066-42b79164e05b"
  }, {
    "category": "system",
    "id": "ea18634b-cc74-48fb-8da8-0d5313d5c228",
    "question": "prefrences",
    "response": "Displayed user settings",
    "timestamp": 1747599125606,
    "userId": "230f9120-7be8-43a3-9066-42b79164e05b"
  }, {
    "category": "settings",
    "id": "a36deb83-f95d-4527-b047-6a37237e8e06",
    "question": "settings",
    "response": "You can change your settings for:\n- Mother language\n- Target language\nWhat would you like to update?",
    "timestamp": 1747599125591,
    "userId": "230f9120-7be8-43a3-9066-42b79164e05b"
  }, {
    "category": "system",
    "id": "1bafcfbc-203f-4a0e-acde-cb55a4ff2b07",
    "question": "help",
    "response": "\nAvailable commands:\n1. chat - Start a conversation\n2. quiz - Take a quiz\n3. history - View your learning history\n4. preferences - Set your language preferences\n5. help - Show this help message\n6. logout - Log out\n7. exit - Exit the application\n",
    "timestamp": 1747599118460,
    "userId": "230f9120-7be8-43a3-9066-42b79164e05b"
  }],
  "quizResults": [{
    "correctAnswers": 3,
    "id": "a70437a3-794d-48c8-b5bd-444d8dec4e55",
    "questions": [{
      "correctAnswer": "Me gusta viajar",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Translate: 'I like to travel'",
      "userAnswer": "Me gusta viajar"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Ella trabaja en un hospital",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Translate: 'She works at a hospital'",
      "userAnswer": "Ella trabaja en un hospital"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "¿Dónde está el baño?",
      "isCorrect": false,
      "question": "Translate: 'Where is the bathroom?'",
      "userAnswer": "¿dónde es el baño?"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Yo como el desayuno todos los días",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "Translate: 'I eat breakfast every day'",
      "userAnswer": "Yo como el desayuno todos los días"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Me llamo John",
      "isCorrect": false,
      "question": "Translate: 'My name is John'",
      "userAnswer": "mi nombre es john"
    }],
    "quizType": "Translation",
    "score": 3.0,
    "timestamp": 1747599385363,
    "totalQuestions": 5,
    "userAnswers": ["Me gusta viajar", "Ella trabaja en un hospital", "¿dónde es el baño?", "Yo como el desayuno todos los días", "mi nombre es john"],
    "userId": "230f9120-7be8-43a3-9066-42b79164e05b"
  }],
  "userId": "230f9120-7be8-43a3-9066-42b79164e05b",
  "username": "messi"
}, {
  "email": "oo",
  "interactions": [{
    "category": "settings",
    "id": "8b4a26d5-9933-40e3-917b-f28225a2b441",
    "question": "set target spanish",
    "response": "You can change your settings for:\n- Mother language\n- Target language\n- Difficulty level\nWhat would you like to update?",
    "timestamp": 1747424715590,
    "userId": "a2a77cbd-07f0-4cae-89e5-5c083cddf925"
  }],
  "quizResults": [],
  "userId": "a2a77cbd-07f0-4cae-89e5-5c083cddf925",
  "username": "kk"
}, {
  "email": "Ali amin",
  "interactions": [{
    "category": "system",
    "id": "a2ed432c-10cf-4045-b6fa-80c0d0c2fdda",
    "question": "help",
    "response": "\nAvailable commands:\n1. chat - Start a conversation\n2. quiz - Take a quiz\n3. history - View your learning history\n4. preferences - Set your language preferences\n5. help - Show this help message\n6. logout - Log out\n7. exit - Exit the application\n",
    "timestamp": 1747600287490,
    "userId": "9d896c8d-cf48-45db-8463-6d41c19ef434"
  }, {
    "category": "chat",
    "id": "86f2f836-b64f-4433-9ca7-4c3e8a04d6b6",
    "question": "Is it raining today?",
    "response": "coat",
    "timestamp": 1747600250254,
    "userId": "9d896c8d-cf48-45db-8463-6d41c19ef434"
  }, {
    "category": "chat",
    "id": "e36b6542-23fa-4d5e-9c54-0e447f4ccf17",
    "question": "Is it raining today?",
    "response": "yes",
    "timestamp": 1747600236337,
    "userId": "9d896c8d-cf48-45db-8463-6d41c19ef434"
  }, {
    "category": "system",
    "id": "d83f519d-e756-416d-adc7-de265fd0cf98",
    "question": "help",
    "response": "\nAvailable commands:\n1. chat - Start a conversation\n2. quiz - Take a quiz\n3. history - View your learning history\n4. preferences - Set your language preferences\n5. help - Show this help message\n6. logout - Log out\n7. exit - Exit the application\n",
    "timestamp": 1747600222766,
    "userId": "9d896c8d-cf48-45db-8463-6d41c19ef434"
  }, {
    "category": "system",
    "id": "9588aa13-6301-4f5d-9674-dd13e537b68a",
    "question": "analytics",
    "response": "Displayed user analytics",
    "timestamp": 1747600194695,
    "userId": "9d896c8d-cf48-45db-8463-6d41c19ef434"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "a494023d-3984-40c5-8e9e-d17e95ac3440",
    "question": "Quiz Question 5: What is 'city' in German?",
    "response": "Answer: s, Feedback: That's not correct. The correct answer is: Stadt",
    "timestamp": 1747600182180,
    "userId": "9d896c8d-cf48-45db-8463-6d41c19ef434"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "cc1eb061-3b2d-43cc-aa5a-9565b92fd8be",
    "question": "Quiz Question 4: What is 'money' in German?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: That's not correct. The correct answer is: Geld",
    "timestamp": 1747600181095,
    "userId": "9d896c8d-cf48-45db-8463-6d41c19ef434"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "5eb97586-6964-41e7-9031-2628c57c28f3",
    "question": "Quiz Question 3: What is 'weather' in German?",
    "response": "Answer: c, Feedback: That's not correct. The correct answer is: Wetter",
    "timestamp": 1747600180478,
    "userId": "9d896c8d-cf48-45db-8463-6d41c19ef434"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "feddee9a-1014-42d7-bb2b-e5c71dceba48",
    "question": "Quiz Question 2: What is 'time' in German?",
    "response": "Answer: b, Feedback: That's not correct. The correct answer is: Zeit",
    "timestamp": 1747600179600,
    "userId": "9d896c8d-cf48-45db-8463-6d41c19ef434"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "aa5d1827-8bba-4af2-b4a6-03d24bebcb61",
    "question": "Quiz Question 1: What is 'work' in German?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: That's not correct. The correct answer is: Arbeit",
    "timestamp": 1747600178210,
    "userId": "9d896c8d-cf48-45db-8463-6d41c19ef434"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "f8db4d86-6f09-4c36-bd45-80c076e23432",
    "question": "What type of quiz would you like to take?",
    "response": "1",
    "timestamp": 1747600174943,
    "userId": "9d896c8d-cf48-45db-8463-6d41c19ef434"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "a0c141ba-4c14-45c7-90c2-13650d8ce6de",
    "question": "Quiz Question 5: What is 'weather' in German?",
    "response": "Answer: c, Feedback: That's not correct. The correct answer is: Wetter",
    "timestamp": 1747600161016,
    "userId": "9d896c8d-cf48-45db-8463-6d41c19ef434"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "c02ea0da-9a30-4beb-9fa6-e3b6dd5a5a2d",
    "question": "Quiz Question 4: What is 'work' in German?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: That's not correct. The correct answer is: Arbeit",
    "timestamp": 1747600160444,
    "userId": "9d896c8d-cf48-45db-8463-6d41c19ef434"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "e282d180-34e2-4174-85c8-20ec84b587f6",
    "question": "Quiz Question 3: What is 'city' in German?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: That's not correct. The correct answer is: Stadt",
    "timestamp": 1747600159982,
    "userId": "9d896c8d-cf48-45db-8463-6d41c19ef434"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "2da51cc6-dade-4ea2-a809-4409134de032",
    "question": "Quiz Question 2: What is 'money' in German?",
    "response": "Answer: c, Feedback: That's not correct. The correct answer is: Geld",
    "timestamp": 1747600159237,
    "userId": "9d896c8d-cf48-45db-8463-6d41c19ef434"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "4f9290ce-cf87-4cb2-9149-b4ef2c39f641",
    "question": "Quiz Question 1: What is 'time' in German?",
    "response": "Answer: a, Feedback: Correct! Well done!",
    "timestamp": 1747600153006,
    "userId": "9d896c8d-cf48-45db-8463-6d41c19ef434"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "d17a82fc-2c57-4b0d-8f50-8f5d8515f4d9",
    "question": "What type of quiz would you like to take?",
    "response": "1",
    "timestamp": 1747600146910,
    "userId": "9d896c8d-cf48-45db-8463-6d41c19ef434"
  }, {
    "category": "settings",
    "id": "792ac981-46df-4dcd-ae57-a4e73a8de6c6",
    "question": "set target language german",
    "response": "Target language set to German",
    "timestamp": 1747600140932,
    "userId": "9d896c8d-cf48-45db-8463-6d41c19ef434"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "4cd7ab6a-bb9b-4c5b-8b01-8be1f9cacc98",
    "question": "exit quiz",
    "response": "Cancelled quiz setup",
    "timestamp": 1747600130283,
    "userId": "9d896c8d-cf48-45db-8463-6d41c19ef434"
  }, {
    "category": "quiz",
    "id": "b5af07e5-dc40-4ded-93f5-1c812c960eb6",
    "question": "What type of quiz would you like to take?",
    "response": "exit quiz",
    "timestamp": 1747600130276,
    "userId": "9d896c8d-cf48-45db-8463-6d41c19ef434"
  }, {
    "category": "unknown",
    "id": "0c02da44-7a41-46fe-b823-6e2618554c65",
    "question": "start",
    "response": "I'm not sure I understand. Try asking about quizzes, changing settings.",
    "timestamp": 1747600113928,
    "userId": "9d896c8d-cf48-45db-8463-6d41c19ef434"
  }, {
    "category": "system",
    "id": "42651ecb-3d2e-4844-9a13-3268ad3eeaf7",
    "question": "help",
    "response": "\nAvailable commands:\n1. chat - Start a conversation\n2. quiz - Take a quiz\n3. history - View your learning history\n4. preferences - Set your language preferences\n5. help - Show this help message\n6. logout - Log out\n7. exit - Exit the application\n",
    "timestamp": 1747600103335,
    "userId": "9d896c8d-cf48-45db-8463-6d41c19ef434"
  }, {
    "category": "unknown",
    "id": "1f57ca64-416e-4676-9d0a-a5be7a78bf0c",
    "question": "hello",
    "response": "Hello, Ali! I'm your Language Learning Bot. Would you like to practice vocabulary, grammar, or start a quiz?",
    "timestamp": 1747600090694,
    "userId": "9d896c8d-cf48-45db-8463-6d41c19ef434"
  }, {
    "category": "system",
    "id": "3a3f7ee1-94a6-4daa-82a6-2e09fb1ed6ed",
    "question": "settings",
    "response": "Displayed user settings",
    "timestamp": 1747600084268,
    "userId": "9d896c8d-cf48-45db-8463-6d41c19ef434"
  }, {
    "category": "settings",
    "id": "58ace051-7b65-40df-be60-e8fffc44ccb0",
    "question": "settings",
    "response": "You can change your settings for:\n- Mother language\n- Target language\nWhat would you like to update?",
    "timestamp": 1747600084258,
    "userId": "9d896c8d-cf48-45db-8463-6d41c19ef434"
  }, {
    "category": "settings",
    "id": "85d84c2c-d70c-45ce-8692-8b1f6dcb7317",
    "question": "set target language french",
    "response": "Target language set to French",
    "timestamp": 1747600081350,
    "userId": "9d896c8d-cf48-45db-8463-6d41c19ef434"
  }, {
    "category": "settings",
    "id": "36b3621c-3c35-4f8a-b763-5bdaa1a0a295",
    "question": "set mother language english",
    "response": "Mother language set to English",
    "timestamp": 1747600072812,
    "userId": "9d896c8d-cf48-45db-8463-6d41c19ef434"
  }, {
    "category": "system",
    "id": "88467850-dbc4-4ba5-965a-538d5c6cdd9a",
    "question": "prefrences",
    "response": "Displayed user settings",
    "timestamp": 1747600058765,
    "userId": "9d896c8d-cf48-45db-8463-6d41c19ef434"
  }, {
    "category": "settings",
    "id": "314ab09a-cfb7-4687-9fe9-e518ecce311c",
    "question": "settings",
    "response": "You can change your settings for:\n- Mother language\n- Target language\nWhat would you like to update?",
    "timestamp": 1747600058751,
    "userId": "9d896c8d-cf48-45db-8463-6d41c19ef434"
  }, {
    "category": "system",
    "id": "7d90e933-4232-440b-9e49-8f86a41caf1a",
    "question": "help",
    "response": "\nAvailable commands:\n1. chat - Start a conversation\n2. quiz - Take a quiz\n3. history - View your learning history\n4. preferences - Set your language preferences\n5. help - Show this help message\n6. logout - Log out\n7. exit - Exit the application\n",
    "timestamp": 1747600051915,
    "userId": "9d896c8d-cf48-45db-8463-6d41c19ef434"
  }],
  "quizResults": [{
    "correctAnswers": 0,
    "id": "8241473c-e4f5-4ba4-809e-de19db429f37",
    "questions": [{
      "correctAnswer": "Arbeit",
      "isCorrect": false,
      "question": "What is 'work' in German?",
      "userAnswer": "schule"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Zeit",
      "isCorrect": false,
      "question": "What is 'time' in German?",
      "userAnswer": "tag"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Wetter",
      "isCorrect": false,
      "question": "What is 'weather' in German?",
      "userAnswer": "klima"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Geld",
      "isCorrect": false,
      "question": "What is 'money' in German?",
      "userAnswer": "zeit"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Stadt",
      "isCorrect": false,
      "question": "What is 'city' in German?",
      "userAnswer": "s"
    }],
    "quizType": "Vocabulary",
    "score": 0.0,
    "timestamp": 1747600182187,
    "totalQuestions": 5,
    "userAnswers": ["schule", "tag", "klima", "zeit", "s"],
    "userId": "9d896c8d-cf48-45db-8463-6d41c19ef434"
  }, {
    "correctAnswers": 1,
    "id": "edfd9275-0ead-49d4-b303-00d4cc3363a6",
    "questions": [{
      "correctAnswer": "Zeit",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "question": "What is 'time' in German?",
      "userAnswer": "Zeit"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Geld",
      "isCorrect": false,
      "question": "What is 'money' in German?",
      "userAnswer": "preis"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Stadt",
      "isCorrect": false,
      "question": "What is 'city' in German?",
      "userAnswer": "land"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Arbeit",
      "isCorrect": false,
      "question": "What is 'work' in German?",
      "userAnswer": "schule"
    }, {
      "correctAnswer": "Wetter",
      "isCorrect": false,
      "question": "What is 'weather' in German?",
      "userAnswer": "klima"
    }],
    "quizType": "Vocabulary",
    "score": 20.0,
    "timestamp": 1747600161024,
    "totalQuestions": 5,
    "userAnswers": ["Zeit", "preis", "land", "schule", "klima"],
    "userId": "9d896c8d-cf48-45db-8463-6d41c19ef434"
  }],
  "userId": "9d896c8d-cf48-45db-8463-6d41c19ef434",
  "username": "Ali"
}]